('190_F.3d_1342', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ATLAS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('POWDER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Hanex_Products', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IRECO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INCORPORATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ICI_Explosives_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
IRECO INCORPORATED ICI_Explosives_USA Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1041', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Sept._7,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Licensee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('explosive_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('intervened', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('right', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Wyoming', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Wyoming Alan B. Johnson Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('sufficient_aeration', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('porous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('interstitial_air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1343', 'LS', '', 'O') ('Stanford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Owen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fabian', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Clendenin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Salt_Lake_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Utah', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Hanex_Products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cullen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Battle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Stanford B. Owen Utah W. Cullen Battle Robert A. Garda Jr. Jon C. Martinson
__NEW_SENT__
('Gordon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roberts', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Parsons', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Behle', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Latimer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Salt_Lake_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Utah', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IRECO_Incorporated', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ICI_Explosives_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Speirs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gordon L. Roberts Parsons Behle & Latimer Utah IRECO_Incorporated ICI_Explosives_USA Inc. C. Kevin Speirs
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Wyoming', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._4111,727', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Wyoming U.S. U.S. Patent
__NEW_SENT__
('RE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('33,788', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Atlas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Powder', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Atlas', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('IRECO_Incorporated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('IRECO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Atlas Powder Company IRECO_Incorporated ( IRECO
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3161,551', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Egly', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.K.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1306,546', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Butterworth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
two U.S. U.K. Butterworth
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('interpreted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explosive_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('detonate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*1344', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('explosives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('oxidizers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reacts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('expanding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explosion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Composite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('explosives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mix', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('widely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('economical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('explosive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('ammonium_nitrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fuel_oil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANFO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ANFO_explosives', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mix', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('94', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ammonium_nitrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('AN', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fuel_oil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
about 94 % 6 % FO
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('AN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('porous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prills', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dense', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prills', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Stengel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('flakes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'VB', '', 'O') ('AN', 'NN', '', 'O')
AN Stengel
__NEW_SENT__
('ANFO_explosives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disadvantages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('wet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conditions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dissolve', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('AN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explosive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unusable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damp', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('settings', 'NNS', '', 'O')
First AN
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('ANFO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('weak', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('explosive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interstitial_air', 'DT', '', 'O') ('occupies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('considerable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('decreasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('explosive_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('volume', 'NN', '', 'O')
Second
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shortcomings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('explosive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('experts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('water-in-oil_emulsions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emulsions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dissolved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dispersed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surrounds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('resistant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('solving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ANFO', 'NNP', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Emulsions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explosive', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('explosive_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Emulsions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disadvantage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Emulsions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('detonate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('unless', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sensitized', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sensitivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blasting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ease', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('igniting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('explosion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Experts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sensitize', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('emulsions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gassing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('microballoons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('throughout', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gassing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('microballoons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('tiny_gas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('air_bubbles', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('throughout', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('detonation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pockets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('compress', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('heat', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('igniting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tiny_gas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('air_bubbles', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('spots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('propagate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explosion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('explosives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANFO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('blasting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unsensitized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('water-in-oil_emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blasting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blasting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('10_to_40', 'JJ', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('greasy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('water-in-oil_emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('60_to_90', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('undissolved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('particulate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('3_to_15', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('2_to_15', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('70_to_90', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('powerful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ammonium_nitrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('powerful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('oxidizer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('constituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ammonium_nitrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('sufficient_aeration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entrapped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enhance', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sensitivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('emulsified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.BIG_TOKEN__1_to_5__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('oil-in-water', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('water-in-oil', 'CD', '', 'O') ('emulsifier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disperse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('phase', 'NN', '', 'O')
10_to_40 % 60_to_90 % about 3_to_15 % about 2_to_15 % 70_to_90 % 0.BIG_TOKEN__1_to_5__BIG_TOKEN %
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Underline', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Underline
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Atlas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continental', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hawaii', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Atlas U.S. Hawaii
__NEW_SENT__
('Atlas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('commenced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IRECO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Atlas IRECO 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('course', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Clay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Robert Clay the United States Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Atlas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_application', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conducted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
first October 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Clay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suspension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
February 1987
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('waiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Clay', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reinstate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
several years 1990
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_reissue_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('surrender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1992
__NEW_SENT__
('Later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1345', 'UH', '', 'O') ('year', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Egly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Butterworth', 'NNP', '', 'O')
1992 1 2 14 one two
__NEW_SENT__
('Egly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Butterworth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('blasting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water-in-oil_emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ANFO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingredients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Butterworth
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explosive_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clay_reissue_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
