('323_F.3d_1324', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ABBOTT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
ABBOTT LABORATORIES Plaintiff-Appellant
__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Industrie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Et', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sante', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Laboratoires_Fournier_S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NOVOPHARM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LIMITED', 'RB', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VBP', 'ORG', 'I')
Fournier Industrie Et Sante NOVOPHARM LIMITED Defendant-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('No._02-1387', 'JJ', 'GPE', 'B')
No._02-1387
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('March_20,_2003', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('April_30,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cholesterol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Darrah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2002_WL_433584', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois John W. Darrah J. 2002_WL_433584
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1325', 'AFX', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I')
James A
__NEW_SENT__
('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Day', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Reavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pogue', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O')
White Jones Day Reavis & Pogue Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reidy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Marlott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heverin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Daniel E. Reidy John A. Marlott Timothy J. Heverin
__NEW_SENT__
('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ossola', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Porter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Industrie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sante', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", "''", 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Laboratoires_Fournier_S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bickham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('A.M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Charles D. Ossola Arnold & Porter Washington DC Fournier Industrie Sante ' Timothy C. Bickham Scott A.M
__NEW_SENT__
('Chambers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Shanks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Shanks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alexandria', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('VA.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gagala', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leydig', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Voit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mark Shanks Shanks & Herbert Alexandria Bruce M. Gagala Leydig Voit & Mayer Ltd. Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hefner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
M. Daniel Hefner
__NEW_SENT__
('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wolfe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Blank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rome', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Comisky', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('McCauley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ohly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Neil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Charles R. Wolfe Rome Comisky & McCauley LLP Washington Impax Laboratories Inc. D. Christopher Ohly Neil R. White
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Industrie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sante', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Laboratoires_Fournier_S.A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4,895,726', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Fournier Industrie Laboratoires_Fournier_S.A. Fournier Abbott Northern_District Illinois Novopharm U.S. 4,895,726
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Labs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Abbott Labs
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nos._00', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2141', 'CD', '', 'O') ('00_C_5094', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('01_C_1914', 'JJ', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2002_WL_433584', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2002', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dist', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Novopharm Ltd. 00_C_5094 01_C_1914 2002_WL_433584 2002 U.S. Dist
__NEW_SENT__
('LEXIS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4659', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Mar.20', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Mar.20 2002
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('therapeutic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('8_and_9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hyperlipidemia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hypercholesterolemia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('11_and_12', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
¡¬726_patent 1-7 8_and_9 10
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Abbott Fournier
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Drug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1326', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('permitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate_capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Abbott NDA the United States Food and Drug Administration FDA Fournier the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tradename', 'NN', '', 'O') ('TRICOR', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('THE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
Abbott TRICOR
__NEW_SENT__
('Novopharm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1999', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('micronized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Abbreviated New Drug Application December 1999 FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Novopharm 21 355 2 IV
__NEW_SENT__
('Under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('files', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('give', 'VB', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pertains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('I', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NN', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('II', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 2 355 2 NDA 355 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('provisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('notified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O')
Novopharm Fournier Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
21 2 Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B')
Fournier Abbott Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TRICORTHE_R', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate_capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Novopharm TRICORTHE_R ¡¬726_patent Novopharm 35 271 2
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('provision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pertinent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('shall', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('submit-', 'VB', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('505', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cosmetic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('codified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') (']..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Act', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Title', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LAW', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'I') ('United', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Code', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug..', 'FW', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
section 505 the Federal Food Drug and Cosmetic Act 21 Act Title 21 of the United States Code
__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 271 2 2000
__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('things', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('staying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('19', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('expiration', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('date', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prohibiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('importing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Fournier Abbott Novopharm January 19 2009 expiration date Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Novopharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('twice', 'RB', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B')
Fournier Abbott Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceeding.1', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('*BIG_TOKEN__1327_Claims_1__BIG_TOKEN', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('independent_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('define', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
10 ¡¬726_patent only two 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('therapeutic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gelatin_capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('especially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hyperlipidemia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hypercholesterolemia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mean_particle_size', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('co-micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('£g', 'NN', '', 'O')
less than 15
__NEW_SENT__
('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
10
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vivo', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('carried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate/solid_surfactant_mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particle_size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('powder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('£g', 'NN', '', 'O')
less than 15
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'I') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 of the ¡¬726_patent 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('co-micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('replaced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mean_particle_size', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('£g', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
less than 15
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('impliedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('intimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mixed', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬726_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._35-43', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matrix', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particle_size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('50_and_500', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('microns', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I')
Fournier between 50_and_500 microns
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('suggest', 'VB', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('suggested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fournier
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('slip', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2-3', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B')
2-3
__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diameter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('fifteen', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('microns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('suggested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
less than fifteen
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('observed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intimate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('significantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('extent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('achieved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('micronizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('micronized_fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬726_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('alteration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mixtures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('micronizing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('micronized_fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Fournier
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lauryl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sulfate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('SLS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate/SLS', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lactose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('starch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1328', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
fenofibrate/SLS
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4-5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
4-5
__NEW_SENT__
('Elaborating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('indicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anything', 'NN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('micronized..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('excipient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
12
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('co-microniz', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-ed', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('-ation', '.', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1_and_10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('encompass', 'VB', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate/solid_surfactant_mixture', 'XX', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ingredients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('objected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O')
10 Novopharm Fournier Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('interpreting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wholly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
13
__NEW_SENT__
('Having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('pre-micronizing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pre-micronized_fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dry', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mixed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lactose', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('monohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pregelatinized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('starch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('croscarmellose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('crosspovidone', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('granulating_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prepared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dissolving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('povidone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SLS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O')
SLS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('granulating_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dry', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate/excipient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('subjected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('wet_granulation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uniform', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mass', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mass', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('granulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('SLS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SLS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('granulated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('dry', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('croscarmellose', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('crosspovidone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stearate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('granules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('pass', 'VB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('#', '$', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('eventual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('encapsulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gelatin_capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O')
16
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('opposed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wet_granulation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('constitute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Fournier Abbott Novopharm Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Nonetheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('micronized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('already', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('just', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Novopharm Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
14
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('suggest', 'VB', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid_surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-micronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('viewed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1329', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬726_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lead', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('relinquished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('micronizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fenofibrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('micronized_fenofibrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Fournier Fournier ¡¬726_patent Fournier
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('14-16', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relinquished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('coverage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prevail', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Novopharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fournier Abbott Novopharm Novopharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Fournier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Fournier Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
