('346_F.3d_1075', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ACCO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('BRANDS', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kensington_Technology_Group', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICRO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SECURITY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DEVICES', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PC_Guardian', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
MICRO SECURITY DEVICES INC. PC_Guardian
__NEW_SENT__
('No._02-1567', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Oct._7,_2003', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('portable_electronic_devices', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('2002_WL_1735385', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Susan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Illston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of California Susan Illston J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('neither', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('equivalently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1076', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('K.T', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cherian', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Townsend', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Townsend', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Crew', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Townsend Townsend Crew LLP San Francisco California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.E', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Brian A.E
__NEW_SENT__
('Smith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McFarlane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hodge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert A. McFarlane Sean Paul Hodge
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McCormack', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kolisch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hartwell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Portland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Oregon', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
John M. McCormack Kolisch Hartwell P.C. Portland Oregon
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Owen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dukelow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Owen W. Dukelow
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('ACCO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brands', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kensington_Technology_Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Micro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Security', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Devices', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PC_Guardian', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('PC_Guardian', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'NN', '', 'O')
ACCO Brands Inc. Kensington_Technology_Group Micro Security Devices Inc. PC_Guardian United_States_District_Court Northern_District California PC_Guardian United States Patent
__NEW_SENT__
('B1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('5,502,989', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('989', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
5,502,989 989
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PC_Guardian.1', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
PC_Guardian.1
__NEW_SENT__
('DISCUSSION', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
DISCUSSION
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬989_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('portable_electronic_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 10 10
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portable_electronic_device', 'XX', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exterior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('security_slot', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('object', 'NN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portable_electronic_device', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proximate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('peripheral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('profile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('complementary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preselected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dimensions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('security_slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('permit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rotatable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unlocked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('removable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1077', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('retained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('security_slot_proximate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('locked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('rotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unlocked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Emphasis', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Emphasis
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('PC_Guardian_devices', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Notebook_Guardian', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Notebook_Guardian', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('2001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
PC_Guardian_devices Notebook_Guardian 2001
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('clause', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('actively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('security_slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unlocked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('post', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('peg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('security_slot_proximate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('locked_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('rotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slot_engagement_member', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unlocked_position', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verb', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ACCO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*6', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Kensington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('challenges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PC_Guardian_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kensington
__NEW_SENT__
