('566_F.3d_999', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ALTANA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wyeth', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TEVA', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
ALTANA PHARMA AG Wyeth TEVA PHARMACEUTICALS USA INC. Teva Pharmaceuticals Industries Ltd. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('Kudco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ireland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Schwarz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Kudco Ireland Limited Schwarz Pharma Inc. Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sun', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Advanced', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Centre', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries Ltd. Sun Pharmaceutical Advanced Research Centre Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1039', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('May_14,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exclusive_licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antiulcer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consolidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('532_F.Supp.2d_666', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Jose', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Linares', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey 532_F.Supp.2d_666 Jose L. Linares J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Owner
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ward', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('District_Judge', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('sitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('designation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Ward District_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial_merit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('irreparable_harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Named', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Expert', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Lester', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mitscher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ph.D', '.', '', 'O')
Lester A. Mitscher
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1001', 'UH', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmer_Cutler_Pickering_Hale', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Door', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
William F. Lee Boston MA
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jakes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kathleen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Daley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Farabow', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Malley", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wexler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hastings', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Janofsky', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Walker_LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
J. Michael Jakes Kathleen A. Daley Finnegan Henderson Farabow Garrett & Dunner L.L.P. Washington DC Joseph M. O'Malley Jr. Bruce M. Wexler Paul Hastings Janofsky & Walker_LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dittmann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hastings', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Janofsy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Walker_LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McElwain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wigmore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmer_Cutler_Pickering_Hale', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Door', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Eric W. Dittmann Paul Hastings Janofsy & Walker_LLP New_York NY William G. McElwain Amy K. Wigmore Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schuman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carlson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Caspers', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Vandenburgh', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lindquist', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1002', ',', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mark D. Schuman Vandenburgh & Lindquist Minneapolis Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jeffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ali', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Werner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Samuel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lockner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sarah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stensland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jeffer Ali Todd S. Werner Samuel T. Lockner Sarah M. Stensland
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sorenson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merchant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gould', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Christopher J. Sorenson P.C. Minneapolis
__NEW_SENT__
('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stuart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pontani', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lieberman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Michael C. Stuart Cohen Pontani Lieberman & Pavane LLP New_York NY Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Julia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vincent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fazzari', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Martin B. Pavane S. Kim Vincent M. Fazzari
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Podvey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Meanor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Catenacci', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hildner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cocoziello', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Chattman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newark', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Gregory D. Miller P.C. Newark
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WARD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('District_Judge', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN GAJARSA Circuit Judges WARD
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('District_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WARD', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Circuit NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('WARD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District_Judge', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wyeth', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LOC', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Altana Pharma AG Wyeth Altana the District of New_Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wyeth', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('accuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Sun', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('et_al', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellants Altana Pharma AG Wyeth Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc. Sun
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4758,579', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('579', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('Wyeth', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive_licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Wyeth the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
February 9 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('USPTO', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('5-year', 'CD', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('156', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman_Act', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('579', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('expires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_19,_2010', 'NNP', '', 'O')
January 4 2004 the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office USPTO 35 156 ¡¬ 579
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound_pantoprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('antiulcer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Protonix', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('THE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
Altana Protonix
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound_pantoprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belongs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proton', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inhibitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastric_acid_pump', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('triggered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastric_acid_pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('secretory_canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('parietal_cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('via', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('H', 'NN', '', 'O') ('+', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('K', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('+-ATPase', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('triggered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transports', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('protons', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('H', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('+', 'XX', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inside', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parietal_cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('secretory_canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exchange', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potassium_ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('K', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('+', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transports', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inner', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O')
K +
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('availability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potassium_ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('attributable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('migration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('KCI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inside', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parietal_cell', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reabsorbs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('K', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('+', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exchange', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('H', 'NN', '', 'O') ('+', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extrusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-remains', ':', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrochloric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('HCI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('secreted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O')
HCI
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastric_acid_pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastric_acid_pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('understood', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('579', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬ 579
__NEW_SENT__
('Part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uncertainty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('attributable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1003', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('prodrugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('active_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('typically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
about 5 about 7
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('acid-activated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prodrugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('active_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('highly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acidic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('secretory_canaliculus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('parietal_cells', 'NNS', '', 'O')
about 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('active_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('binds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cysteine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amino', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pump', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('binding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastric_acid_pump', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('commercialized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Prilosec_THE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')
first the U.S. Food and Drug Administration FDA 1989
__NEW_SENT__
('Omeprazole', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('synthesized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hassle', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1979', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4255,431', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬431_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Omeprazole first AB Hassle AstraZeneca 1979
__NEW_SENT__
('Omeprazole', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Prilosec_THE_R', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('today', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blockbuster', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('suffer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heartburn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('symptoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('stem', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gastro-esophageal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflux', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disease', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GERD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Prilosec_THE_R today
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('successful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('commercialization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Prilosec_THE_R', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Byk', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('Gulden', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('predecessor', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('develop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('PPIs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compete', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O')
Byk Gulden Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('efforts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issuance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4555,518', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmacology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effectiveness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
18 four
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('chosen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('testing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
one 18 12
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('structurally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬518_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Pantoprazole', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('very', 'RB', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compound', 'VB', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
12
__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('main', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('molecular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('backbone', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benzimidazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methylsulfinyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bridge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬579_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2:5-15', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right-most', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('above', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radicals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R4', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('579', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1-3C-alkoxy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radicals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('R2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R4', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1-3C-alkoxy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('atom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-H', 'NFP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1-3C-alkyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬ R3 one
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('2:28-31', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radical_consisting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CnH2n+i', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-CH3', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkoxy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radical_consisting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('linked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('simple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methoxy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-OCH3', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pantoprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('radical', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('3-position', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O')
12
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-CH3', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('*1004', 'FW', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pantoprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxy_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-OCH3', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
12
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_6,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman_Act', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('requesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Protonix', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('THE_R', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Teva Abbreviated New Drug Application FDA Protonix
__NEW_SENT__
('Sun', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ANDA_applications', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_1,_2005', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('June_25,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Sun ANDA_applications March_1,_2005
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sun', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('certifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conjunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('respective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ANDA_applications', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
Teva Sun IV ANDA_applications
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA_applications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Altana', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sun', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
ANDA_applications Teva Sun
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_22,_2007', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sun', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid.1', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬579_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('teachings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sachs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('article,2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Bryson_article,3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬431_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Teva Sun 1 Altana ¡¬518_patent 2 3 4 ¡¬431_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('modification', 'NN', '', 'O')
12 ¡¬518_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sachs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('better', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O')
one 4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa_value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('measured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logarithmic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('willingness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('accept', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('donate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proton', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('numerical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('acidic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pH', 'XX', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('stable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
5 4 5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sachs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa_value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('characteristic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parietal_cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Bryson_article', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa_value', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bryson_article
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxy_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('3-position', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bryson
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬431_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feasibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substituting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxy_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('3-position', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PPI', 'NNP', '', 'O')
¡¬431_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('considering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('lacked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial_merit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1005', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('modification', 'NN', '', 'O')
one 12
__NEW_SENT__
('Next', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sachs', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('modify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('achieve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Sachs one 12 4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Bryson_article', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxy_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('3-position', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridine_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa_value', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pKa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Bryson_article 4
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬431_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substitution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('feasible', 'JJ', '', 'O')
¡¬431_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indicia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disregard', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('irreparable_harm', 'NN', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('harms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('irreparable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('irreversible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('price', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erosion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('decrease', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('share', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('service', 'NN', '', 'O') ('debts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('employee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('layoffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opportunities', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('irreparable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('able', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('satisfy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('prevail', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('suffer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('irreparable_harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Altana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('irreparable_harm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Altana
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1292 1
__NEW_SENT__
