('601_F.3d_1333', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United_States', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United_States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ANASCAPE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LTD.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NINTENDO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('OF', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
NINTENDO OF
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1500', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_13,_2010', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
April_13,_2010
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_1,_2010', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hand-operated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('controllers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer_screen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('television_display', 'NN', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('video_games', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Clark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('duly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('post-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('further_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas Ron Clark J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'VB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gajarsa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gajarsa Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1334', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Douglas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cawley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKool', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Douglas A. Cawley McKool Smith Dallas
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Sochia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Callahan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Anthony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garza', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David Sochia Steven C. Callahan Anthony M. Garza
__NEW_SENT__
('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cutler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pickering', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hale', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dorr', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
William F. Lee Wilmer Cutler Pickering Hale Boston MA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lauren', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fletcher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gunther', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alexandra', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('McTague', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sadaf', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Abdullah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lauren B. Fletcher Robert J. Gunther Jr. Alexandra McTague Sadaf R. Abdullah
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Faris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Presta', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gordon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Klancnik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nixon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Vanderhye', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Scholer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert W. Faris Joseph S. Presta Gordon P. Klancnik Nixon & Vanderhye P.C. Arlington James S. Blank Kay Scholer LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN GAJARSA DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nintendo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Nintendo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('video', 'NN', '', 'O') ('game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('controllers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6,906,700', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Anascape', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('damages.1', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('duly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('post-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('further_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nintendo of America Inc. United_States_District_Court Texas Nintendo 6,906,700 ¡¬700_patent Anascape Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nintendo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Microsoft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('settled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Nintendo Microsoft
__NEW_SENT__
('DISCUSSION', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
DISCUSSION
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hand-operated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('controllers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer_screen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('television_display', 'NN', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('video_games', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manipulate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('graphic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('procedure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hand_inputs', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hand_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('implemented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('handles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('joysticks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('trackballs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('sensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('translated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('electronically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('linear', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rotational', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('movements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('graphic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hand_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('move', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('directions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('degrees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('freedom', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('DOF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lexicon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O')
six DOF
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hand_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('linear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('axes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('forward/backward', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('left/right', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('up/down', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rotational', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('linear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('axes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('roll', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pitch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('yaw', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
three three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('6,222,525', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬525_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
¡¬700_patent November 16 2000 6,222,525
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('525', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('July_5,_1996', 'NNP', '', 'O')
¡¬
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('120', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('title', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States..', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('shall', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*1335', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application..', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 120 first section 112 United_States.. application..
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reiffin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Microsoft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('214_F.3d_1342', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1345-46', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2000', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ensure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('overreach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('contribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Reiffin Microsoft Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rationale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whose', 'WP$', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('antedate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Moba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('B.V.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Diamond', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Automation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('325_F.3d_1306', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1319-20', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Ralston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Purina', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Far-Mar-Co', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('772_F.2d_1570', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1575', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1985', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
See Moba B.V. Diamond Automation Inc. 1319-20 Ralston Purina Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('Anascape', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('conceded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DualShock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('controller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Goto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DualShock', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ("''", "''", 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('controller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Anascape Sony DualShock 1998 Goto 1998 Sony DualShock 2 '' United_States October 2000
__NEW_SENT__
('Anascape', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_5,_1996', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O')
Anascape July_5,_1996
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('principal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
