('763_F.3d_1354', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('APOTEX', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Canadian', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'WRB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Delaware_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('UCB', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Delaware_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kremers', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Urban', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Delaware_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
APOTEX Canadian Corporation Apotex_Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Schwarz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Delaware_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Llc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Perrigo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', '', 'O')
Schwarz Pharma INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2013-1674', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._15,_2014', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Dec._16,_2014', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hypertension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('moexipril_magnesium', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Florida', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Middlebrooks', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('970_F.Supp.2d_1297', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Florida Donald M. Middlebrooks J. 970_F.Supp.2d_1297
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Reyna Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirmatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('misrepresented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1355', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Breisblatt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Katten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Muchin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosenman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert B. Breisblatt Katten Muchin Rosenman LLP Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kuchii', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Masar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rubin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jackson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Eric C. Cohen Craig M. Kuchii Martin S. Masar III Howard R. Rubin Christopher D. Jackson Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Adam', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Gahtan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('N.Y.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Adam Gahtan White & Case LLP New York N.Y.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Dimitrios', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Drivas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Glancy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Amit', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thakore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('And', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Laura', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Moran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Dimitrios T. Drivas Christopher J. Glancy Amit H. Thakore Laura T. Moran
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('REYNA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HUGHES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('REYNA', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'PRP$', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Florida', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._6767,556', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('judicially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('disclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('coverage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('laches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('recovering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pre-suit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
REYNA Circuit_Judge Apotex Inc. Apotex_Corp. Apotex United_States_District_Court Florida 1 Apotex U.S. Patent No._6767,556 2 Apotex 3 4 Apotex ¡¬556_patent 5 Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('UCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('970_F.Supp.2d_1297', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.Fla.2013', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Apotex Inc. UCB Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_Patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('titled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Compositions', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Comprising', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Moexipril', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Magnesium', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('old', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬556_patent `` Pharmaceutical Compositions Comprising Moexipril Magnesium '' ten years old
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_27,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Canadian', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_5,_2000', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Canadian April_5,_2000
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bernard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sherman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('founder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('chairman', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('wrote', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('556', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('sole', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bernard Charles Sherman Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sherman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('leads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('himself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('hundred', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Sherman Apotex approximately one hundred Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('He', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('moexipril_tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Moexipril', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angiotensin-converting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ACE', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('inhibitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('hypertension', 'NN', '', 'O')
ACE
__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ACE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('inhibitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Moexipril', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('acid_addition_salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('moexipril_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('susceptible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('instability', 'NN', '', 'O')
ACE Moexipril
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('moexipril_tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mostly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moexipril_magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('moexipril', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('acid_addition_salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_magnesium_compound', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬556_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2_ll._53', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-56', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1356', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('captured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moexipril_magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('moexipril', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_magnesium_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('80', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moexipril', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('moexipril', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moexipril_magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O')
greater than 80 %
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moexipril_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reacted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hydroxide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('weak', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('carbonate', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('moexipril_magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'LS', '', 'O') ('2_l._66', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-col.', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('3_l._5', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬556_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('accomplished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dry', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('carried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬556_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('2_ll._38', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-45', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('evaporated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('compressed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('wet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('granulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'DATE', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
at least the 1980s
__NEW_SENT__
