('464_F.3d_1286', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ALZA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MYLAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MYLAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMCEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
MYLAN LABORATORIES INC. MYLAN PHARMCEUTICALS INC. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._06-1019', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._6,_2006', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Sept._6,_2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended-release', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('urinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('incontinence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Northern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('West', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Irene', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keeley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('388_F.Supp.2d_717', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Northern District Irene M. Keeley 388_F.Supp.2d_717
__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gajarsa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Gajarsa Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1288', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Diskant', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patterson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Belknap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Webb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tyler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plantiff-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Gregory L. Diskant Patterson Belknap Webb & Tyler LLP New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.D', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jeffrey I.D
__NEW_SENT__
('Lewis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McCormick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Lewis Richard J. McCormick
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wyss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wiley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fielding', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John B. Wyss Wiley Rein & Fielding LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wallace', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scheffel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James H. Wallace Jr. Kevin P. Anderson Robert J. Scheffel
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Alza_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Alza', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('13_and_14', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._6124,3551', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'355_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Alza 1-3 11 13_and_14 U.S. Mylan Laboratories Inc. Mylan Pharmaceuticals Inc. Mylan
__NEW_SENT__
('Alza_Corp.', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('388_F.Supp.2d_717', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.W.Va.2005', 'ADD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Alza', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Alza_Corp. Mylan Labs. Inc. Alza II
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arose', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Applications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('once-a-day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extended', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-incontinence', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('720', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Alza', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ditropan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('XLTHE_R', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mylan two Abbreviated New Drug Applications 720 Ditropan XLTHE_R
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('738', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
738
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arose', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('filings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once-daily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('controlled-release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mylan 's Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('Oxybutynin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('urinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('incontinence', 'NN', '', 'O')
Oxybutynin
__NEW_SENT__
('Once-a-day', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('dosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('usual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('benefits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('convenience', 'NN', '', 'O') ('steady-dosing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('possibly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('absorption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metabolite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('leads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side-effects', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Once-a-day
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'355_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Claim 2
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sustained-release', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('urge_incontinence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('therapeutic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('delivers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0_to_1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0_to_4', 'CD', '', 'O') ('hours', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('to', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('2.5', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('0_to_8', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('hours', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2.BIG_TOKEN__75_to_4__BIG_TOKEN25', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0_to_1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'TIME', 'B') ('hours', 'NNS', 'TIME', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3.75', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0_to_24', 'CD', 'TIME', 'B') ('hours', 'NNS', 'TIME', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1289', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('urge_incontinence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 mg to 2.5 mg in 0_to_8 hours 4 hours 3.75 mg to 5 0_to_24 hours
__NEW_SENT__
('col._17,_ll._31-38', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'355_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Order', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('reported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alza_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('349_F.Supp.2d_1002_(N.D.W.Va.2004)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Alza', 'UH', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Markman Order Alza_Corp. Mylan Labs. Inc. Alza I ``
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('deliver', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vivo', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('release', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('tract', 'NN', '', 'O')
GI
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1019', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1019
__NEW_SENT__
('Alza', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('present', 'VB', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('released', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('tract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'355_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mylan GI
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('offer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('types', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('released', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitro', 'FW', '', 'O') ('dissolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accumulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oxybutynin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bloodstream', 'NN', '', 'O')
two 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alza', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alza
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'355_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('need', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Alza', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alza
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
