('160_F.3d_1350', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Carl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('BAI', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('L', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WINGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', "''", '', 'O') ('d/b/a', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wings', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Carl B. BAI L & Wings
__NEW_SENT__
('Great', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('World', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Elufa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fashions', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
Great World Co. New_York Ltd. Elufa Fashions Inc. Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Nov._3,_1998', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Nov._3,_1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKenna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('1997_WL_527870', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Lawrence M. McKenna J. 1997_WL_527870
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1351', 'UH', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rogers', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wells', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
John E. Daniel Rogers & Wells New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Allen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rubenstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gottlieb', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rackman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Reisman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Allen I. Rubenstein P.C. New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Carl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'UH', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('L_Wings', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ('game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('4,017,076', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Carl B. Bai United_States_District_Court L & 1 Bai 4,017,076
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('L_Wings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._95', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Bai v. L &
__NEW_SENT__
('10824', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('LMM', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('1997_WL_527870', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y', 'NN', '', 'O')
10824
__NEW_SENT__
('Aug.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Aug. 22 1997
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1352', 'FW', '', 'O') ('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'076_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Bai
__NEW_SENT__
('He', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wings', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wings 1
__NEW_SENT__
('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 one
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('saucer-', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Frisbee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('THE_R-shaped', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Frisbee
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('backside', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('largely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('flat', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('middle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('curved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ends', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('excludes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Wings', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('largely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('flat', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wings
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
three 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fabric_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('constitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('missile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thrown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('thereagainst', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dish', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fabric_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('spaced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therewith', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('present', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resilient_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('deflectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('struck', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('missile', 'NN', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Muchnick', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,953,030', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1,633,926', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Lemelson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('et', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('al.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,857,566', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hartel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,378,260', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3 four Muchnick 3,953,030 1,633,926 3,857,566 Hartel 3,378,260
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dish-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hartel_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lemelson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lemelson_target', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hand-held', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('kind', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gloves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Muchnick', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Lemelson Lemelson_target Muchnick Craig
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('canceled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('incorporate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2_and_3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('add', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Bai 2_and_3 1
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('remarked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('amending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('details', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1 Bai 1
__NEW_SENT__
('He', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gloves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Muchnick', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('functions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lemelson_target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O')
Muchnick Craig
__NEW_SENT__
('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hartel_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('summarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('believed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('irrelevant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Bai
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target_game', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dish-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic_member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1353', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic_member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('palm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('player', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fabric_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dish-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic_member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('constitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('missile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thrown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('thereagainst', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fabric_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic_member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('spaced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inner', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('present', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resilient_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('deflectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('struck', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('missile', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wings', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bai Wings
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cross-motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('focusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('briefs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('addressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Supreme', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Warner-Jenkinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hilton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Davis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chem', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('520_U.S._17', 'CD', '', 'O') ('117_S.Ct._1040', 'CD', '', 'O') ('137_L.Ed.2d_146', 'CD', '', 'O') ('41_USPQ2d_1865_(1997)', 'CD', '', 'O')
the Supreme Court Warner-Jenkinson
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('structures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sphere', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nevertheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sphere', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('apparently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pictured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('close', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exactly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1997_WL_527870', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*2', 'FW', '', 'O')
Bai
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('perceptibly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('flattened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1997_WL_527870', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*2', 'FW', '', 'O')
Bai
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unrelated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bai 103 Bai
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1997_WL_527870', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*4-*5', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'VB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Bai', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MAGIC_CATCH', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Bai 1
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1997_WL_527870', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*5', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1 1994
__NEW_SENT__
