('554_F.3d_982', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('BOSTON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SCIENTIFIC', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'I') ('SCIMED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Boston_Scientific_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CORDIS', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
BOSTON SCIENTIFIC SCIMED INC. Johnson & Johnson Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1073', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._15,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_24,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expandable_stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug-eluting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('434_F.Supp.2d_308', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_2775087', 'CD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*983', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Diskant', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patterson_Belknap_Webb', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tyler_LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gregory L. Diskant & Tyler_LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Eugene', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gelernter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Timmons', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Irena', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Royzman', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Eugene M. Gelernter Michael J. Timmons Scott B. Howard Irena
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Constantine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Trela', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Constantine L. Trela Jr. Sidley Austin LLP Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kathleen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Crotty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patterson_Belknap_Webb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tyler_LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kathleen M. Crotty Patterson_Belknap_Webb & Tyler_LLP of New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weiss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Charles A. Weiss Kenyon & Kenyon LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DeLucia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Elizabeth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gardner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Levy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard L. DeLucia Elizabeth A. Gardner Michael K. Levy
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6,120,536', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬536_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Cordis Corporation Johnson & Johnson Inc. Cordis the District of Delaware JMOL 8 6,120,536
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Boston_Scientific_Scimed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cordis_Corp.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('No._03-283-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SLR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2005_WL_1322946', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('U.S._Dist', 'NN', '', 'O')
See Boston_Scientific_Scimed Inc. 2005
__NEW_SENT__
('LEXIS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('10735', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('June_3,_2005', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Claim_Construction_Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Boston_Scientific_Scimed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cordis_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('434_F.Supp.2d_308', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2006', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Opinion_Denying_JMOL', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Boston_Scientific_Scimed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cordis_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._03-027-', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SLR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('03-283-SLR', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_2775087', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del', 'NN', '', 'O')
June_3,_2005 Boston_Scientific_Scimed Inc. 434_F.Supp.2d_308 Boston_Scientific_Scimed Inc. Nos._03-027- 2007_WL_2775087
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('24', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Sept. 24 2007
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('536', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Boston_Scientific_Scimed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Boston_Scientific_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Boston_Scientific', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('own', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬536_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug-eluting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expandable_stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O')
Boston_Scientific_Scimed Inc. Boston_Scientific ¡¬536_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Boston_Scientific', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*984', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬536_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Cordis March 2003 Cordis 8
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 8 6 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('read', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 6 and 8 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medical_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('implantable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('metallic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metallic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('biologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undercoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrophobic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elastomeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('incorporating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('biologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('therein', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('timed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefrom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('coating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undercoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biostable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nonthromobogenicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elutable_material', 'JJ', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medical_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expandable_stent', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
8
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tubular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ends', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lattice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sidewall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conforms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sidewall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('preserves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lattice', 'NN', '', 'O')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬536_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('l.13-col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('l.4', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_13,_1996', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
13 14 June_13,_1996
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', '', 'O')
June 2005
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('promote', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thrombosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim_Construction_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('U.S._Dist', 'NN', '', 'O')
2005
__NEW_SENT__
('LEXIS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('10735', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*3', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('2005_WL_1322946', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1', 'NNS', '', 'O')
10735
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('medical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dictionary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('definitions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('causing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('thrombosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('coagulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('thrombolytic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('break', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissolv', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thrombus', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('thrombolytic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*BIG_TOKEN__3_n._6__BIG_TOKEN', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('2005_WL_1322946', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*BIG_TOKEN__1_n._6__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('definition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('significant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thrombogenicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('experienced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bare', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Cordis
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*BIG_TOKEN__4_n._7__BIG_TOKEN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2005_WL_1322946', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1', 'FW', '', 'O') ('n.7', 'NN', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elutable_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('largely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elutable_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*4', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('2005_WL_1322946', 'CD', '', 'O') ('*1', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('drug-eluting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expandable_stent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cordis Cypher
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('coatings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undercoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Early', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('drug-free', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sprayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('solvents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('tetrahydrofuran', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('THF', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('toluene', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('toxic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('humans', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solvents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dissolve', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('diffuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undercoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sterilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('undercoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concentration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('thinner', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undercoat', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('23', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sterilization', 'NN', '', 'O')
about 23 %
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬536_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5,545,208', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Wolff', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5,512,055', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Domb', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
8 U.S._Patent 5,545,208 U.S._Patent 5,512,055
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*985', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
8
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('renewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cordis JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cordis
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upheld', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Domb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wolff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Domb Wolff
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Domb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('esophageal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('suggest', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Domb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Domb Domb
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion_Denying_JMOL', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('434', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('320', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
320
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wolff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metallic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-layer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wolff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('decade', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('evidenced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Wolff one Wolff more than a decade
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('praise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('identifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('took', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('great', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('deal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('develop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug-eluting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cordis
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('321', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
321
__NEW_SENT__
('Regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantial_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('experts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('testified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cypher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O')
three Cypher
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('316-17', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('witness', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('drug-free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('1_to_2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('%_drug..', 'CD', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1_to_2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('%_drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('315', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
315
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pointed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('need', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sterilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('implantable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('drug-free', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('elutable_material', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬536_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contemplates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implantation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('implying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topcoat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬536_patent 23 %
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantial_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thrombosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug-eluting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Cordis Cordis FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cypher_stent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('non-thrombogenicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Cordis
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬536_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ll.23-24', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('death', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('heart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('possibly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thrombosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('speculative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('warrant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Cordis second FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_2775087', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*3', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cordis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Cordis JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
