('555_F.3d_984', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('BALL', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('AEROSOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AND', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('SPECIALTY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CONTAINER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LIMITED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('BRANDS', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bath', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Body_Works', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Henri_Bendel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bath', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Body_Works', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('White_Barn_Candle_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
BALL AEROSOL AND SPECIALTY CONTAINER Bath & Body_Works Inc. Henri_Bendel Inc. Bath & The White_Barn_Candle_Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1333', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Feb._9,_2009', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Samuel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Der-Yeghiayan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_1049581', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('514_F.Supp.2d_1051', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('553_F.Supp.2d_939', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois J. 2006_WL_1049581 514_F.Supp.2d_1051
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('phrase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('engagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('feet', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('putting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('feet', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('predictable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('variation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('minimal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('outweigh', 'VB', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('apparent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('put', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*985', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McPherson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Polster', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lieder', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Woodruff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lucchesi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('St.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('MO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
McPherson D. Moore Polster Lieder Woodruff & Lucchesi L.C. St. Louis
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Douglas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Churovich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cunningham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gregory', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('A.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Castanias', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jones_Day', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Douglas D. Churovich William B. Cunningham Jr. Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Luke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sobota', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blackman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('*986', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jones_Day', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zinna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ward', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Olivo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Luke A. Sobota Marc S. Blackman Chicago John F. Ward David M. Hill Michael J. Zinna New York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Limited_Brands', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bath', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Body_Works', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Henri_Bendel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bath', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Body_Works', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('White_Barn_Candle_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('6,457,969', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O')
Limited_Brands Inc. Bath & Body_Works Inc. Henri_Bendel Inc. Bath & Body_Works Inc. The White_Barn_Candle_Co. Limited Northern_District Illinois 6,457,969
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Ball_Aerosol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Specialty_Container', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Limited_Brands', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('553_F.Supp.2d_939', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Ball_Aerosol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Specialty_Container', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Limited_Brands', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('514_F.Supp.2d_1051', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.2007', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Ball_Aerosol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Specialty_Container', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Limited_Brands', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._05-_CV-3684', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('2006_WL_6178978_(N.D.Ill._June_28,_2006)', 'ADD', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('document', 'NN', '', 'O') ('137', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Validity_Motion', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Ball_Aerosol', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Specialty_Container', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Limited_Brands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._05-_CV-3684', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill', '.', '', 'O')
Ball_Aerosol & Limited_Brands Inc. Ball_Aerosol & Limited_Brands Inc. 514_F.Supp.2d_1051 Ball_Aerosol & Limited_Brands Inc. No._05-_CV-3684 2006_WL_6178978_(N.D.Ill._June_28,_2006) 137 Validity_Motion
__NEW_SENT__
('June_28,_2006', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('document', 'NN', '', 'O') ('139', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Infringement_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Can', 'MD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Limited_Brands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._05-_CV-3684', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_1049581', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill', '.', '', 'O')
June_28,_2006 139 U.S. Can Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('19', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Claim_Construction_Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
19 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ball_Aerosol', 'LS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Specialty_Container', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('BASC', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('employee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Jivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kumar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kholsa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Specialty_Container Inc. BASC Jivan Kumar Kholsa
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('removable_cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('table', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('scorching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('damage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Putting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('minimizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scorching', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('feet', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('rest', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*987.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬969_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fig.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('B', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('designed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Travel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Candle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('square-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('removable_cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O')
2003 Limited Candle four
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('BASC', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Eastern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
October 25 2004 Limited United_States_District_Court the Eastern District Michigan
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_31,_2005', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Northern_District Illinois May_31,_2005
__NEW_SENT__
('BASC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('969', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
969 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin_comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hollow', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('closed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wick', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('burn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wick', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('over', 'RP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('removably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('burning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('damage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cup', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface_open_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('down', 'RP', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('therefrom', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('resting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('seat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('M5', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin_comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cup', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wick', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('burn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wick', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cup', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('over', 'RP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('removably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lit', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*988', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('burning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('damage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface_open_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('down', 'RP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('therefrom', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('resting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('seat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'969_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.5', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ll.35-56', '.', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('id', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.6', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.10-30', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_19,_2006', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rest', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim_Construction_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_1049581', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*2', 'FW', '', 'O')
2006_WL_1049581
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disagreed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protrusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('lock', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'RP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feet', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fitting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('recesses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('engagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_28,_2006', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inherently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('6,398,544', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Wright', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
June_28,_2006 Limited 6,398,544 Wright
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O')
Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('p', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('atent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('encompassed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wright', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,285,694', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Marchi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Limited ¡¬969 Wright 3,285,694
__NEW_SENT__
('Infringement_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._05-_CV-3684', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument-that', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('self-evident', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('solve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scorching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder-as', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('11-12', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('supplied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('p', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('atent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conclusory_statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lieu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explanation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Limited ¡¬969
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
12
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('BASC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_tin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('need', 'MD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('candle_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('positions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
17
__NEW_SENT__
('Two', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('later', 'RB', 'DATE', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_30,_2006', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sua', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sponte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Infringement_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Two days later Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('Validity_Motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._05-_CV-3684', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_6178978', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_trier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Plaintiff
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('leave', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('supplemental', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 16 2006 Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('briefing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_22,_2007', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('briefing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('impact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Supreme', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teleflex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('550_U.S._398', 'CD', '', 'O') ('127_S.Ct._1727', 'CD', '', 'O') ('167_L.Ed.2d_705_(2007)', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*989', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('reaffirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
June_22,_2007 the Supreme Court 's KSR International Co. Teleflex Inc. 167_L.Ed.2d_705_(2007) Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('docket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('quoted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('explicit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
KSR
__NEW_SENT__
('Ball_Aerosol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Specialty_Container', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Limited_Brands', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._2', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':05-CV-3684', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1-2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill', '.', '', 'O')
Ball_Aerosol & Specialty_Container Inc. Limited_Brands Inc. 1-2
__NEW_SENT__
('June_22,_2007', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('document', 'NN', '', 'O') ('191', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Analysis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('quoting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('127', 'CD', '', 'O') ('S.Ct.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1741', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
June_22,_2007 191 KSR 1741
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Infringement_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('conclusory_statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reaffirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_trier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Limited Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('BASC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬969_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
September 4 2007 Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('BASC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('royalty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_27,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('entirety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('previous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Limited KSR
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Seagate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Techology', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('497_F.3d_1360_(Fed.Cir.2007)', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_23,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('grants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_validity', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
