('394_F.3d_1348', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('BRUNO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INDEPENDENT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LIVING', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AIDS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACORN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MOBILITY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SERVICES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LTD.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Acorn_Stairlifts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O')
BRUNO INDEPENDENT LIVING AIDS INC. ACORN Acorn_Stairlifts Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._04-1114', 'NN', '', 'O') ('04-1125', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Jan._11,_2005', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Defendant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('prevailed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('false', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('advertising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Barbara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crabb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('277_F.Supp.2d_965', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Wisconsin Barbara B. Crabb J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('warranted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('extraordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1349', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McIntyre', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whyte', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hirschboeck', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dudek', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jeffrey A. McIntyre S.C. Madison Wisconsin
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pyper', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cynthia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Buchko', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas M. Pyper Cynthia L. Buchko
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sylke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sylke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Law', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Offices', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O')
C. Thomas Sylke Sylke Law Offices LLC Milwaukee
__NEW_SENT__
('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Florey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richardson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Michael E. Florey Fish & Richardson P.C. P.A. Minneapolis Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1350', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hanson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Woodford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dragseth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Deanna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reichel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Chad A. Hanson William R. Woodford John A. Dragseth Deanna J. Reichel
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE GAJARSA LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('DECISION', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bruno_Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Living_Aids', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mobility', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Services', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Acorn_Stairlifts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('285', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('exceptional_case', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('predicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('engaged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecuting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5,230,405', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Living_Aids Inc. Bruno Acorn Mobility Services Ltd. Acorn_Stairlifts Inc. Acorn 35 285 Bruno 5,230,405
__NEW_SENT__
('Bruno_Indep', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Living_Aids', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mobility', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Servs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('277_F.Supp.2d_965', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis.2003', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Living_Aids Inc. Acorn Mobility Servs. Ltd. W.D.Wis.2003
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disturb', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exceptional_case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('conditionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Acorn
__NEW_SENT__
('Bruno_Indep', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Living_Aids', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mobility', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Servs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._02-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C-0391-C', 'XX', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis', 'NN', '', 'O')
Living_Aids Inc. Acorn Mobility Servs. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('June_9,_2003', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
June_9,_2003
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bruno', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('manufactures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('stairlifts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('persons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mobility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('impairments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ascend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('descend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stairways', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('travels', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rail', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bruno
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United_States_Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stairlift', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'405_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
November 1991 Bruno the United_States_Patent and Trademark Office July 1993
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'405_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
July 2002 Bruno Acorn 5 9 10 and 15
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('produced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disclosures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('stairlifts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Acorn
__NEW_SENT__
('Admitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('immaterial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Acorn Bruno
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('course', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment,1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Acorn 5 10 and 15
__NEW_SENT__
('Bruno_Indep', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Living_Aids', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mobility', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Servs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('286_F.Supp.2d_1020_(W.D.Wis.2003)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Living_Aids Inc. Acorn Mobility Servs. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequently', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('accused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('intentionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('withheld', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('asked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('declare', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('exceptional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('285.2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('additional_discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('justify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fee_award', 'NN', '', 'O')
Acorn Bruno 285.2 Acorn
__NEW_SENT__
('Upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('briefing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exceptional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecuting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'405_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('additional_discovery', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bruno Acorn
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('stairlifts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stairlift', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'405_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Bruno Bruno the Food and Drug Administration FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Observing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('occurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('concurrently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'405_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court-noting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('credible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('faith', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explanation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('*1351', 'UH', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO-inferred', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('withheld', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deceptive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O')
FDA Bruno
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thereupon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('deemed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exceptional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('imposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fee_award', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('285', 'CD', '', 'O')
Bruno
__NEW_SENT__
('Final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('399,459.32', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
November 2003 Bruno 399,459.32
__NEW_SENT__
('Bruno_Indep', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Living_Aids', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mobility', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Servs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._02-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C-0391-C', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('2003_WL_23095743_(W.D.Wis._Nov._6,_2003)', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Living_Aids Inc. Acorn Mobility Servs. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bruno', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('challenges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exceptional_case', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bruno
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Acorn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('conditionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('additional_discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Acorn
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
