('229_F.3d_1120', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('BROWN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('WILLIAMSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TOBACCO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PHILIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MORRIS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INCORPORATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
BROWN & WILLIAMSON PHILIP MORRIS INCORPORATED
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._99-1389', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('99-1403', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Oct._17,_2000', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nov._15,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kentucky', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Simpson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged_public_use', 'NN', '', 'O')
Charles R. Simpson III
__NEW_SENT__
('Manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cross-appealed', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1122', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morgan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Stephen R. Smith Morgan & Finnegan L.L.P. New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Diaz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paulson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Marcus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Andrea', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wayda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John A. Robert E. Paulson Harry C. Marcus Andrea L. Wayda
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schildkraut', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gould', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Marc G. Schildkraut James W. Gould
__NEW_SENT__
('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grossi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Porter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-cross-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Peter T. Grossi Jr. Arnold & Porter Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daneker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Phillips', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosenthal', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Michael D. Daneker Amy K. Phillips
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Karen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stoll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farabow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Donald R. Dunner Karen F. Stoll Finnegan Henderson Farabow Garrett & Dunner Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grubbs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Woodward', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hobson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fulton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Louisville', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Kentucky', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
William D. Grubbs Hobson & Fulton Louisville Kentucky
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
CLEVENGER BRYSON LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Brown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Williamson_Tobacco_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Philip_Morris_Inc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PM', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seek', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('April_1,_1999', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kentucky', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Brown & Williamson_Tobacco_Corp. B & W '' Philip_Morris_Inc. April_1,_1999 United_States_District_Court Kentucky
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Williamson_Tobacco_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Philip_Morris_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('No._3', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (':89CV-0470-S', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Ky', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
See Brown & Williamson_Tobacco_Corp. Philip_Morris_Inc. No._3 :89CV-0470-S W.D.Ky
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr._1,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Williamson_Tobacco_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Philip_Morris_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('No._3', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (':89CV-0470-S', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Ky', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Brown & Williamson_Tobacco_Corp. Philip_Morris_Inc. No._3 :89CV-0470-S W.D.Ky
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr._1,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('W', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Reissue', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2,615', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'615_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed2', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Slims', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('SuperSlims', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('VSSS', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PM', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'TIME', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', 'TIME', 'I') ('PM', 'NNP', 'TIME', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'TIME', 'I') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('up', 'IN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receipt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged_public_use', 'NN', '', 'O')
B & W 1 4 and 11 U.S. 1 1 4 and 11 the Virginia Slims SuperSlims VSSS 2 ) PM 's March May of 1989 3 1 4 and 11
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1 4 11 1 4 and 11
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moots', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('*1123', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willfulness', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Luke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('employee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('British', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('American', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tobacco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('BAT', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('worked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cigarettes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John Luke Luke_patent British American Tobacco Co. Ltd. BAT
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980s', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Luke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('tobacco', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('expenses', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the early 1980s Luke
__NEW_SENT__
('His', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cigarettes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('burned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('efficiently', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Luke', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prototypes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cigarettes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('management', 'NN', '', 'O')
Luke
__NEW_SENT__
('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subsidiary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BAT', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('aware', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Luke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cigarettes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
B & W BAT Luke the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Luke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4637,410', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'410_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
B & W Luke U.S. Patent No._4637,410 January 20 1987
__NEW_SENT__
('Shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lephardt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Lephardt B & W the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reissued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_1,_1988', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
March_1,_1988
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('foreign', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_24,_1985', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_22,_1985', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Luke_patent May_24,_1985 U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('fifteen', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O')
fifteen 1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 4 11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('10-19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mm', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('traditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cigarettes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('circumferences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('23-27', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mm', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I')
23-27 mm
__NEW_SENT__
('Around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'410_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mm', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('marketed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Capri', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
B & W 17 mm Capri
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mm', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Capri', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
17 mm 1 4 and 11 Capri
__NEW_SENT__
('Shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'410_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Capri', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compete', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Capri', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
B & W Capri Capri
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('took', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('two', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('place', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('competing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cigarette', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('VSSS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O')
more than two years VSSS
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_30,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('W', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O')
B & W
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged_public_use', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Luke_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1 1994
__NEW_SENT__
