('445_F.3d_1374', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('BRUCKELMYER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GROUND', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HEATERS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Mark BRUCKELMYER GROUND HEATERS
__NEW_SENT__
('T.H.E', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Machine_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._05-1412', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_20,_2006', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
April_20,_2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Donovan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2005_WL_1155938', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Donovan W. Frank J. 2005_WL_1155938 two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Canadian_patent_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('publicly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accessible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('establishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('conditions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge Canadian_patent_application two
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Linn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1375', 'UH', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lunseth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Briggs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Morgan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
John B. Lunseth II Briggs Morgan P.A. Minneapolis Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Streater', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael H. Streater
__NEW_SENT__
('Aaron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patterson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thuente', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Skaar', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Christensen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Aaron W. Davis Patterson Thuente Skaar & Christensen P.A. Minneapolis
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Randall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Skaar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chadwick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Randall T. Skaar Eric H. Chadwick
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Moskal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Warner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Norcross', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judd', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Grand', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Rapids', 'NNPS', 'GPE', 'I') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O')
James Moskal Warner Norcross & Judd LLP Grand Rapids Michigan
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Burpee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Charles E. Burpee
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MICHEL LOURIE
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Mark_Bruckelmyer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
United_States_District_Court the District of Minnesota U.S
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('5,567', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('085_and_5820,301', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('T.H.E', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
5,567 085_and_5820,301 Ground_Heaters Inc. T.H.E
__NEW_SENT__
('Machine_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bruckelmyer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._02-_CV-1761', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2005_WL_1155938', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Minn', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('May_13,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Final_Decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bruckelmyer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Canadian_patent_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Canadian_Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1,158,119', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Bruckelmyer Canadian_patent_application 1,158,119 35 102
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('slip', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('therein', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
3_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_20,_1995', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'085_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('naming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Mark_Bruckelmyer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O')
July_20,_1995 the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office Mark_Bruckelmyer
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_17,_1996', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1376', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('naming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Bruckelmyer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bruckelmyer
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thawing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frozen_ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('laid', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'085_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._34-51', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._34-51', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cold', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weather', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('laying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('harden', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-uniform', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'NN', '', 'O') ('laid', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('frozen_ground', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('crack', 'VB', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('settling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('thaws', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('warmer', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('weather', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'085_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._10-26', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._10-26', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('place', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('rubber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hoses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('narrow', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('footing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'085_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._2,_l._25-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._3,_l._58', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_l._25-', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._4,_l._15', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('heated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('antifreeze', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('circulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hoses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('thaws', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frozen_ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prevents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hardening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_7,_1982', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thirteen', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bruckelmyer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'085", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('Norman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Young', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Canadian_Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1,158,119', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
May_7,_1982 thirteen years Bruckelmyer Norman Young 1,158,119
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
December 6 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heating_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('flexible_hoses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('close', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proximity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shapes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('configurations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('heat', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('abstract', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('preheated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flexible_hoses', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('object', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fresh', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pre-constructed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formwork', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extreme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cold', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weather', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('illustrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('drawings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('heating_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('heat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beam', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('notes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subjects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('necessarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('confined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('placement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('typical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('uses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') (':..', 'CD', '', 'O') ('thawing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frozen_ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('p.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('Relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('omits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drawings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('viz.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('drawings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('illustrating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('heating_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thaw', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frozen_ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('figures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('3_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
two 3_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('Figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cancelled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O')
3_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('Nonetheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('remain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('file_wrapper', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('forward', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_15,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bruckelmyer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('responsive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pleading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid.1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('19', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('figures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('3_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 19 2002 3_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('enabled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('undue', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O')
3_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('Bruckelmyer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ground_Heaters', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._02-_CV-1761', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2003_WL_21402870_(D._Minn._June_16,_2003)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Initial', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Decision', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
8 2003_WL_21402870_(D._Minn._June_16,_2003) `` Initial Decision ``
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deny', 'VB', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('*1377', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
102
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inspection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Canadian_Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hull', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Quebec', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Canadian_Patent Office Hull Quebec more than one year
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('albeit', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('file_wrapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accessible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('interested', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('constitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
102
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('figures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('3_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'119", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bruckelmyer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
3_and_4 102 Bruckelmyer
__NEW_SENT__
('Final_Decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Bruckelmyer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('removed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pertinent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bruckelmyer
__NEW_SENT__
('Ground_Heaters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('renewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_13,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bruckelmyer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')2', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
