('910_F.2d_804', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('CONSOLIDATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ALUMINUM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff/Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FOSECO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LIMITED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Foseco_Incorporated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Alumax_Incorporated', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trialco_Incorporated', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendants/Cross-Appellants', '.', '', 'O')
CONSOLIDATED Trialco_Incorporated
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._89-1637', 'RB', '', 'O') ('89-1643', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_19,_1990', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ceramic_foam_filters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molten_metal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('counter-claimed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('violation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sherman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I')
Sherman Act
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Will', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('716_F.Supp._316', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois Will J. 716_F.Supp._316
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Markey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('practicing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fictitious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inoperable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('warranted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unclean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hands', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('procuring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exceptional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('warranting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Markey Circuit_Judge 1 2 one 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*805', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ross', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Van', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Santen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steadman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Simpson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff/appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomas I. Ross Hill Van Santen Steadman & Simpson Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lewis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steadman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Metzger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Lewis T. Steadman Robert M. Barrett David R. Metzger
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bachman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bachman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LaPointe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Haven', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Conn.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taylor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ice', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Donadio', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ryan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Indianapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ind.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants/cross-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert H. Bachman Bachman & LaPointe New Conn. Jay G. Taylor Ice Miller Indianapolis Ind.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants/cross-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grear', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Manich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Victor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Copeland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Britton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Haight', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hofeldt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MARKEY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('*BENNETT', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SHARP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Joseph A. Grear Stephen J. Manich Victor G. Copeland Britton A. Davis Haight & Hofeldt Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('**', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*806', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MARKEY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Aluminum', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Illinois', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Will', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.J', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Consolidated Aluminum Corporation Consolidated United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of
__NEW_SENT__
('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Foseco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FIL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Foseco_Incorporated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Alumax_Incorporated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Alumax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trialco_Incorporated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Trialco', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Foseco International Limited FIL Alumax
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('presume', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('familiarity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Memorandum_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('716_F.Supp._316', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('11_USPQ2d_1817_(N.D.Ill.1989)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', 'ORG', 'I') ('Report', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Recommendation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master,1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10_USPQ2d_1143_(N.D.Ill.1988)', 'CD', '', 'O')
716_F.Supp._316 the `` Report and Recommendation ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Hence', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('underlie', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dispositive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_4,_1982', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Alumax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trialco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('FIL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('violations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Nos._3893,917', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'917", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('3,962,081', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'081", 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('4,024,056', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'056", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('4,081,371', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'371", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('4,024,212', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'212", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,075,303', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'303", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ceramic_foam_filters', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molten_metal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aluminum', 'NN', '', 'O')
May_4,_1982 Consolidated four Foseco Alumax Trialco FIL six United States Nos._3893,917 3,962,081 4,024,056 4,081,371 4,024,212 4,075,303
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('violations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ceramic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filter', 'NN', '', 'O')
Foseco
__NEW_SENT__
('Foseco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('joint', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('induced_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Alumax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trialco', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('direct_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('FIL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encouraging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('commercialize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('teaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contributory_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Alumax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trialco', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('direct_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('FIL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('induced_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encouraging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('commercialize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('teaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contributory_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'056", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'371_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Alumax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trialco', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('direct_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'056", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'371_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('FIL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('induced_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'212", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'303_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encouraging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('commercialize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('helping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('teaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIVEX.2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('antitrust_violations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Foseco Alumax Trialco FIL Foseco Foseco SIVEX Foseco Alumax Trialco FIL Foseco Foseco SIVEX Foseco Alumax Trialco FIL Foseco Foseco
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('31', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six-week', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('2000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('exhibits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('27', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('70', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('94', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('page', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('report', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recommendation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-BIG_TOKEN__2_and_4__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('-9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'056_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'371_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('24', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'212_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'303_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('intentional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('withholding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fictitious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inoperative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'212_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'303_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('FIL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Trialco', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alumax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('6', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('*807', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_violations', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('7', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('further_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('permanently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('change', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'081_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('256', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('9', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Yarwood', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Preuss', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'363_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
October 31 1988 more than 2000 27 70 94 1 1-BIG_TOKEN__2_and_4__BIG_TOKEN 2 7 8 10 and 14 15 20 and 24 3 7 15 and 20 35 102 103 2 35 3 Consolidated 4 1 4 5 and 9 1 2 and 18 1 Foseco FIL 5 1 4 5 and 9 Trialco Alumax 6 Consolidated 8 Consolidated 35 9 Yarwood and Preuss
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('objections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('report', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recommendation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('53', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', ':', '', 'O')
Rule 53 2
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_15,_1989', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('46', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('page', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Memorandum_Opinion', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('affirming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917", 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'371", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'056_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concealing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('best', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fictitious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
June_15,_1989 46 Memorandum_Opinion 1 2 3 Consolidated
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'917_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('intentional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081", 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'212", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'303_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pattern', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('6', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'081", 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'212", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'303_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('7', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
4 Consolidated 5 Consolidated 6 7 8
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_21,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_6,_1989', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Foseco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
July_6,_1989 Foseco
__NEW_SENT__
