('363_F.3d_1247', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('CHIRON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GENENTECH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
GENENTECH
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._03-1158', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('03-1159', 'CD', '', 'O')
Nos._03-1158
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('March_30,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_8,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('binding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('breast_cancer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shubb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California William B. Shubb J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('concurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('268_F.Supp.2d_1148', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1249', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Harold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McElhinny', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morrison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Foerster', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Harold J. McElhinny Morrison & Foerster LLP San_Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Rachel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Krevans', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Walters', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crotty', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Rachel Krevans Eric S. Walters Jason A. Crotty
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nancy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Koch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blackburn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Harry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Guth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Emeryville', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Nancy J. Koch Robert P. Blackburn Joseph Harry Guth Chiron Corporation Emeryville
__NEW_SENT__
('Leora', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ben-Ami', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Clifford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chance', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Leora Ben-Ami Clifford Chance New York
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Roy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hofer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cynthia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Homan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Meredith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Addy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Noel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kaman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brinks', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hofer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lione', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Roy E. Hofer Cynthia A. Homan Meredith Martin Addy C. Noel Kaman Brinks Hofer Gilson & Lione Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Daralyn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Durie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Keker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Van', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nest', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
John W. Keker Daralyn J. Durie Keker & Van Nest San_Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6054,561', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1250', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
United_States_District_Court California Genentech U.S. 35 102 1984 1985 and 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Chiron_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
Genentech Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('S-00-1252', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('WBS_GGH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Sept.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Oct._23,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
S-00-1252 Sept. 9
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adequately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('or', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Chiron ¡¬561_patent 1984 1985 or 1986 JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬561_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('states:1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('binds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('human_c-erbB-2_antigen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
19
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('modern', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('understanding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('homogeneous_antibody_population', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immune_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('recognizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('binding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_antigen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Y-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('protein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('amino', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chains', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('heavy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O')
four two two
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('simplified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant_region', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ends', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Y', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('binds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('interacts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target_antigen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complementary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CDR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recognizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('binds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('binding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('site', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O')
CDR
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Y', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('interacts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immune_system', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target_antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('binding', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('epitopes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CDRs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('binds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('epitope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O')
one more than one
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('561', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('human_c-erbB-2_antigen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-an', ',', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breast_cancer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O')
19 ¡¬ 561
__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('One', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hybridoma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cloned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('produces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O')
One
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hybridoma_method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('species', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mice', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('hamsters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rats', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humans', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Murine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('antibodies-derived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mouse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cells-are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Murine
__NEW_SENT__
('Another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('genetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('engineering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('recombinant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Monoclonal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('combines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('encoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('species', 'NNS', '', 'O')
more than one
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('derive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mouse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('predominantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'NN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('nonhuman_portions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('completely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('human_constant_region', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('But', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonhuman', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1251', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('synthetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('often', 'RB', '', 'O') ('come', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CDRs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('event', 'NN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('crucial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('recognize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_antigen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('play', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('role', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technologies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diagnostics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('short-term', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('therapies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('administered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('people', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('long-term', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deleterious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('immunogenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Human', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Anti-Mouse', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Antibody', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HAMA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('occurs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('immune_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recognizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('murine_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('foreign', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O')
Human Anti-Mouse Antibody
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('HAMA_response', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('toxic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('death', 'NN', '', 'O')
HAMA_response
__NEW_SENT__
('Chimeric', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('HAMA_response', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('minimizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonhuman_portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('administered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Chimeric HAMA_response
__NEW_SENT__
('Furthermore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('benefit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('activating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('immune', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('responses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cellular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cytoxicity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980s', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('scientists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('predecessor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Cetus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('investigating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('target', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('breast_cancer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antigens', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
the early 1980s Chiron Cetus Corp. Chiron
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('facilitates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('diagnosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breast_cancer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('investigational', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
first February 8 1984
__NEW_SENT__
('Within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
a year January 11 1985 continuation-in-part CIP 1984
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_21,_1986', 'NNP', '', 'O')
CIP
__NEW_SENT__
('Eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('561', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_7,_1995', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
¡¬ 561 CIP June_7,_1995
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('focuses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬561_patent 1984 1985 and 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('454C11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('binds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O')
1984 454C11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('454C11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('murine_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hybridoma_method', 'NN', '', 'O')
454C11
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deposit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hybridoma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibody_technology', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appear', 'VB', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('months', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('surprising', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
four months 1984
__NEW_SENT__
('Similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appeared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
May 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mention', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1984
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1985 six
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deposit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hybridoma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('520C9', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approximate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('210', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('kilodaltons,2', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('describe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('identity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O')
210
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('note', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bind', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('epitope', 'NN', '', 'O')
six seven
__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chimeric_antibody_technology', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('adds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('herein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('homogeneous_antibody_population', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regards', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1252', 'FW', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deposit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hybridomas', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1986 six three
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thirteen', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('deposits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('hybridomas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('454CBIG_TOKEN__11_and_520__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('C9', 'NN', '', 'O')
thirteen five
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('epitopes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O')
at least three
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('200', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('kilodaltons', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I')
approximately 200 kilodaltons
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('quotes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('monoclonal_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regards', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1986
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Herceptin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('THE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('long-term', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breast_cancer', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬561_patent Chiron Genentech Herceptin THE_R
__NEW_SENT__
('Herceptin', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('binds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('antigen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('growth', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cancerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Herceptin
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Herceptin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibody', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('minimizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('HAMA_response', 'XX', 'NORP', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Herceptin HAMA_response
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('broadly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('embrace', 'VB', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('murine_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HER2', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Chiron_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('266_F.Supp.2d_1172_(E.D.Cal.2002)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Genentech Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Chiron
__NEW_SENT__
('Chiron_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
Genentech Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('S-00-1252', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('WBS_GGH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2002', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dist', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
S-00-1252 U.S. Dist
__NEW_SENT__
('LEXIS', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('19126', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2002_WL_32123930_(E.D.Cal._June_24,_2002)', 'CD', '', 'O')
LEXIS
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬561_patent ¡± 102 1984 1985 and 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thirteen-day', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjudicated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('satisfy', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O')
35 first
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980s', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('adequately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('humanized_antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬561_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
the 1980s 1995
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('proved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('satisfy', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('561', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Genentech ¡¬ 561
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('specify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('left', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unfulfilled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡± 112
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Chiron JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Chiron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('post-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('conditionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Chiron Genentech
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('styled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('treats', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('affirming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enlarge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lessen', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('adversary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bailey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Container', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mich.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('292_F.3d_1360', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1362', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Bailey Dart Container Corp. Mich. 1362
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O')
28
__NEW_SENT__
