('216_F.3d_1367', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('CANTON', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('BIO-MEDICAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('INTEGRATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LINER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TECHNOLOGIES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
CANTON INTEGRATED LINER
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1568', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_30,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('binding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('uncured', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('elastomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('silicone_rubber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polyolefins', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Frederick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scullin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('19_F.Supp.2d_22', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of New_York Frederick J. Scullin Jr. J. 19_F.Supp.2d_22
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1368', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Filardi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chase', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
*1368 Edward V. Filardi White & Chase of New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Scheibeler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John Scheibeler
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Muldoon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hancock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Estabrook', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Syracuse', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
James R. Muldoon Hancock & Estabrook LLP Syracuse
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('FRIEDMAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Canton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bio-Medical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Canton', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York,1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Integrated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Liner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technologies', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Canton', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._4499,148', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Canton Bio-Medical Inc. Canton Integrated Liner Technologies Inc. ILT Canton United States
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Patented', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Invention', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Canton', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('septa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('closures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liquid-containing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vessels', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ILT Canton
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('septa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('perforation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('self-sealing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('needle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('withdrawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vessels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('significant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('septa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Canton', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laminations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastomer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('silicone_rubber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin', 'NN', '', 'O')
ILT Canton one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1369', 'FW', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('148', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inert', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bond', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('laminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('septa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬ 148
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬148_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four-step', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corona_discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('primed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('primer_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bonded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uncured', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elastomer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('laminate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('firm', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bond', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bridge', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastomer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chemically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('bonding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('elastomeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('chemically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('polyolefins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('exposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inert', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('polyolefin_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corona_discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corona_discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primer_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ethyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('silicate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ethyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('orthosilicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tetra', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('butyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('titanate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('organic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('placing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('primed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polyolefin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uncured', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elastomeric_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molecular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('61,000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elongation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('modulus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fifty', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('percent', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastomeric_compound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('elastomeric_compound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('firmly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('curing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastomeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('firmly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('securely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('bonded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('thereto', 'RB', '', 'O')
61,000 fifty percent
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyolefin_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corona_discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('primed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('laminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastomer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O')
ILT
__NEW_SENT__
('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('differ', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ways', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ILT two
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('contends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('primer_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
First ILT
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('ILT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bonded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('elastomeric_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('uncured', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Second ILT
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemicals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('primer_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Canton', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ILT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Canton ILT 1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
