('890_F.3d_1042', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('D', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('THREE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ENTERPRISES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SUNMODO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('D_Three', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('Enterprises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rillito_River_Solar_LLC', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('dba', 'XX', '', 'O') ('EcoFasten_Solar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
Rillito_River_Solar_LLC
__NEW_SENT__
('2017-1909', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'RB', '', 'O') ('2017-1910', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('May_21,_2018', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('roof', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mount_sealing_assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mount', 'VB', '', 'O') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('seal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cross-motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':15-cv-01148-CBS', ':', '', 'O') ('1:15-cv-01151-CBS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shaffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2017_WL_1023389', 'CD', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Magistrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Craig B. Shaffer United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wallach', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Wallach Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prejudice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Posture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Summary', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judgment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Motion for Summary Judgment
__NEW_SENT__
('*1044', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') (':15-cv-01148-CBS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:15-cv-01151-CBS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Magistrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shaffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Colorado Nos._1 Craig B. Shaffer
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Friedman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Suder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cooke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fort', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Worth', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dave R. Gunter Friedman Suder & Cooke
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cooke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Corby', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Vowell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael Thomas Cooke Robert Vowell
__NEW_SENT__
('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Klarquist', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sparkman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Portland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('OR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Scott E. Davis Klarquist Sparkman
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sarah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Elisabeth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jelsema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Siegel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Sarah Elisabeth Jelsema Todd M. Siegel
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wallach', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Reyna Clevenger
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Wallach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Enterprises', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'ADD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SunModo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('SunModo', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rillito_River_Solar_LLC', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('EcoFasten_Solar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('EcoFasten', 'VBN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._8689,517', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'517_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('9,068,339', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'339_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('8,707,655', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'655_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Patents-in-Suit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Appellees SunModo Corporation SunModo Rillito_River_Solar_LLC EcoFasten U.S. the District of Colorado District_Court U.S. 9,068,339 8,707,655
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inter_alia', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('joint', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('various_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._61', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('/150,301', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
U.S. Patent Application No._61 District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Enters.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rillito_River_Solar_LLC', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('5-cv-01148-CBS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('15-cv-01151-CBS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2017_WL_1023389', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*14', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('Colo.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mar._15,_2017', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Rillito_River_Solar_LLC D.
__NEW_SENT__
('31-34', 'LS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Final', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judgments', 'NNPS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('2212-48', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Application', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') (')1', '.', '', 'O')
2212-48 2009 Application
__NEW_SENT__
('*1045', 'UH', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'CD', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1 2012
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Patents-in-Suit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('roof', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mount_sealing_assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mount', 'VB', '', 'O') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('seal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('location..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Patents-in-Suit
__NEW_SENT__
("'517_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'655_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'339_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'517_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inter_alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('roof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('standoff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('object', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roof', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bracket', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('threaded', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('element', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
2 second
__NEW_SENT__
("'517_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('10_ll._27', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-29', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('33', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('43', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('45', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
10_ll._27 33 43 45 1
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('SunModo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('EcoFasten', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2009,3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2017_WL_1023389', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*13', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('n.16', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Patents-in-Suit', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2014_and_2015', 'CD', '', 'O')
SunModo 2010 EcoFasten June the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office Patents-in-Suit
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('successfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Patents-in-Suit', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Patents-in-Suit D_Three February 5 2009
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*3', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*13', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2212', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
2212
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Asserted_Claims', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('2009', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('broader', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'FAC', 'B') ('Application', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')4', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2017_WL_1023389', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*5', 'FW', '', 'O') ('*9-10', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*12', 'NFP', '', 'O')
District_Court Asserted_Claims the 2009 Application 2009 Application 35 2012
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('divided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Asserted_Claims', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('washer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('asked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('roof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('soft_washer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bracket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('soft_washer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
District_Court Asserted_Claims two
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*7', 'NN', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('2009', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('washerless_assembly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('requir', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('W', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-', 'HYPH', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pronged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bracket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1700', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Asserted_Claims', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('broader', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('configurations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('washerless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
District_Court the 2009 Application 's 1700 Asserted_Claims
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*10', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
J.A
__NEW_SENT__
('*1046', 'FW', '', 'O') ('2225', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('discussing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('washerless_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Application', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', 'EVENT', 'I') ('2246', 'CD', 'EVENT', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('41', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2225 2009 Application ) 2246 41
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('washers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('washers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('situated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Asserted_Claims', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('covered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('washers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashing', 'NN', '', 'O')
District_Court 2009 Asserted_Claims
__NEW_SENT__
('D_Three', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('2017_WL_1023389', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*11', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('*12', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('D_Three', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benefit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pplication', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date..', 'XX', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('P', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('atents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-', ',', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('-S', 'NFP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('uit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('SunModo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('EcoFasten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('QuikFoot', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Roof', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mount', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
2009 SunModo EcoFasten QuikFoot Roof Mount System
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*13', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('invalidated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('but', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Asserted_Claims', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('D_Three', 'ADD', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'655_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purportedly-withdrawn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('EcoFasten', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Tile', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Flashing', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('System', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('post-dated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('2009', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
District_Court one Asserted_Claims D_Three 6 EcoFasten Tile Flashing System the 2009 Application
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
(';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2772-811', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2813-44.5', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
