('464_F.3d_1356', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('DYSTAR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('TEXTILFARBEN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('GMBH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DEUTSCHLAND', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('KG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('C.H', 'NNP', '', 'O')
DYSTAR TEXTILFARBEN GMBH & CO DEUTSCHLAND
__NEW_SENT__
('PATRICK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Quimica', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTDA', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PATRICK CO. Bann Quimica
__NEW_SENT__
('No._06-1088', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Oct._3,_2006', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Oct._3,_2006
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dec._4,_2006', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chemical_manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('induced_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('textile_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('catalytically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hydrogenated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('South_Carolina', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Catoe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('United', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('States', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Magistrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of South_Carolina William M. Catoe Jr. JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Michel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Schall', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
Schall Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1357', 'UH', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Enos', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Oblon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Spivak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McClelland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Maier', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alexandria', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
William T. Enos Oblon P.C. Alexandria
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kelly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Beverina', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard D. Kelly Andrew K. Beverina
__NEW_SENT__
('Neil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nelson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mullins', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Riley', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scarborough', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Greenville', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Neil C. Jones Greenville SC
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
SCHALL Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MICHEL', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DyStar_Textilfarben_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Deutschland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('KG', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DyStar', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('C.H', 'NNP', '', 'O')
DyStar_Textilfarben_GmbH & Deutschland KG DyStar
__NEW_SENT__
('Patrick_Co.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bann_Quimica_Ltda', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Bann', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('South_Carolina', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('induced_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5586,992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('992', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')1', 'XX', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('textile_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('catalytically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hydrogenated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of South_Carolina U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('DyStar', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bann_Quimica_Ltda', 'NNS', '', 'O')
DyStar
__NEW_SENT__
('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical_manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1358', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('prereduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('C.H', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patrick_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('purchased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prereduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('indigo_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bann_Quimica_Ltda', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dye', 'VB', '', 'O') ('yarn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O')
2002
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('DyStar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
DyStar the United States Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Bann', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Quimica', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('C.H', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('assessed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('90,000', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬992_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Patrick 1-4 90,000
__NEW_SENT__
('DyStar_Textilfarben_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co_Deutschland_KG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('C.H', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
DyStar_Textilfarben_GmbH & Co_Deutschland_KG v. C.H
__NEW_SENT__
('Patrick_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._6', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (':02-2946-WMC', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.S.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
No._6
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept._16,_2005', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Sept._16,_2005
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('briefing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alternatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬992_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bann JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('DyStar_Textilfarben_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co_Deutschland_KG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('C.H', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
DyStar_Textilfarben_GmbH & Co_Deutschland_KG v. C.H
__NEW_SENT__
('Patrick_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._6', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (':02-2946-WMC', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.S.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
No._6
__NEW_SENT__
('Nov._1,_2005', 'UH', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('His', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('diligently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concludes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('great', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('request', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DyStar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bann JMOL DyStar
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Bann JMOL 1-4
__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Indigo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('textile_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thousands', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
I. Indigo thousands of years
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pigment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('insoluble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('de-oxidized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water-soluble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('white', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Leuco', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('indigo', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unstable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('oxidizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('returns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('blue_pigment_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('exposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O')
Leuco
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('needs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('kept', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxygen-free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stabilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('dyehouses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('commonly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-house', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrosulfite_reduction', 'NN', '', 'O')
many years
__NEW_SENT__
('Dyers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('stock_vat', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sodium_hydrosulfite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('solubilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkali', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hydroxide', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prepared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('textile_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('dyed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('dipping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('skying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('dipping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('textile_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('contacted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('skying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('textile_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('causing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('blue_pigment_form', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('catalytic_hydrogenation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Andre', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Brochet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1917', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
second Andre Brochet 1917
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._1247,927', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Brochet', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
U.S. Brochet
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('superficial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrosulfite_reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('catalytic_hydrogenation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('gaseous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1359', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sodium_hydrosulfite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Catalytic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hydrogenation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('economical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concentrated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solutions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('leuco', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('derivatives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('impurities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mineral', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('left', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('settle', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('naturally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('separates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nickel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catalytic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('drawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('ready', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Brochet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ll.88-90', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('109-110', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Brochet 109-110
__NEW_SENT__
('Most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyehouses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brochet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stabilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('usually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('powder', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('paste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('coated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molasses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('glue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('protect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('premature', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('oxidation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Brochet
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('shift', 'VB', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyehouses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chemical_manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prereduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyehouses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1900s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
the early 1900s
__NEW_SENT__
('Rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stock_vat', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('dyers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dissolve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prereduced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preparation_tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('add', 'VB', '', 'O') ('caustic_soda', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hydroxide', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sodium_hydrosulfite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('remove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preparation_tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('significantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prepare', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyehouses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('expenditures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sodium_hydrosulfite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('caustic_soda', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('level', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pollution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyehouse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('waste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyehouse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('floors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('textile_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('catalytically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hydrogenated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('traditionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('leuco', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('stabilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('usually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('paste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('powder_form', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preparation_tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('re-converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('dipping', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('skying', 'VBG', '', 'O')
six 1 2 3 4 5 6
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬992_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cellulose-containing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('textile_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Claim 1 of
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('introducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('prepared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('catalytic_hydrogenation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('contacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('textile_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('gone', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('textile_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('converting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pigment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('oxidation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'992_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.6', 'VB', '', 'O') ('l.66-col.7', 'UH', '', 'O') ('l.6', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬992_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eliminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('traditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('stabilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('leuco_indigo_solution', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('powder_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reconstituting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preparation_tank', 'NN', '', 'O')
two and three
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pour', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prereduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('indigo_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dyebath', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('commence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dyeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
