('644_F.3d_1376', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('DURAMED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Women', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Health', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PADDOCK', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
DURAMED PHARMACEUTICALS INC. Teva Women 's Health Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2010-1419', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_21,_2011', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogen_tablets', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Leonard', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('B', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('Sand', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('715_F.Supp.2d_552', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('polyvinyl_alcohol', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('absorption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('storage-related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogen_tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('need', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('narrowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
PVA MBC
__NEW_SENT__
('international_patent_application', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('foreseeable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
PVA MBC
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1377', 'LS', '', 'O') ('Charanjit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brahma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Charanjit Brahma Kirkland & Ellis LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Corey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Manley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alexander', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mackinnon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Corey J. Manley J. John Lee Alexander F. Mackinnon
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Krupka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert G. Krupka
__NEW_SENT__
('*1378', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Edgar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haug', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frommer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Haug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Edgar H. Haug New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zwally', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David A. Zwally
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE GAJARSA DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Duramed Pharmaceuticals Inc. Duramed Paddock Laboratories Inc. Paddock ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharms.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('715_F.Supp.2d_552', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y.2010', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Duramed Pharms. Inc. Paddock Labs. Inc. S.D.N.Y.2010
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Duramed
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5,908,638', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬638_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('estrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hormone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('replacement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therapies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Duramed U.S._Patent 5,908,638
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('extremely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('highly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('susceptible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('¡¬638_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.6', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.46-56', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absorption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('storage-related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Accordingly Duramed MBC
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.6', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.36-45', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_26,_1995', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Duramed July_26,_1995
__NEW_SENT__
('Original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('coated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('254', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
254
__NEW_SENT__
('Original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ethylcellulose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
7
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('255', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
255
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interview', 'NN', '', 'O') ('advised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inter_alia', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Duramed 1 7
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating_comprising_ethylcellulose', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
December 3 1998 Duramed 1
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('304', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
304
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('¡¬638_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hormonal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('peri-menopausal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('menopausal', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('post-menopausal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('woman', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('coated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('organic_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('powdered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('conjugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('estrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inorganic_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('30-70', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('gel-forming', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('organic_excipient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('30-70', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('non-gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('organic_excipient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2.5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('%', 'NN', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2.5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('total', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('coated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating_comprising_ethylcellulose', 'NN', '', 'O')
one about 30-70 % about 30-70 % 2.5 %
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬638_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬638_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('hormone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('replacement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therapy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CenestinTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
March 2009 Duramed Paddock 35 271 2 Paddock Abbreviated New Drug Application Duramed
__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6-8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('generic_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polyvinyl_alcohol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('marketed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Opadry_AMB', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Duramed 1 4 and 6-8 Paddock PVA MBC
__NEW_SENT__
('Paddock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amendment-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*1379', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating_comprising_ethylcellulose', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Duramed PVA
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pre-amendment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('international_patent_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Colorcon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Cooperation', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Treaty', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colorcon_PCT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Paddock Colorcon the Patent Cooperation Treaty Colorcon_PCT
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colorcon_PCT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('discloses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('MBCs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Opadry_AMB', 'UH', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Description', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Prior', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Art', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('notes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drawbacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
Colorcon_PCT January 25 1996 `` Description of the Prior Art '' PVA MBC
__NEW_SENT__
('Paddock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('3,935,326', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Groppenbacher_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1976', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moisture-tight', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Chemist', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('tests', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('PVA_MBCs', 'VBP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concludes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Opadry_AMB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('highly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('scientific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA_MBCs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('authored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scientific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conferences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('May', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invoices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('indicating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Opadry_AMB', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Colorcon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
1 3,935,326 1976 PVA 2 December 1995 `` Manufacturing Chemist '' PVA_MBCs Opadry_AMB 3 three PVA_MBCs May 1995 November 1998 4 Colorcon September 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Paddock Duramed
__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('715', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('555-56', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Duramed 715 F.Supp.2d 555-56
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ethylcellulose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('narrowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('triggering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Festo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Shoketsu', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kinzoku', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kogyo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kabushiki', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('344_F.3d_1359', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1366-67', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Festo', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('IX', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surrendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('territory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O')
Duramed Festo Corp. Shoketsu Kinzoku Kogyo Kabushiki Co. 1366-67 Festo IX Duramed
__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('715', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('559-60', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Duramed 715 F.Supp.2d 559-60
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rebut', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Festo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inter_alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unforeseeability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Duramed Festo PVA MBC
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('560', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
560
__NEW_SENT__
('Rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA_MBCs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('foreseeable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('narrowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colorcon_PCT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moisture_barrier_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Opadry_AMB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paddock', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('generic_product', 'NN', '', 'O')
Duramed Colorcon_PCT PVA Opadry_AMB Paddock
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('560-61', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reinforced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pre-September', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('invoices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Opadry_AMB', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Groppenbacher_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('coating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ensure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'moisture", 'VB', '', 'O') ('tight', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ness', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'insolub", 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ility', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tract', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O')
1 1996 2 PVA
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('561-62', 'CD', '', 'O')
1 Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Duramed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colorcon_PCT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA_MBCs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drawbacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('serious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('effectiveness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MBC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effectiveness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unknown', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVA_MBCs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unforeseeable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Duramed Colorcon_PCT PVA_MBCs PVA MBC PVA 1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('563', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
563
__NEW_SENT__
('Duramed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Duramed
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
