('214_F.3d_1302', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ELEKTA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INSTRUMENT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('O.U.R', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ELEKTA INSTRUMENT S.A.
__NEW_SENT__
('SCIENTIFIC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
SCIENTIFIC INTERNATIONAL INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1556', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_1,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_10,_2000', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gamma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKenna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('51_F.Supp.2d_478', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('seller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Lawrence M. McKenna J. 51_F.Supp.2d_478
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('be', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('latitudes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('30¢X', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('45¢X', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 30¢X 45¢X
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1304', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Theresa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gillis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Day', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pogue', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Theresa M. Gillis Jones Reavis & Pogue New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thompson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rice', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nemerovski', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Canady', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Falk', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rabkin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Todd E. Thompson Howard Rice California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Margolin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('California', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Anthony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('De', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alcuaz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Amy E. Margolin San_Francisco California Anthony De Alcuaz Palo Alto California
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('O.U.R', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Scientific', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4,780,898', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cross-motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Elekta_Instrument_S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Elekta', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Scientific International Inc. OSI United_States_District_Court U.S. 4,780,898 Elekta
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Elekta_Instrument_S.A.', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('O.U.R', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Scientific', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Int', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('51_F.Supp.2d_478', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y.1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Scientific Int
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Rotating', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Gamma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('RGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'898_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')
OSI Rotating Gamma System 1
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Elekta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'898_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('medical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('gamma_units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Elekta
__NEW_SENT__
('Gamma_units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('brain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tumors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('focused', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therapy', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Elekta', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('51', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('479', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Elekta 51 F.Supp.2d 479
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('typical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gamma_unit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('beams', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('aimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('focal_point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('brain', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('focal_point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beams', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('destroys', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('abnormal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('brain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tissue', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gamma_units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('consist', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('radioactive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cobalt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('isotopes', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hemispherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('narrow', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('beneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('collimator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('aligned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('table', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gamma_unit', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 2 3 4
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('479-80', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'898_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reduces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scatter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gamma_unit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'898_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._38-43', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._3,_ll._8-9', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
one five
__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sole', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gamma_unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('radially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('focal_point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accommodating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('radially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('focal_point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diametrical_plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('zone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('latitudes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('30¢X-45¢X', 'CD', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('diametrical_plane', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('col._3,_ll._16-27', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'898_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('depicts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('*1305.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6_and_19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diametrical_plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('zone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('latitudes', 'VB', '', 'O') ('30¢X-45¢X', 'CD', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('diametrical_plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
8 11 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('col._1,_ll._44-50', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6_and_19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('annular', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('zone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('maximally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('latitudes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('30¢X', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('-45¢X', ':', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diametrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vertical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O')
8 30¢X
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._16-22', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._3,_ll._2-3', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
col._3,_ll._2-3
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6_and_19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gamma_unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beams', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('pass', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('focal_point', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('F', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('impinge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('solely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_shield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
8 2
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._3,_ll._3-7', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('OSI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('offers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('RGS', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gamma_unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('latitudes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ranging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('14¢X', 'CD', 'GPE', 'B') ('>', 'XX', 'GPE', 'I') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('43¢X', 'CD', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diametrical_plane', 'NN', '', 'O')
the United States 14¢X > 43¢X
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Elekta', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('51', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('481', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Elekta 51 F.Supp.2d 481
__NEW_SENT__
('Elekta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Elekta OSI 1
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('479', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
479
__NEW_SENT__
('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Elekta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cross-moved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
OSI Elekta
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Elekta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('cross-motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interpreting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gamma_units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1306', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation_sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('beam_channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('beginning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('0', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('30¢X-45¢X', 'CD', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ('>', 'XX', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'898_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
OSI Elekta 1 OSI 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('485', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Id.at 485
__NEW_SENT__
('OSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
OSI
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1 1994
__NEW_SENT__
