('516_F.3d_1350', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ERICO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VUTEC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wiremaid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
ERICO INTERNATIONAL CORPORATION Plaintiff-Appellee Wiremaid Products Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('Doc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Marketing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Doc 's Marketing Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2007-1168', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Feb._19,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('April_10,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('communications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J-hook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('fastener', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Kathleen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Malley", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Ohio Kathleen M. O'Malley J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on-sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Vacated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1351', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Jay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Campbell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Renner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Otto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Boisselle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sklar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cleveland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jay R. Campbell Cleveland Ohio
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tucker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Todd R. Tucker Mark C. Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('Douglas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sprinkle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gifford', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Krass', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sprinkle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Citkowski', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Troy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Douglas W. Sprinkle Anderson & Citkowski P.C. Troy Michigan
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schneider', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark D. Schneider
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Marketing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Erico_Int', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('l_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Erico', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Doc 's Marketing Corp. Doc Northern_District Ohio Plaintiff-Appellee Erico_Int
__NEW_SENT__
('Erico_Int', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('l_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mktg.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('1:05-cv-2924', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_1174259_(N.D.Ohio_May_3,_2006)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Initial_Order', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Erico_Int', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('l_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1352', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mktg.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1:05-cv-2924', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_108450_(N.D.Ohio_Jan._9,_2007)', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Reconsideration', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Order', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Doc 's Mktg. Inc. Doc 's 2007_WL_108450_(N.D.Ohio_Jan._9,_2007) `` Reconsideration Order ``
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Doc
__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Erico', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('develops', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufactures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fasteners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('installation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('communications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cables', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('buildings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facilities', 'NNS', '', 'O')
I. Erico
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Erico', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('popular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fastener', 'NN', '', 'O')
Erico
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('strengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sizes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Erico', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Raymond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laughlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._5740,994', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬994_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')
Raymond Scott Laughlin U.S. Patent No._5740,994 ¡¬994_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬994_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬994_patent April 21 1998 December 26 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬994_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
6 ¡¬994_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Erico', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('asserts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O')
17
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('run', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('spaced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('comprised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('curved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('saddle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('smooth', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('down-turned', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('obtuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('angle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lateral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('edges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('suspending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('run', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('saddle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('saddle', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('spacing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('saddles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('run', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('run', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sags', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('saddles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', '', 'O') ('cm', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('saddles', 'NNS', '', 'O')
17
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬994_Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.9', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.61-67', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬994_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('*1353.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
18 ¡¬994_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬994_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reexamination', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('No._90', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('/005,606', 'NNP', '', 'O')
January 2000 the United States Patent and Trademark Office ¡¬994_patent Reexamination No._90
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('cancelled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('references-Akashi', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('et', 'FW', '', 'O') ('al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
PTO 35 103 three references-Akashi
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('¡¬290', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('3-89290', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sep.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Japanese', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('Kokai', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Erico', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', 'ORG', 'I') ('For', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Communications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Low', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Voltage', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Applications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') ('pp', '.', '', 'O')
3-89290 Sep. 11 1991 Japanese Erico `` For Communications & Low Voltage Applications ''
__NEW_SENT__
('3-26', 'LS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('OBO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bettermann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Publication', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('p.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('243', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Cable', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Support', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Clips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('p.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3-26 1994 OBO Bettermann Publication 243 18
__NEW_SENT__
('Ex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('parte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Raimond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laughlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No.2002-0244', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_14,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Raimond Scott Laughlin
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Interferences', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cancellations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Board of Patent Appeals Interferences Board
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('survived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 17
__NEW_SENT__
('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('manufactures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hardware', 'NN', '', 'O') ('items', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('manufactures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('J-Hooks', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Doc
__NEW_SENT__
('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('concedes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('copies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Erico', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O')
Doc Erico
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Erico', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('copy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('informed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O')
2005 Doc Doc
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('assured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Erico', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('J-Hook', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inventory', 'NN', '', 'O')
Doc
__NEW_SENT__
('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Erico', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('refrain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('future', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('copying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J-Hooks', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Doc Erico J-Hooks
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('very', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('promised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('retain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('continued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('knock', 'VB', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('J-Hooks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Doc J-Hooks
__NEW_SENT__
('Initial_Order', 'VB', '', 'O') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'CD', '', 'O') ('*5', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Erico', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enjoin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬994_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Doc
__NEW_SENT__
('Doc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('challenged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Doc Claim 17 's
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
