('157_F.3d_887', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('EMI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GROUP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NORTH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('INTEL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant/Cross-Appellant', '$', '', 'O')
EMI GROUP NORTH AMERICA INC. INTEL
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._97-1137', 'NN', '', 'O') ('97-1153', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._29,_1998', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Sept._29,_1998
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nov._30,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing
__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fabricating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('metal_oxide_semiconductor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('MOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('field_effect_transistors', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O')
MOS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Roderick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKelvie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('928_F.Supp._449', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('936_F.Supp._1186', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Roderick R. McKelvie J. 928_F.Supp._449
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cross-appealed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('challenging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Affirmed
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*889', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bradley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
James P. Bradley Sidley & Austin Dallas Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chibib', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kathi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael Chibib Kathi A
__NEW_SENT__
('Cover', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kavrukov', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Phillips', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cooper', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Parsons', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nichols', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Arsht', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tunnell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Ivan S. Kavrukov Peter J. Phillips Cooper & Dunham LLP New York City Donald F. Parsons Jr. Nichols Arsht & Tunnell Wilmington DE
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hemingway', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lisa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baeurle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nichols', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Arsht', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tunnel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
D. Scott Hemingway Sidley & Austin Lisa B. Baeurle Morris Nichols Arsht & Tunnel
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Elacqua', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brobeck', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Phleger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harrison', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant/cross-appellant', 'CD', '', 'O')
James J. Elacqua Palo Alto
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Susan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knoll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dowler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Durkee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Susan K. Knoll Jeffrey L. Garrett Michael S. Dowler Arnold White & Durkee
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Detkin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Seeley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Intel_Corporation', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Santa', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Clara', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Peter N. Detkin Mark V. Seeley Intel_Corporation Santa Clara
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Amber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hatfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Durkee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Amber L. Hatfield Arnold White & Durkee
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN PLAGER BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-day', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Intel_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Intel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._4486,943', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'943_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('EMI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('North', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('America.1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('EMI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Markman three Intel United States EMI Group EMI
__NEW_SENT__
('Intel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('inter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('alia', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Intel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'943_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Intel Intel
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PATENTED', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('INVENTION', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'943_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Zero', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Drain', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Overlap', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Self', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Aligned', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Contact', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Method', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('MOS', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Devices', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fabricating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('metal_oxide_semiconductor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('MOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('field_effect_transistors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('microprocessor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O')
`` Zero Drain Overlap and Self Aligned Contact Method for MOS Devices '' December 11 1984 MOS
__NEW_SENT__
('Each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MOS_transistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('turn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('off', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('million', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('transistors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
several million
__NEW_SENT__
('MOS_transistors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('built', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wafer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('forms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transistor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MOS_transistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('typically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('deposited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dielectric', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('insulating', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('conductive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('drain', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conductive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('channel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('poorly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('conductive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('MOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
MOS
__NEW_SENT__
('*890.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O') ('Upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contributes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('discontinued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reverts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('static', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ceases', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('emit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('signals', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('MOS_transistors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dielectric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('illustration', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('silicon_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('depositing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polysilicon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dielectric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('doping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polysilicon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('activating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ionic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('electricity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vertically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('implanting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('doping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('silicon_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('become', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('conductive', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('shielded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('implantation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implantation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('edges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('vertically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aligned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implantation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('heated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('activate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implanted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('conductive', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undesirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consequence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implanted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('tend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('diffuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Diffusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('causes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('buildup', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Miller_capacitance', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reduces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('operating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O')
Miller_capacitance
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'943_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MOS_transistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fabrication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reduces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('occurrence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Miller_capacitance', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'943", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dielectric', 'NN', '', 'O') ('oxide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('thermally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('grown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate_electrode', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('serves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mask', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('implantation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('spacing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fig._1', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'943_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
Fig._1
__NEW_SENT__
