('265_F.3d_1268', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FRANKLIN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
GFI FRANKLIN
__NEW_SENT__
('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Astro_Lounger_Furniture_Manufacturing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Parkhill_Furniture', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Washington Furniture Manufacturing Co. Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._00-1268', 'RB', '', 'O') ('00-1288', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Sept._7,_2001', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sectional_sofa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reclining_seats', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('console', 'NN', '', 'O') ('separating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seats', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mississippi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Glen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davidson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('27_F.Supp.2d_686', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('88_F.Supp.2d_619', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Mississippi Glen H. Davidson Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('waiver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney-client', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('privilege', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intentionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Mayer Chief_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1271', 'NN', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James J
__NEW_SENT__
('Foster', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wolf', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Greenfield', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sacks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lowrie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Foster Wolf Greenfield & Sacks P.C. Boston GFI Inc. Matthew B. Lowrie
__NEW_SENT__
('Norwood', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lawing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Winston-Salem', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Franklin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Norwood Robinson Robinson & Lawing L.L.P. Franklin Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taylor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John N. Taylor Jr. Stephen Robinson
__NEW_SENT__
('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Bryan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Medlock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
V. Bryan Medlock Sidley & Austin Dallas Washington Furniture Manufacturing Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Constantine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Trela', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Maher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sidley', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Austin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Constantine L. Trela Jr. Joseph B. Maher Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Burns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Okolona', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MS.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('J.T', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Kenneth M. Burns Okolona MS. J.T
__NEW_SENT__
('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Parkhill_Furniture', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Creekmore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amory', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mississippi', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Martin Washington DC Parkhill_Furniture Inc. John M. Creekmore
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MAYER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('formerly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Gentry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gallery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mississippi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._5064,244', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Franklin_Corp.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('88_F.Supp.2d_619', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Miss.2000', 'ADD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GFI_III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Parkhill_Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Parkhill', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('furniture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Franklin_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':97cv16-D-A', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Miss', 'NN', '', 'O')
Chief_Judge GFI Inc. The Gentry Gallery Inc. GFI Northern_District Mississippi 1 United States ¡¬244_patent GFI Inc. GFI_III 2 Parkhill_Furniture Inc 's Parkhill 8000 GFI Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept._8,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("''", "''", 'GPE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Astro_Lounger_Furniture_Manufacturing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Astro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1272', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('GFI_III', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Franklin_Industries', 'NNPS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Astro', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('cross-appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Franklin_Industries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('27_F.Supp.2d_686', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Miss.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('287', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Washington Furniture Manufacturing Company Washington '' ¡¬244_patent 35 103 1994 GFI_III Franklin_Industries Washington Astro 1 GFI Inc. 2 35 287 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sectional_sofa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reclining_seats', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wedge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('console', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reclining_seats', 'NNS', '', 'O')
GFI January 3 1991
__NEW_SENT__
('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('Make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Special', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('expedite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O')
GFI
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_12,_1991', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
GFI June_12,_1991
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('12', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬244_patent November 12 1991
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('discussions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Walter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Durling', 'VBG', 'PERSON', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('furniture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mississippi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('built', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('loveseat-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recliners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('middle', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('console', 'NN', '', 'O')
Walter Durling Mississippi two
__NEW_SENT__
('Durling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('months', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
two months
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discussions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('centered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extracting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'VBG', 'PERSON', 'B') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conception', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
GFI Durling Durling
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('specify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recliner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('controls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sproule', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('saw', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('furniture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('or', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('console-mounted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('controls', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sproule ¡¬244_patent Durling late October or early November of 1990
__NEW_SENT__
('Durling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exchange', 'VB', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conception', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conception', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('refused', 'VBD', '', 'O')
¡¬244_patent GFI
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('GFI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Franklin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Astro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Parkhill', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Franklin', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1997 GFI Franklin Astro Parkhill Washington Franklin
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('equitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-jury', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
