('754_F.3d_1364', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United_States_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('GEMALTO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('HTC_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Exedea', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Google', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Motorola_Mobility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motorola_Mobility', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Samsung_Electronics_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Samsung_Telecommunications_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
GEMALTO S.A. HTC CORPORATION HTC_America Inc. Exedea Inc. Google Inc. LLC Motorola_Mobility Inc. Samsung_Electronics_Co. Ltd. Samsung_Telecommunications_America LLC Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2013-1397', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_19,_2014', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microcontroller', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2012_WL_2505745', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The United States District Court Texas Leonard Davis J. 2012_WL_2505745
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United_States_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The United_States_Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_semiconductor_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('integrating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electronic_circuit_components', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_processing_unit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embedded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1365', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whealan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chevy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chase', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
John M. Whealan Chevy Chase MD
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Dirk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKool', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cote', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('N.Y.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Joel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thollander', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Dirk D. Thomas McKool Smith P.C. Washington DC Robert A. Cote New_York N.Y. Joel L. Thollander Austin
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perlson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Emanuel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Urquhart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David A. Perlson Quinn Emanuel Urquhart & Sullivan LLP of San_Francisco CA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Verhoeven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Antonio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sistos', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Charles K. Verhoeven Antonio R. Sistos
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kristin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Madigan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Milowic', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('N.Y.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kristin J. Madigan San_Francisco CA Joseph Milowic III Robert B. Wilson NEWMAN DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1366', 'FW', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._6308,317', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬317_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('7,117,485', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬485_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('7,818,727', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('727', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Gemalto S.A. Gemalto U.S. 7,117,485 7,818,727
__NEW_SENT__
('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('HTC_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Exedea', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Google', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Motorola_Mobility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Samsung_Electronics_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Samsung_Telecommunications_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gemalto HTC Corporation HTC_America Inc. Exedea Inc. Google Inc. LLC Samsung_Electronics_Co. Ltd. LLC Eastern_District Texas three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('challenges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gemalto
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬317_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬485_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬727_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('derive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('provisional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application,1', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('share', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('title', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('High', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Level', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Programming', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Language', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Microcontroller', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
Microcontroller
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('resource-constrained', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('microcontrollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('programs', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_languages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Java', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
2 Java
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('microprocessor-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('personal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Java_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gemalto
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('processors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('off-chip_memory', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Gemalto
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('microcontroller-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_cards', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('smart_cards', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('external', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('function', 'VB', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('constrained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Java', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('implementations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('microcontroller-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('smart_cards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_cards', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gemalto Java
__NEW_SENT__
('Due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disparity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constraints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('demands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('f', 'LS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('itting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Java', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('smart_cards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('playing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('golf', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telephone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('booth', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Java
__NEW_SENT__
('Joint', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Appendix', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Joint Appendix J.A
__NEW_SENT__
('643', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('quoting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Sun', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Microsystems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('CEO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('McNealy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('quotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('marks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
643 Sun Microsystems Scott McNealy
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enabled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('resource-constrained', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_languages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Java', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('minimizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('consumed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('execution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gemalto Java
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resource-constrained', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embedded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('executes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converted_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('virtual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('translate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converted_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('execute', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('on-chip_memory', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Java', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('fit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constraints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('execution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Java
__NEW_SENT__
('*1367', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('smartphones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('run', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Android', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('operating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Java_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Android', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('kit', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
October 2010 Gemalto Android Android
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('contended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('smartphones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('resource-constrained', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('off-chip_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Java_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('personal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('narrowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬317_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('38_and_39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬485_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬727_patent3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_card', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converted_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gemalto 6 1 4 and 5 38_and_39 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬317_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_card', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
Claim 1 ¡¬317_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_card', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terminal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('communicator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('communicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terminal', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_language_format', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_language_format', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('compiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('converting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O')
first at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jumps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('destinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('converting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vice-versa', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('modifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('identifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('strings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('unique', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('identifiers', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('renumbering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('interpret', 'VB', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_language_format', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('interpret', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('execution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('communicator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('communicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terminal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬317_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('19_ll._38', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-67', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬727_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 3 3
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and.at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loaded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('interpreted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('programming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiler', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('programs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('level', 'NN', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
and.at least one at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('post', 'NN', '', 'O') ('processing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1368', 'NN', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resource_constraints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬727_patent_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('19_ll._29', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-43', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_card', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('store', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converted_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resource_constraints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬727_patent_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('19_ll._41', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-43', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program_memory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('-i.e.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Java', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('high_level_programming_language', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Java
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('26', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('footnote', 'NN', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
26
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('resource_constraints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('insufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compiled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unconverted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('40-41', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_card', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('card', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_semiconductor_substrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_processing_unit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('31', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
31
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('programmable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_semiconductor_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('integrating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electronic_circuit_components', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_processing_unit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embedded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('33', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
33
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gemalto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'all", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('program_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_semiconductor_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ("'off", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused..', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Android', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('off-chip_memory', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('off-chip_memory-i.e.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gemalto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('theory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('temporarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('loaded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('on-chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cache', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('execution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gemalto
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temporary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cache', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gemalto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('de', 'FW', '', 'O') ('novo', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lighting', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ballast', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Elecs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Philips Elecs
__NEW_SENT__
('N.A', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
N.A
__NEW_SENT__
('Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('744_F.3d_1272', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1276-77', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2014', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Cybor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FAS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('138_F.3d_1448', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1454-55', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1276-77 Cybor Corp. FAS Techs. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bd', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Univ', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Tex', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sys', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BENQ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Am', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('533_F.3d_1362', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1367', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1367
__NEW_SENT__
