('618_F.3d_1294', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('GEO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
GEO
__NEW_SENT__
('M.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MARTIN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Family', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trust-1989', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ALLIANCE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MACHINE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SYSTEMS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
M. MARTIN COMPANY the Martin Family
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2009-1132', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2009-1151', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._20,_2010', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bundle_breakers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_4105832', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('560_F.Supp.2d_893', 'CD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alsup', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('634_F.Supp.2d_1024', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District California William H. Alsup J. 634_F.Supp.2d_1024
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cross-appealed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('standing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('profit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1296', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Krieg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Keller', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sloan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Reilley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Roman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kenneth E. Keller Krieg Keller Sloan Reilley & Roman LLP San Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Holland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lisi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Christopher T. Holland Michael D. Lisi
__NEW_SENT__
('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vitt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dorsey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Whitney', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
J. Thomas Vitt Minneapolis
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sri', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sankaran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brogan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Torvik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Sri K. Sankaran John J. Brogan Bart B. Torvik
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
ARCHER PROST Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hung', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._6655,566', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Northern_District California U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Geo', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('M.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alliance', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mach', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
M. Martin Co. Alliance Mach
__NEW_SENT__
('Sys', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", '``', '', 'O') ('l', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('634_F.Supp.2d_1024', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2008', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Opinion', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
LLC 634_F.Supp.2d_1024 2008 JMOL Opinion
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('separate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stacked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('traditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('compliance_structures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('break', 'VB', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heights', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('plants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('typically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('prepare', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('stacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bundles', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rotary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('die', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scores', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('weakened', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('boxes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Next', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('collects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stacks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('aligns', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('weakened', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('weakened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('planes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('separates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bundles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('breaking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('weakened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('planes', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('puts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pallets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('separating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bundles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2_and_3', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
August 28 2002 December 2 2003
__NEW_SENT__
('*1297.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('typical_bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upstream', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstream', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O')
14 10 13
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('weakened', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('straddles', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('breaking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('stopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('16_and_17', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('lowered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O')
9
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstream', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pivots', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('axis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('break', 'VB', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle', 'NN', '', 'O')
103
__NEW_SENT__
('Unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('typical_bundle_breaker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('bundle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('off', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstream', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('advancing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('continue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('breaking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bundle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('breakers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sort', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Pallmac', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('feed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('bundle_breaker', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('speed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O')
one Pallmac two
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multiple-log', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('came', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side-by-side_logs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('perhaps', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('miscount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breaking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('exert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unequal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('M', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ore', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('exerted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('taller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('damage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('compressible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cardboard', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('compressible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('insufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shorter', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bundles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('broken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('log..', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'lack", 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compliance', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('force', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side_logs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬566_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.16-31', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬566_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Merrill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Talken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('came', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('solve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compliance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('compliance_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Merrill Martin Daniel Talken
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('compliance_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
20
__NEW_SENT__
