('748_F.3d_1326', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('HOFFMANN-LA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ROCHE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('APOTEX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
ROCHE INC. Genentech Inc. APOTEX INC. Apotex Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Hoffmann-La_Roche_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Genentech Inc. Laboratories Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Hoffmann-La_Roche_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Watson_Laboratories', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Actavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Watson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cobalt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cobalt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Genentech Inc. Watson_Laboratories Inc. Actavis Inc. Watson Pharma Inc. Cobalt Pharmaceuticals Inc. Cobalt Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Hoffmann-La_Roche_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Orchid_Chemicals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Orchid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Healthcare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Orchid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Orgenus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Genentech Inc. Orchid Healthcare Orchid Pharmaceuticals Inc. Orgenus Pharma Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Hoffmann-La_Roche_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genentech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Genpharm', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('ULC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('formerly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Genpharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genpharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Genentech Inc. Mylan Pharmaceuticals Inc. Genpharm ULC Genpharm Inc. Genpharm L.P. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2013-1128', 'RB', 'GPE', 'B') ('2013-1161', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2013-1162', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2013-1163', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2013-1164', 'CD', '', 'O')
Nos._2013-1128 2013-1162
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_11,_2014', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing*', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_11,_2014', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rehearing*
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('commenced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('monthly_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('R.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Chesler', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('2011_WL_7121450', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2012_WL_1637736', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2013_WL_323335', 'CD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey Stanley R. Chesler J. 2011_WL_7121450
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('monthly', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('regimen', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('set', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('150', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge monthly 150
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1327', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Waddell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Loeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Loeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mark E. Waddell Loeb & Loeb LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Warren', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MacRae', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paula', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Colbath', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kathleen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gersh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Warren K. MacRae Paula K. Colbath Kathleen Gersh
__NEW_SENT__
('Deanne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mazzochi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rakoczy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Molino', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mazzochi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Siwik', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Deanne M. Mazzochi Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rakoczy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Raghavan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hunt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Watson_Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
William Rakoczy Tara M. Raghavan Eric R. Hunt Watson_Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Feldman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Louise', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Walsh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Philip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Segrest', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('R.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cherry', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sherry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rollo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Husch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Blackwell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Edgar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Parke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kurz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frommer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haug', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Steven E. Feldman James P. White T. Walsh Sherry L. Rollo Husch Blackwell Chicago Apotex Inc. Edgar H. Richard E. Parke Richard F. Kurz Frommer Lawrence & Haug LLP
__NEW_SENT__
(';', ':', '', 'O') ('Stuart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sender', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Choi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Budd_Larner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Short_Hills', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('et_al', 'NN', '', 'O')
Stuart D. Sender Michael Choi Budd_Larner P.C.
__NEW_SENT__
(';', ':', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Utermohlen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Oliff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Meara", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Oliff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Berridge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alexandria', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Orchid_Chemicals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
William J. Utermohlen James A. Oliff John W. O'Meara Oliff & Berridge PLC Alexandria VA for Orchid_Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cecchi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Byrne', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bain', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gilfillan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cecchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Stewart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Olstein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Roseland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Watson_Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
James E. Cecchi Carella Cecchi Stewart & Olstein of Roseland NJ Watson_Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calmann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Saiber', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newark', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('et_al.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Radin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Budd_Larner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Short_Hills', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('et_al', 'NN', '', 'O')
Arnold B. Calmann Newark Bruce D. Radin Budd_Larner P.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fox', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rothschild', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Exton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Orchid_Chemicals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Charles N. Quinn Exton PA for Orchid_Chemicals & Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN LOURIE BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hoffmann-La', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._7718,634', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬634_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._7410,957', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬957_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Plaintiff Hoffmann-La Roche Inc. Roche the District of New_Jersey 1-8 1-10
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('once', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('monthly_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ibandronate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('commercially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('monthly', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('BonivaTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O')
Roche monthly the United States Food and Drug Administration FDA 2005
__NEW_SENT__
('Once', 'IN', '', 'O') ('monthly', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('Boniva', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*1328', 'NN', '', 'O') ('THE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('150', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('milligram', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mg', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronate', 'NN', '', 'O')
monthly THE_R 150
__NEW_SENT__
('Osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disease', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abnormal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resorption', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Resorption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('broken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('down', 'RP', '', 'O') ('causes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('decreased', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fractures', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('potent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inhibitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resorption', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬957_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._39-40', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('abnormal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('destruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gradual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('restoration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mineral', 'NN', '', 'O') ('density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('BMD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
BMD
__NEW_SENT__
('Bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('administered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fraction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('absorbed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Additionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('result', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('esophageal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('taking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('adhere', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('regimen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tablet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fasting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'TIME', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'TIME', 'I') ('30', 'CD', 'TIME', 'I') ('minutes', 'NNS', 'TIME', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drinking', 'VBG', '', 'O')
at least 30 minutes
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('past', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inconvenience', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('regimen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compliance', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Researchers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('believed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less-frequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('result', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('continuing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('successful', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Roche', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬634_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬957_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬634_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Roche ¡¬634_patent ¡¬957_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬634_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('957', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('describe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('150', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('monthly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_day', 'NN', '', 'O')
1-8 ¡¬634_patent 1-10 957 150
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'I') ('¡¬634_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 of the 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inhibiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('postmenopausal_osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('postmenopausal_woman', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inhibition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('postmenopausal_osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('commencing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('postmenopausal_woman', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tablet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tablet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('150', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
first about 150
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('continuing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('monthly', 'RB', 'DATE', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tablet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('150', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ibandronic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O')
monthly about 150
__NEW_SENT__
