('514_F.3d_1244', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('HALLIBURTON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ENERGY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('SERVICES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I_LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Drilling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fluids', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
HALLIBURTON ENERGY SERVICES INC. M-I_LLC M-I Drilling Fluids
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._2007-1149', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._25,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_18,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil_field_drilling_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('fragile_gels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('drilling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mud', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('456_F.Supp.2d_811', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
The District Court Texas Leonard E. Davis J. 456_F.Supp.2d_811
__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Michel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1245', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Manzo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Alex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McFarron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Manzo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cummings', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mehler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Edward D. McFarron Manzo Cummings & Mehler Ltd. Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Monte', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patterson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dykema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gossett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Monte M. Bond David L. Patterson Dykema Gossett PLLC Dallas Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keville', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
John R. Keville Howrey LLP Houston Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cagle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Stephen H. Cagle Richard L. Stanley
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Calvin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Capshaw', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McCarroll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Longview', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
S. Calvin Capshaw Brown McCarroll LLP Longview Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('*1246', '``', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('FOGEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MICHEL', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Halliburton_Energy_Services', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Halliburton_Energy_Services Inc. Halliburton Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('Halliburton_Energy_Services', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I_LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('No._6', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (':05-CV-155', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Tex', '.', '', 'O')
Halliburton_Energy_Services Inc. M-I_LLC No._6
__NEW_SENT__
('Nov._20,_2006', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I_LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1-BIG_TOKEN__3_and_5__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6887,832', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('832', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
M-I_LLC U.S. No._6887,832 35
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
November 7 2007
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lacked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('artisan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil_field_drilling_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('fragile_gels', 'NNS', '', 'O')
I. Halliburton
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drilling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('drilling_fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('drill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cuttings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wellbore', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lubricating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('aiding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pipe', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drill', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrostatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('maintain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wellbore', 'NN', '', 'O') ('walls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('well', 'UH', '', 'O') ('blowouts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('832', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II.27-31', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
II.27-31
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('drilling_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drilling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subterranean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('drilling_fluid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invert', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('thinners', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('emulsifiers', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('weighting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('running', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('casing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('borehole', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('drilling_fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('drilling_fluid', 'NN', '', 'O')
Halliburton
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('appears', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preamble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('independent_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('concedes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drilling_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Halliburton
__NEW_SENT__
('Pitney', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bowes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hewlett-Packard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('182_F.3d_1298', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1305', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_preamble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('context', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_preamble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("'necessary", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('give', 'VB', '', 'O') ('life', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vitality', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_preamble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Pitney Bowes Inc. Hewlett-Packard Co. 1305
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('herein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('easily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disrupted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thinned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liquifies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('becomes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less_gel-like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('liquid-like', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stress', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('returns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stress', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('alleviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('circulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('drilling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stopped', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragileness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gels', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contributes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unique', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('surprising', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1247', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('behavior', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('advantages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('believed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('disrupted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mere', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wave', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compression', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wave', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drilling', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('seem', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('break', 'VB', '', 'O') ('instantaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('disturbed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('reversing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('minimum_pressure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('force', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('force', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flowable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II.26-42', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Rheliant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drilling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mud', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
May 2005 Halliburton M-I Texas M-I
__NEW_SENT__
('M-I', 'SYM', 'PERSON', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O')
M-I
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disputes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Markman M-I M-I
__NEW_SENT__
('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Energy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Serv.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M-I_LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('456_F.Supp.2d_811', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('825', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Tex.2006', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Halliburton Energy Serv. Inc. M-I_LLC 456_F.Supp.2d_811 825
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('looked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('definition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('subjective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unclear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('easily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('transitions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('easily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disrupted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thinned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('less_gel-like', 'UH', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('liquid-like', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('returns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('break', 'VB', '', 'O') ('instantaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('minimum_pressure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('force', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('817', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Additionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('41', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('distinguish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Halliburton 3 41
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('822-23', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('*1248.', 'UH', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('FIG._3', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('SF', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('prior_art_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACCOLADE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('tm', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
SF
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.4', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I.65-col.5', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I.7', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('70', 'CD', 'TIME', 'B') ('minute', 'NN', 'TIME', 'I') ('mark', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('height', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('curve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('stress', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('forms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('curve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('falls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('breaks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('transitions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
3 70 minute
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('graph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('delineate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exhibit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('curves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('12.1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('SF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('12.65', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ACCOLADE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('15.6', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('ACCOLADE', 'NN', 'MONEY', 'I') ('fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fall', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('themselves', 'PRP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
12.1 15.6 ACCOLADE
__NEW_SENT__
('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('456', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'FAC', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('820', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Halliburton 456 F.Supp.2d 820
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('height', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('curves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('precisely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('leg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('L-shaped', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('curve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('reach-i.e.', '.', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ("'strong", 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be-for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exhibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'fragile_gel", 'DT', 'PERSON', 'B') ('behavior', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O')
Halliburton 'fragile_gel
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Id', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'UH', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('organophilic_clay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lignite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('imported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fragile_gel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preferably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clays', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Halliburton
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('824', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
824
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('differentiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('counseled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('organophilic_clay', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('824-25', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬832_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('moot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('M-I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prejudice', 'NN', '', 'O')
November 2006 M-I
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('timely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
