('732_F.3d_1339', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('INTELLECT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WIRELESS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HTC_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
HTC_America Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2012-1658', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Oct._9,_2013', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wireless_transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('caller_identification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ID', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Northern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('910_F.Supp.2d_1056', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
the United States District Court the Northern District Illinois William T. Hart J. 910_F.Supp.2d_1056
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Moore Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('falsehoods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct_claim', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('satisfied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('element', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct_claim', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1341', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Meredith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Martin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Addy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Steptoe', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Amanda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Streff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Amanda K. Streff
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Raymond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Niro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vickrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Niro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Haller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Niro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Raymond P. Niro Paul K. Vickrey Niro Haller Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Korniczky', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sheppard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mullin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hampton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Diego', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Stephen S. Korniczky Sheppard Mullin Richter
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bader', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mueller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Martin R. Bader Matthew M. Mueller
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nagendra', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Setty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kanabe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Nagendra Setty George Kanabe San Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Buccigross', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Diego', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Graham Marc Buccigross
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("O'MALLEY", 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PROST O'MALLEY
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Intellect_Wireless', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Intellect', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._7266,186', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('¡¬186_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('7,310,416', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('¡¬416_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Intellect_Wireless Inc. U.S. 7,310,416
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('wireless_transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('caller_identification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ID', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('share', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('caller_ID_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('personal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cell_phone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('via', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬186_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('57', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('id', 'UH', '', 'O')
57
__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('4.', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('l.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('66-col.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('5_l._4', 'CD', '', 'O')
4.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('displaying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('caller_ID_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cell_phone', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('15_ll._20', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-24', '.', '', 'O')
15_ll._20
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'I') ('¡¬186_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recipient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('picture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_originator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telephone_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('receiver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-facsimile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('picture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supplied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_originator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('caller_ID', 'NN', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('communications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telephone_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_originator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_originator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('caller_ID', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('picture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('message_center', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Claim 1 of the
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('display', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('picture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('caller_ID', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬186_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Intellect', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HTC_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
HTC Corporation HTC_America Inc. HTC
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sole', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Daniel Henderson
__NEW_SENT__
('Intellect_Wireless', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('910_F.Supp.2d_1056', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.2012', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Intellect_Wireless Inc. HTC Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Intellect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
