('269_F.3d_1360', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('John_Lazzeroni', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Melinda_K._Carevich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HARLEY-DAVIDSON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Cross_Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
J & M CORPORATION John_Lazzeroni Melinda_K._Carevich
__NEW_SENT__
('Radio_Sound', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Cross_Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Radio_Sound Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._00-1295-00-1297', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Nov._2,_2001', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mount', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('motorcycle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arizona', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Broomfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'VB', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court District Arizona Robert C. Broomfield J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Archer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Senior_Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('double', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Archer
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1361', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Law', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Group', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Phoenix', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('AZ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Stephen T. Sullivan Sullivan Law Group Phoenix
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Tish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Tish L. Berard
__NEW_SENT__
('*1362', 'NFP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Katherine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Best', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Friedrich', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('WI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
*1362 Katherine W. Schill Michael Milwaukee
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Husmann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael E. Husmann
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ralph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('King', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('King', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Schickli', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('PLLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lexington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('KY.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior_Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
J. Ralph King King Schickli PLLC Lexington
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Senior_Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('John_Lazzeroni', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Melinda_K._Carevich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LOC', 'I') ('Arizona', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I')
J & M Corporation John_Lazzeroni Melinda_K._Carevich the District of Arizona
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Reissue', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Number', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('34,525', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distributed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Radio_Sound', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
U.S. 34,525 Harley-Davidson Inc. Radio_Sound Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
J & M_Corp. Harley-Davidson Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('CIV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('97-2353-PHX-RCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Ariz', 'NNS', '', 'O')
CIV 97-2353-PHX-RCB
__NEW_SENT__
('Feb._10,_2000', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('M_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Harley-Davidson_cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J & M
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reissue', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Number', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('34,525', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('¡¬525_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')
J & M Reissue Patent Number 34,525 `` the ¡¬525_patent ``
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('audio', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('motorcyclists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('communicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('companions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('riding', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O')
J & M 's two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('near', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcyclist', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('mouth', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('receives', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('wires', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('earphones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interior', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('receives', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('wires', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('leading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('audio', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equipment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Melinda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lazzeroni', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Applicants', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬525_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
John Melinda Lazzeroni Applicants December 8 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('Helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Applicants', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('superior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Applicants
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('via', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('drilled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('causing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('undesirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬525_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_l._63-', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_l._5', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accessory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('avoided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('Such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clamped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('extended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('down', 'RP', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulky', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('object', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('annoyingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('strike', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcyclist', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('shoulder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('turned', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('exacerbated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug_mount', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('larger', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('object', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._5-11', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('avoided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug_mount', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clamped', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')
electrical_plug_mount
__NEW_SENT__
('Applicants', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('damage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1363', 'FW', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('protrude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Applicants
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Number', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4,788,724', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬724_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissued', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('¡¬525_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pertinent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
United States 4,788,724 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('helmets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('viewing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wearer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_side_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('outside', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_side_edge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('placing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proximate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wearer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('mouth', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('placing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proximate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wearer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('mouth', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proximate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('earphones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('audio_instruments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('distal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'VB', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('clamp_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_side_edge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clamp_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outside', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('jaw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inside', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('jaw..', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('connections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wearer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('utilize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('earphones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('audio_instruments', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom_seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('outside', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jaw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wires', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom_seat', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('outside', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jaw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proximate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom_seat', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('proximate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outside', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O')
2 second
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Emphasis', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Emphasis
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4-7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('add', 'VB', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
4-7
__NEW_SENT__
('Applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('broadly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Reissue', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Declaration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Applicants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('element..', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('Accordingly', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Applicants', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('new_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('15-20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('encompassed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clamped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jaws', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Reissue Declaration Applicants Accordingly Applicants 15-20
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
35 112
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
1 35
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('251', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2 35 251
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fail', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ed', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15_through_20', 'CD', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug_mounted', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jaw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('commented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_claims', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('concept', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('occurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jaws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1364', 'XX', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Applicants', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('cancelled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new_claims', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('drafted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('means-plus-function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O')
Applicants
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('broadly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('gripping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug_mount', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15-17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent.1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Applicants', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reissued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬525_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('15-17', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬724_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
15-17 Applicants February 1 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('buying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Harley-Davidson J & M 's late 1987 early 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬724_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug_mounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('via', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate_clamps', 'NNP', '', 'O')
¡¬724_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('continued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('buy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Harley-Davidson J & M 1991
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('summer', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Radio_Sound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
the summer of 1989 Harley-Davidson Harley-Davidson
__NEW_SENT__
('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Radio_Sound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Harley-Davidson first 1990
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('extended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Radio_Sound', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('helmet_accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('numbers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('77147-BIG_TOKEN__98_and_77147__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-91C', ':', '', 'O')
1997 Radio_Sound and Harley-Davidson two
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_boom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('attach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motorcycle_helmet', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('¡¬525_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
J & M
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3-BIG_TOKEN__7_and_15__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('-17', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬525_patent2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('non-infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J & M Harley-Davidson November 1997 3-BIG_TOKEN__7_and_15__BIG_TOKEN J & M 's
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('preliminarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enjoin', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J & M
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
J & M 's J & M
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
J & M_Corp. Harley-Davidson Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('CIV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('97-2353-PHX-RCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Ariz', 'NNS', '', 'O')
CIV 97-2353-PHX-RCB
__NEW_SENT__
('May_14,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('M_I', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_plug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clamp', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M_I', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('8-15', 'CD', '', 'O')
J & M_I
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('carried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('demonstrating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
J & M
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('15-19', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('summarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
J & M
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('185_F.3d_885_(Fed.Cir.1999)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('unpublished', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('table', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
J & M_Corp. Harley-Davidson Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('affirmative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1365', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J & M Harley-Davidson
__NEW_SENT__
('Harley-Davidson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Harley-Davidson
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J & M 's J & M 's
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assertions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assertions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15-17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('contending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('means-plus-function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('statutorily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure..', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
15-17 structure..
__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
35 112
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('gripping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15-17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('corresponds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('separate_clamps', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone_mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plug_mount', 'NN', '', 'O')
15-17
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M_I', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('13-14', 'CD', '', 'O')
See J & M_I
__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate_clamps', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('gripping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15-17', 'CD', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
J & M 35
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
¡± 112
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15-17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3-7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O')
6 15-17 3-7
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counter-arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history_estoppel', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('next', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('expert_reports', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inadmissible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('defective', 'JJ', '', 'O')
J & M three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('function-way-result', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalency', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('clamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('attach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helmet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulkiness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessory', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('52', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
52
__NEW_SENT__
('Separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clamping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microphone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plug_mounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulkiness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mounts', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_clamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulkiness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accessory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('juror', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('53-54', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('abused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('excluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('expert_reports', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('accessories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J & M J & M 's
__NEW_SENT__
('Harley-Davidson_cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history_estoppel', 'NNP', '', 'O')
J & M
__NEW_SENT__
