('828_F.2d_1572', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('KORODY-COLYER', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', 'EVENT', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GENERAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MOTORS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VBP', '', 'O')
KORODY-COLYER CORPORATION Plaintiff-Appellant
__NEW_SENT__
('No._87-1180', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sept._18,_1987', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
Sept._18,_1987
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('violation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Mariana', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pfaelzer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('untimely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('certain_antitrust_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California Mariana R. Pfaelzer J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Markey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('staying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_claim', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('completion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_validity_issue', 'WP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('toll', 'VB', '', 'O') ('running', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entirely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original_complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original_complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concealment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('toll', 'VB', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Markey Chief_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1573', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dennis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Cal.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Michael J. Dennis D.C. Los_Angeles Cal.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cal_.', 'NNP', '', 'O')
John Joseph Hall
__NEW_SENT__
('Maxwell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blecher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Blecher', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Collins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cal.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Maxwell M. Blecher Blecher & Collins
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Layne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Blecher', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Collins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cal_.', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Christopher Layne Ann I. Jones Blecher & Collins
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weinbaum', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Judith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Collier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('General_Motors_Corp.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Detroit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mich.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MARKEY', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('BENNETT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert C. Weinbaum Judith L. Collier General_Motors_Corp. NEWMAN Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MARKEY', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('54', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Rule 54
__NEW_SENT__
('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Pfaelzer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ordering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('untimely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('certain_antitrust_claims', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Second_Supplemental', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amended_Complaint', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Korody-Colyer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('Korody', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('General', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motors', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Second_Supplemental Amended_Complaint Korody-Colyer Corporation ( Korody General Motors Corporation GM
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Korody', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3555,972', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
January 1980 Korody GM GM U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
GM
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Korody', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('faith', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hamper', 'VB', '', 'O') ('competition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fraud', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('knew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('knowingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('extensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pertinent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1982 GM GM GM
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Korody', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('illegal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tie-in', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('demanding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O')
Korody
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('staying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('completion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_validity_issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
July 1982
__NEW_SENT__
('Proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
GM
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Judge_Pfaelzer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fraudulently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
August 10 1984 GM 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Korody-Colyer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('General_Motors_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('224_USPQ_368_(C.D.Cal.1984)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Korody-Colyer Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_2,_1985', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
May_2,_1985
__NEW_SENT__
('760_F.2d_1293', 'LS', '', 'O') ('225_USPQ_1099_(Fed.Cir.1985)', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Korody', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Second_Supplemental', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amended_Complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O')
June 1986 Second_Supplemental
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('violated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enforcing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('knowingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fraudulently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concerned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Walker_Process', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('claim.1', 'ADD', '', 'O')
GM
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Judge_Pfaelzer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('succinct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('complete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Korody', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Walker_Process', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four-year', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1574', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
December 3 1986 Korody Walker_Process 15
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tolling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Korody', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
