('667_F.3d_1261', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('KRIPPELZ', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FORD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MOTOR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Jacob KRIPPELZ Plaintiff-Appellee FORD MOTOR COMPANY
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2011-1103', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._27,_2012', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Jan._27,_2012
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_12,_2012', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('illuminate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Northern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zagel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('670_F.Supp.2d_815', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('21,017,400', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('750_F.Supp.2d_938', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Northern District Illinois James B. Zagel J. 670_F.Supp.2d_815 21,017,400
__NEW_SENT__
('Manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Prost Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('phrase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('conical_beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'VB', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('focal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('French', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('optical_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('conical_beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
French
__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('side', 'VB', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1262', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bartlit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Beck', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Herman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Palenchar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scott', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mark E. Ferguson Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mortara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hamilton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Martha', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pacold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Adam K. Mortara Hamilton H. Hill Martha M. Pacold
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ryndak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Suri', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weimers', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ryndak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suri', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
James D. Ryndak Mark K. Suri Eric H. Ryndak & Suri LLP Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Constantine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Trela', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Constantine L. Trela Jr. Sidley Austin LLP Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Linda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Friedlieb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Linda R. Friedlieb
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gene', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schaerr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Winston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Strawn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Gene C. Schaerr Winston & Strawn LLP Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lewry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brooks', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kushman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Southfield', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MI', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Thomas A. Lewry Brooks Kushman Southfield
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("O'MALLEY", 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN PROST
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PROST', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Defendant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('*1263', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'B') ('56', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O')
Ford Motor Company Ford $ 56 million
__NEW_SENT__
('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('errors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('analyses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-liability', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('lengthy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('deceased', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle-mounted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lamp.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('titled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Emergency', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Light', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
February 1989 Jacob Krippelz `` Emergency Light ''
__NEW_SENT__
('U.S._Patent_No._5017,903', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('54', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
54
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side_view_mirror', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('shining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('downward', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('fig.1', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inclement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weather', 'NN', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fog', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('reflect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dust', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('airborne', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('visible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_drivers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('interfere', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('vision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('driving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1991
__NEW_SENT__
('He', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('says', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('sent', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('copy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('interested', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('taking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ford Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('period', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('nothing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('happened', 'VBD', '', 'O')
a period of years
__NEW_SENT__
('Then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('offering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('option', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Explorer', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('automobiles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('puddle_light', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1997 Ford Explorer
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('puddle_light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('side_view_mirror', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('shone', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('downward', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('puddle_light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('equipped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lens', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('diffused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('illuminate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('viewed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('puddle_light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O')
1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Complaint', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._98-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CV-2361', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill', '.', '', 'O')
Complaint Krippelz Ford Motor Co. Krippelz
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr._16,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ECF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('revolved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2 2
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emergency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('warning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('automotive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unadjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('directing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conical_beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('downwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('visible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1264', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('front', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('behind', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('impinging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬903_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'XX', '', 'O') ('3_l._19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-col.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('4_l._3', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('About', 'RB', 'DATE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('asked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reexamine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
About a year the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Information', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Disclosure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Statement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('accompanying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acknowledged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ongoing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Requestor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Ford Ford Requestor
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Info', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Stmt', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Aug._30,_1999', 'LS', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('¡¬903', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Reexam', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Aug._30,_1999 2
__NEW_SENT__
('File', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hist.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('12516', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('12517', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
12516 12517
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('confirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬903_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Reexam', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Certificate', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S._Patent_No._5017,903', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Aug._13,_2002', 'PRP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Certificate Aug._13,_2002
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('states', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬903_patent Mr._Krippelz Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('Those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('next', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('several', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('handled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recount', 'VB', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('state', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('much', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('analyze', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('puddle_lights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
the next several years Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('note', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2008', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench.2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Tr', 'UH', '', 'O')
2008
__NEW_SENT__
('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nov._21,_2008', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Proceedings', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('12:11-17', 'CD', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Nov._21,_2008 Proceedings
__NEW_SENT__
('114', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('125', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
114 125
__NEW_SENT__
('Infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('addressed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('French', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._1031,294', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('trans', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Ford 2 French
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_22,_1953', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
June_22,_1953
__NEW_SENT__
('13430', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DuBois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('DuBois', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
13430 DuBois DuBois
__NEW_SENT__
('DuBois', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appear', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('optical_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('illuminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pavement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('next', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O')
DuBois
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('give', 'VB', '', 'O') ('other_drivers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('know', 'VB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enough', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('room', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pass', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DuBois', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('J.A', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
DuBois J.A
__NEW_SENT__
('13431', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
13431
__NEW_SENT__
('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DuBois', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Ford DuBois 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('DuBois', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('conical_beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O')
DuBois two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬903_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DuBois', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'B') ('23', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
DuBois $ 23 million Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('Jury', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Verdict', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.BIG_TOKEN__Dec._12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('_2008__BIG_TOKEN', 'NFP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ECF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._429', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willfulness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1265', 'UH', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mr._Krippelz', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'B') ('11.7', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prejudgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Ford Mr._Krippelz $ 11.7 million $ 21 million
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('670_F.Supp.2d_806_(N.D.Ill.2009)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('willfulness', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('670_F.Supp.2d_815', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.2009', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Krippelz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('675_F.Supp.2d_881_(N.D.Ill.2009)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Krippelz Krippelz Krippelz
__NEW_SENT__
('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('Krippelz', 'NN', '', 'O') ('750_F.Supp.2d_938', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.2010', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Op', 'NNP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Ford
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
