('499_F.3d_1303', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PLASTICS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('AMERIMAX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HOME', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PRODUCTS', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gutter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('World', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amerimax_Diversified_Products', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
AMERIMAX HOME PRODUCTS INC. Gutter World Amerimax_Diversified_Products Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2006-1465', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._12,_2007', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Sept._12,_2007
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('composite_gutter_guard', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('snapped', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gutters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conrad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('431_F.Supp.2d_578', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Robert James Conrad Jr.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('melting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('capture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('attachments', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1304', 'FW', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jakes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Farabow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Garrett', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dunner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
J. Michael Jakes Finnegan Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Adams', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ashley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Adams', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Evans', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Charlotte', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
W. Thad Adams III Stephen S. Ashley Jr. Adams Evans P.A.
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rabin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Manning', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David A Rabin Morris Manning & Martin LLP Atlanta GA
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DYK', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Plastics Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Home', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amerimax_Diversified_Products', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Plastics United_States_District_Court Amerimax Home Products Inc. Amerimax_Diversified_Products Inc. Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._6463,700', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Jan._16,_2001', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
U.S. Jan._16,_2001 ¡¬700_patent L.B
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invoke', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1305', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circumstances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('gutter_guards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filtering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('dirt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leaves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('debris', 'NN', '', 'O')
Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composite_gutter_guard', 'XX', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('snaps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gutters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Fig._1', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
January 16 2001
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._09', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('/760,557', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬557_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
U.S. Patent Application No._09
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬557_application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')
December 5 2001 the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('unpatentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5555,680', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sweers', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._patent_No._5406,754', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬754_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Sweers U.S._patent_No._5406,754 Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rejecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Sweers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('welding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('spot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('every', 'DT', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('12', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('inches', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer..', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cosby every 12 inches
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('modify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Sweers', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('welds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('welds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breaks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('better', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('bond', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('debris', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sweers Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A.at', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('121', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
121
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('distinguish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('spot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('welding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('stop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('debris', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('beneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plastics Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A.at', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('131', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
131
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*1306', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous_heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uninterrupted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('longitudinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('15', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬700_patent October 15 2002
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('fourteen', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O')
¡¬700_patent fourteen three
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composite_gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('longitudinally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('U-shaped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('collecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distributing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rainwater_runoff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roofs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('residential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('homes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('buildings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elongate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('spaced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('openings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('laterally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('longitudinally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer-coated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('overlying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('openings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cooperating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('capture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('debris', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rainwater_runoff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('opposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('opposing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edges', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Claim 1 first second first second
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous_heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uninterrupted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('longitudinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opposing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('9_and_14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('welded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('weld', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5555,680', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sweers', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._patent_No._5406,754', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬754_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Two Sweers U.S._patent_No._5406,754 Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A.at', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('120', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
120
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sweers', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('disclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('gutter_guards', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sweers Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('Sweers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one-piece', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬754_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.6', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I.17', '.', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
I.17
__NEW_SENT__
('Cosby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('connect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cosby
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('fine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mechanical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fastener', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('welded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('I.65-col.5', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('I.1', 'NNP', '', 'O')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bond', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']..', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('every', 'DT', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('12', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('inches', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
approximately every 12 inches
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.5', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('II.40-44', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('n', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('applied..', 'UH', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.6', 'VB', '', 'O') ('II.1-4', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('criticizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gutter_guards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('incorporating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('costly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consuming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('labor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('intensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬700_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬700_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II.27-29', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('24', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')
February 24 2004
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('competing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Amerimax Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('comprised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('glue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cooled', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('glue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('soften', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('melt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1307', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('continuous_heat', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('encompass', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hot_glue_adhesive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Plastics Amerimax Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
L.B
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('contended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('hot_glue_adhesive', 'CD', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plastics
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('involve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('welding', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Plastics Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('define', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dictionary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('unite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('flow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mesh', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('guard_panel', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Home', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prods.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('431_F.Supp.2d_578', 'CD', '', 'O') ('581', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.N.C.2006', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('quoting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Merriam-Webster', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Online', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Dictionary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('http', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('//www', '.', '', 'O')
Plastics Inc. Amerimax Home Prods. Inc. 581 W.D.N.C.2006 Online Dictionary
__NEW_SENT__
('m-w.com/dictionary/weld', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('¡¬700_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.3', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I.44', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
I.44
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fus', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('confirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('fusion-bonding', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat-activated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('melt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('fusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('431', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('582', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Trilogy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("Commc'ns", 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Times', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fiber', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("Commc'ns", 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('109_F.3d_739', 'CD', '', 'O') ('744', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1997', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
582 Trilogy Commc'ns Inc. Times Fiber Commc'ns Inc. 744
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('melt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('attaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Amerimax Amerimax
__NEW_SENT__
('Turning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amerimax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Amerimax two
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('credited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('welding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('gluing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('accomplish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('joining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('accomplish', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('welding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('interface', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('connecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('joining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('substance', 'NN', '', 'O')
First two two third
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Warner-Jenkinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hilton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Davis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chem', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('520_U.S._17', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('35', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('117_S.Ct._1040', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('137_L.Ed.2d_146_(1997)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('quoting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Union', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Paper-Bag', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Machine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Murphy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('97_U.S._120', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('125', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('24_L.Ed._935_(1878)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('function-way-result', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
See Warner-Jenkinson Co. Hilton 520_U.S._17 35 117_S.Ct._1040 Union Paper-Bag Machine Co. Murphy 97_U.S._120 125
__NEW_SENT__
('Next', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
L.B
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invoking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('espite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adhesives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('L.B', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
L.B
__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weld', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('welding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('gutter_guard', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('431', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('583', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Plastics Inc. 583
__NEW_SENT__
('L.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plastics', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plastics
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Flex-Rest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Steelcase', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('455_F.3d_1351', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1357', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2006', 'ADD', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
LLC Steelcase Inc. 1357 Fed.Cir.2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cybor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FAS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('138_F.3d_1448', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1456', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Cybor Corp. FAS Techs. Inc. 1456
__NEW_SENT__
('Infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ferguson', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Beauregard/Logic', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Controls', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Div', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Ferguson Beauregard/Logic Controls Div
__NEW_SENT__
('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dover', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Res.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*1308', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mega', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sys.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('350_F.3d_1327', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1338', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Mega Sys.
__NEW_SENT__
