('181_F.3d_1313', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('LORAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('FAIRCHILD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SONY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
LORAL FAIRCHILD CORPORATION Sony Electronics Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('Matsushita', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industrial', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Matsushita', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Technologies', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Canon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Canon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Consumer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Information', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Components', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hitachi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hitachi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Home', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('America', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fuji', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Photo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Film', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fuji', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Photo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Film', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sanyo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sanyo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Fisher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Usa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sales', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Electronics', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Samsung', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Samsung', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('National', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Semiconductor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fairchild', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Semiconductor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
Matsushita Electric Industrial Company Ltd. Matsushita Electric Corporation of America NEC America Inc. NEC Technologies Inc. Canon Inc. Canon U.S.A. Inc. Toshiba Corp. Toshiba America Inc. Toshiba America Consumer Products Inc. Toshiba America Information Systems Inc. Toshiba America Electronic Components Inc. Hitachi Ltd. Hitachi Home Electronics Fuji Photo Film Co. Ltd. Fuji Photo Film USA Inc. Sanyo Electric Co. Ltd. Sanyo Fisher Usa ) Corp. Mitsubishi Electric Corp. Mitsubishi Electric Sales America LG Electronics U.S.A. Inc. Samsung Electronics Co. Ltd. Samsung Electronics America Inc. National Semiconductor Corporation Fairchild Semiconductor Corp. Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('No._97-1017', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_8,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('July_16,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing
__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ownership', 'NN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('931_F.Supp._1014', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Archer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Senior_Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CCD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Archer 1 2 CCD 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1315', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wyss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fielding', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
John B. Wyss Wiley Rein & Fielding Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wallace', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lyons', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James H. Wallace Jr. Gregory R. Lyons
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Carl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Moy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mitchell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('College', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Law', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('St.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O')
R. Carl Moy William Mitchell College of Law
__NEW_SENT__
('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lipsey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farabow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Charles E. Lipsey Finnegan Henderson Farabow Garrett & Dunner L.L.P. Washington D.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Douglas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jakes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kwon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Douglas B. Henderson Donald R. Dunner Barry W. Graham J. Michael Jakes Howard A. Kwon
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anzalone', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Steven M. Anzalone
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior_Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('**', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Senior_Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fairchild', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_23,_1996', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._91-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CV-5056', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Loral Fairchild Corporation Loral July_23,_1996 United_States_District_Court Sony Corporation Sony Electronics Inc. Sony Loral
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pertinent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._3931,674', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'674_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sony United_States_Patent_No._3931,674
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*1316', 'NN', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._3896,485', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'485_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents.1', 'WP', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procedural', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Background', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Loral', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'674", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'485_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japanese', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('electronics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('semiconductors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('purchase', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('semiconductors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices.2', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resolved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clarifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('go', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Loral Japanese
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Loral_Fairchild_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Victor_Co.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('906_F.Supp._813_(E.D.N.Y.1995)', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('marking', 'VBG', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Victor_Co. Japan
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('preliminary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('day', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('resolve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two day Markman
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Loral_Fairchild_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Victor_Co.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('906_F.Supp._798_(E.D.N.Y.1995)', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Victor_Co. Japan 906_F.Supp._798_(E.D.N.Y.1995)
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('neither', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Part_Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Summary_Judgment', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Non-Infringement', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ("'674_Patent", 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Civil_Action_Nos._92-0128-_ARR', 'IN', '', 'O') ('91-5056-ARR', 'CD', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Denying', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Part_Sony', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Summary_Judgment', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Non-Infringement', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ("'485_Patent", 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Denying', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Motion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Summary_Judgment', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('on', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Invalidity', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ("'485_Patent", 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Civil_Action_Nos._92-0128-_ARR', 'IN', '', 'O') ('91-5056-ARR', 'CD', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('15', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Part_Sony Motion for Summary_Judgment of Non-Infringement of the '674_Patent December 14 1995 Motion for Summary_Judgment of Non-Infringement of the '485_Patent Denying Toshiba 's Motion for Summary_Judgment on Invalidity of the '485_Patent December 15 1995
__NEW_SENT__
('Concerned', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prejudice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ownership', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('weeks', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('special', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')
five weeks
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deliberation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('induced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'674_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
four days Loral Sony Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'674_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel3', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'485_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('Loral_Fairchild_Corp.', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Victor_Co.', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('931_F.Supp._1014', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.N.Y.1996', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Victor_Co. Japan
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('54', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
54
__NEW_SENT__
('*1317', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Technology', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CCD', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
CCD
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('store', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('changing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('camcorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cameras', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('copiers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('facsimile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('imager', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('camcorder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('localizes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electrical_charges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('exposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('points', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pixels', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('packet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical_charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('picture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('intends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('record', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CCD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('collects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('changing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonconductive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('insulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electrodes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O')
CCD
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electrodes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('creates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('potential_well', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrode', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('packet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical_charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('representing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pixel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('potential_well', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alternately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electrodes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge_packets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('forced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O')
two one
__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('transporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge_packets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Backward', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge_packets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prevented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('implanted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('barriers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
