('537_F.3d_1349', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('LEGGETT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('PLATT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INCORPORATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Property', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Management', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
LEGGETT & PLATT INCORPORATED L & P Property Management Company Plaintiffs-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2007-1515', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._21,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._26,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('consisted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jetting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('freezing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('curing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('UV-curable', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('inks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deforming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')
UV-curable
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Missouri', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Catherine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2006_WL_3813677', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Missouri Catherine D. Perry J. 2006_WL_3813677
__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Prost Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('diodes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('LEDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cured', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('great_extent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nevertheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inherently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('LEDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ("''", '``', '', 'O') ('do', 'VB', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inapplicable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1350', 'UH', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roodman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bryan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('St.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Missouri', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David A. Roodman Bryan Cave St. Louis Missouri
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Marshall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
K. Lee Marshall
__NEW_SENT__
('Russell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Irvine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('California', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Russell B. Hill Howrey LLP Irvine California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rooklidge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stimson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alyson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
William C. Rooklidge Michael J. Stimson Alyson G. Barker
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PROST', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Leggett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Platt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Property', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Management', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('L', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VUTEk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('large-scale', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('printers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('9-10', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S._Patent_No._6755,518', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Leggett & Platt Inc. L & P Property Management Co. L & P '' Defendant-Appellee VUTEk Inc. 1-3 9-10 19 L & P 's
__NEW_SENT__
('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
¡¬518_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1 9 10 and 19 2 3 and 7 two
__NEW_SENT__
('Leggett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Platt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._4', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':05-CV-788', ':', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_3813677', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Miss', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Leggett & Platt Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Dec.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Summary_Judgment_Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Dec. 26 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Method', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Apparatus', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Ink', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Printing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rigid', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Panels', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('deformable_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('causing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('temporarily', 'RB', '', 'O')
Method and Apparatus for
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deformable_substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tendency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('bend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ripple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('warp', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('deform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('exposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infrared', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('IR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('print', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('ink-which', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('dried', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exposure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ultraviolet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('radiation-and', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1351', 'XX', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cold_UV', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('radiation_source', 'JJ', '', 'O')
¡¬518_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('emit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('non-UV', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('heat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('deform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cold_UV', 'JJS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('radiation_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deforming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('UV_curable_ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('deposited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cold_UV', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('radiation_source', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('freezes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('spreading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('wicking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('height', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('vary', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('maintaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink_jet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('printheads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Missouri', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('PressVu', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ('printers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
May 2005 L & P United_States_District_Court Missouri PressVu L & P 's ¡¬518_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
L & P 2 19
__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ink_jet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('UV_curable_ink', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink_jet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('printhead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tendency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', '', 'O') ('least', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('temporarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('deform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('printhead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('curing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printing_station', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printhead', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carriage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink_jet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('printhead', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thereon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printing_station', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('jetting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('cold_UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carriage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('moveable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printhead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('oriented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printing_station', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('close', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('jetted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('freeze', 'VB', '', 'O') ('dots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jetted_ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cold_UV', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('impinge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('UV', 'NN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('impinging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('heat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('temporarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printing_station', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.9', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.6-25', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('phrases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Markman April 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Leggett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Platt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vutek', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':05-CV-788', ':', '', 'O') ('2006_WL_1479537_(E.D.Miss._May_25,_2006)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Order', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Leggett & Platt Inc. Vutek Inc. 2006_WL_1479537_(E.D.Miss._May_25,_2006) `` Markman Order ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cold_UV', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('freeze', 'VB', '', 'O') ('dots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jetted_ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O')
Three 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cold_UV', 'JJS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ultraviolet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('employs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('selected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wavelengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('impinges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('**2-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*12', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Next', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('freeze', 'VB', '', 'O') ('dots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jetted_ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('spread', 'VB', '', 'O') ('wick', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*7', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*12', 'NFP', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('great_extent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('almost', 'RB', '', 'O') ('completely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('**7-8', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*12', 'NFP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
October 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('deemed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('moot', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Summary_Judgment_Order', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('23-24', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
23-24
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('9-10', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O')
1-3 7 9-10 19
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*1352', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1-2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1-2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6457,823', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬823_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬823_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6616,355', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬355_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
First first 1 9 10 and 19 2 3 and 7
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('5-18', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Alternatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reluctantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('deform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('deforming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('deformation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('meets', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('definiteness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C', 'NNP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
35 112
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('18-23', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('VUTEk', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
23
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('9-10', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬518_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1-3 7 9-10 19
__NEW_SENT__
('Leggett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Platt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vutek', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':05-CV-788', ':', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_2030134_(E.D.Miss._July_9,_2007)', '.', '', 'O')
Leggett & Platt Inc. Vutek Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('P', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
L & P
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
