('231_F.3d_1373', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SECOND', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('FAMILY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LIMITED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PARTNERSHIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TOSHIBA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Toshiba_America_Electronic_Components', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LI SECOND FAMILY LIMITED PARTNERSHIP Toshiba_America_Electronic_Components Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1451', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nov._8,_2000', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Jan._9,_2001', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('semiconductor_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('several_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Leonie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brinkema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Virginia Leonie M. Brinkema J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plager', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Plager Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1375', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rolf', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('O.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stadheim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stadheim', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Grear', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rolf O. Stadheim Stadheim & Grear Ltd. Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grear', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Joseph A. Grear
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Owen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stockbridge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('McLean', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Amy S. Owen McLean Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('Arthur', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Oblon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Spivak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McClelland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Maier', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Arthur I. Neustadt Oblon Maier & Neustadt P.C. Arlington Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Carl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schlier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Carl E. Schlier
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ronald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Yin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Everett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Limbach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Limbach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Ronald L. Yin Stephen M. Everett Limbach & Limbach L.L.P. San Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PLAGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Li', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Second', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Family', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Partnership', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Li', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Toshiba_America_Electronic_Components', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
The Li Second Family Limited Partnership Li 1 United_States_District_Court Virginia Toshiba Corporation Toshiba_America_Electronic_Components Inc. Toshiba
__NEW_SENT__
('Li', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('semiconductor_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Li', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4946,800', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Li Toshiba Li
__NEW_SENT__
('Among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Li', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Toshiba Li the United States Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Toshiba
__NEW_SENT__
('Li', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Second', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Family', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("P'ship", 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._97-306-', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('A', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Va', 'CD', '', 'O')
Li Second Family Ltd. Toshiba Corp. No._97-306-
__NEW_SENT__
('May_19,_1999', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('memorandum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Li', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4916,513', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O')
Li
__NEW_SENT__
('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Li', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('events', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Toshiba Li
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Serial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._05', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('/386,102', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'102", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('now-abandoned', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1971', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Serial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._05', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('/154,300', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'300", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1990 1973 continuation-in-part CIP 1971
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Serial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._05', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('/838,758', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1977', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'300", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
1990 1977 CIP
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'102", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('examiners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO-the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'102", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Examiner_Saba', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Examiner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Larkins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Examiner_Saba Examiner Larkins
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'300", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1968', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1971', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3585,714', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'714_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1965', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('*1376', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1969', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3430,109', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'109_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
CIP 1968 1971 CIP 1965 1969
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('isolation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('separate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('regions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('More', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('conductivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('P-type', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opposite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conductivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('N-type', 'NNPS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PN_junction', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('isolation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('groove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PN_junction', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('groove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('microns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PN_junction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('0.1', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('micron', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PN_junction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('groove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('curved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('groove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('rounding', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
two 0.1 0.1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('semiconductors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('groove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1.0', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('micron', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PN_junction', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('1.0', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('micron', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
16 1.0 micron PN_junction 1.0
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('0.1', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('micron', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 16 0.1 micron
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rounding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
8
__NEW_SENT__
('Prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'102", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('continued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1977', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Examiner_Saba', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outcome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'300", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
1973 February 10 1977 Examiner_Saba
__NEW_SENT__
('Prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'102", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('resume', 'VB', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1984
__NEW_SENT__
('Meanwhile', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suspension', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
