('485_F.3d_1157', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('LEAPFROG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ENTERPRISES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FISHER-PRICE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mattel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
LEAPFROG ENTERPRISES INC. FISHER-PRICE INC. Mattel Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._06-1402', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_9,_2007', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interactive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('learning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sleet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2006_WL_891001', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Gregory M. Sleet J. 2006_WL_891001
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('praise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('long-felt', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inadequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1158', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shulman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sonsini', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Goodrich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosati', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
*1158 Ron E. Shulman Wilson Sonsini Goodrich & Rosati of Palo Alto CA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Terry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kearney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berta', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Terry Kearney Michael A. Berta
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Galbraith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
James Galbraith Kenyon & Kenyon LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DeLucia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Flock', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hutchins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Richard L. DeLucia John Flock John R. Hutchins Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Butler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'DT', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Jeffrey M. Butler
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Enterprises', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('5,813,861', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬861_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fisher-Price', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mattel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Fisher-Price', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Leapfrog Enterprises Inc. Leapfrog the District of Delaware 25 Leapfrog 5,813,861 Fisher-Price Inc. Mattel Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fisher-Price', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('PowerTouch', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬861_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Leapfrog October 2003 PowerTouch 25
__NEW_SENT__
('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('add', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Mattel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('codefendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Leapfrog Mattel Inc. September 2004
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬861_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('learning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('help', 'VB', '', 'O') ('young', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('children', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ('phonetically', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
Claim 25
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interactive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('learning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound_production_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('depiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sequence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('letters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('associable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reader', 'NN', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('communicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('identity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('activates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('communicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('causing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound_production_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('generate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sequence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('letters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬861_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ll.23-36', '.', '', 'O')
10
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('April_7,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
25
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('choosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sequence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('letters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('coming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proximity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Enters.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fisher-Price', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._03-927', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del', 'NN', '', 'O')
Leapfrog Enters. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr._7,_2005', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Apr._7,_2005
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('PowerTouch_device', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hinged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('electronics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('speaker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('opens', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lie', 'VB', '', 'O') ('flat', 'JJ', '', 'O')
PowerTouch_device
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('opened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('book', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rectangular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recess', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('books', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('colorful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pictures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('show', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pictures', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('select', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('modes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('phonics_mode', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('touches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('page', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pronounces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pronounces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phoneme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sequence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pronounces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('crosspoints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('underneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('books', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('detect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('page', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'NN', '', 'O') ('touched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('programmed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('associate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1159', ':', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crosspoint', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('books', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('corresponds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crosspoint', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phonics_mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pronunciation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phonemes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('regardless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('touches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('programming', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('deadlocked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_27,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_30,_2006', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬861_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
March_30,_2006 25
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('PowerTouch_device', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('letters', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PowerTouch_device
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PowerTouch', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
PowerTouch 25
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,748,748', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bevan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Instruments', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Super', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Speak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Read', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('SSR', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fisher-Price', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Ronald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Milner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
25 3,748,748 Bevan SSR one Ronald Milner
__NEW_SENT__
('Leapfrog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Leapfrog
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
