('163_F.3d_1342', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LAITRAM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEC_Information_Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Plaintiff-Appellee NEC CORPORATION NEC_Information_Systems Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1060', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._18,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electro-optical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('printer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alphanumeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('photosensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('medium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Louisiana', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Edith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clement', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1994_WL_261966', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Louisiana Edith Brown Clement JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('62_F.3d_1388', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
The Court of Appeals 62_F.3d_1388
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1995_WL_758904', 'CD', '', 'O')
District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('115_F.3d_947', 'CD', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unaddressed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim_identicality', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1997_WL_539890', 'CD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('original_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O')
JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('scope', 'VB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('type_quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1344', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Phillip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wittmann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stone', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pigman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Walther', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wittmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hutchinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Orleans', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Louisiana', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Phillip A. Wittmann Wittmann & Hutchinson L.L.P. New Orleans
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Usdin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephanie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shuler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Steven W. Usdin Stephanie D. Shuler
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sharon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hwang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Held', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Timothy J. Malloy Sharon A. Hwang McAndrews Held & Malloy Ltd. Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hopgood', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kalil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judlowe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John M. Calimafde Hopgood Calimafde Kalil & Judlowe New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marvin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gordon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Marvin N. Gordon
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEC_Information_Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Louisiana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Matter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,952,311', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', '', 'O')
NEC Corporation NEC_Information_Systems Inc. NEC Louisiana JMOL 1_and_2 Laitram U.S. 3,952,311
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Civ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Laitram Corp. NEC Corp. Civ
__NEW_SENT__
('A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._89-1571-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('N', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1997_WL_539890', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.La', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
E.D.La
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Sept. 2 1997
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('changed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Invention', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'311_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('electro-optical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('printing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('employing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation-sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('image-recording', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mediums', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('records', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('graphic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Laitram
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'311_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._5-9', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fashion', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('changed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'311_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('emphasized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deletions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brackets', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electro-optical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('printing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('photosensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recording_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation_emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wavelengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('radiation_emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('activating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('activated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('recorded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alipha', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-numeric', ':', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('irradiate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_areas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('irradiated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('print', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electro-optically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('photosensitive_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('arranging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation_emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1345', 'UH', '', 'O') ('array', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wavelengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('photosensitive_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('energizing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('transmitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('relative_movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coordinate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('energized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relative_movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alpha-numeric_character_images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('recorded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exposure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ares', 'NNS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('synchronously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('generating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('programs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('determines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('duration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('employing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('signals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('effect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('record', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alpha-numeric_character_images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('type_quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'NN', '', 'O')
first second first second
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'311_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certificate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._22-67', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._1-19', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bracketing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('paragraphing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('address', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('type_quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim_identicality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type_quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alone', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
