('78_F.3d_540', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('LAMB-WESTON', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('INC.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('McCAIN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('FOODS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Foods', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
LAMB-WESTON McCAIN FOODS LTD. McCain Foods Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._93-1536', 'NN', '', 'O') ('94-1225', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Feb._29,_1996', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Food', 'NN', '', 'O') ('processor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trademark_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unfair_competition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('trademark_dilution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('lattice-shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('waffle-cut', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('potato_product', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McDonald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('818_F.Supp._1376', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Alan A. McDonald J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('lattice-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('french_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('unnecessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*541', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Yakima', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('McDonald', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
U.S. District Court Washington Yakima
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rohde', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bogle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gates', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Seattle', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert E. Rohde Bogle & Gates Seattle Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Al', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Van', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kampen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ramsey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Al-Salam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Al Van Ramsey M. Al-Salam
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Karen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McGaffey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Karen M. McGaffey
__NEW_SENT__
('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Unikel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Seyfarth', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Shaw', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fairweather', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Geraldson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Alan L. Unikel Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PAULINE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
RADER Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('PER_CURIAM', 'RP', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pauline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Circuit Pauline Newman
__NEW_SENT__
('PER_CURIAM', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S._Patent_No._4937,084', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Washington Lamb-Weston Inc. 's
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('renders', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vacates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('food', 'NN', '', 'O') ('processing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('frozen_potato_products', '.', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Foods', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('compete', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frozen_potato_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O')
McCain Foods McCain Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('make', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('frozen_potato_products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston McCain
__NEW_SENT__
('Fierce', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('competition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frozen_potato_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spurs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('centers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('lattice-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('french_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('*542', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1979', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Matsler', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('confidentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('waffle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slicing_apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', '', 'O')
October 1979
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Mr._Matsler', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('slicing_apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('98', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('waffle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unusable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
January 1980 98 %
__NEW_SENT__
('Nevertheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('negotiations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Matsler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('license', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston Mr._Matsler
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contracting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mr._Matsler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('licensed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('J.R.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Simplot', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Lamb-Weston Mr._Matsler Lamb-Weston J.R. Simplot Company
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1979', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Mr._Matsler', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('cutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('J.R.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Simplot', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 1979 J.R. Simplot
__NEW_SENT__
('Mr._Matsler', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('fried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('potato_slices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distributed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('customers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('local', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Dairy', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('Queen', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('Restaurant', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Oregon', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Dairy Queen Restaurant Dallas Oregon
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('received', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Jayne', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('offering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('confidentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('waffle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O')
February 1980 Lamb-Weston Mr._Jayne
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('evaluated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mr._Jayne', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('unacceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
March 1980 Lamb-Weston Mr._Jayne
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('terminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('communications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Jayne', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('starting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('waffle-style', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adapting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('started', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('testing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trademark', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CrissCut', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston 1980 late 1983 CrissCut
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('waffle-cut', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slicing_apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 1983 Lamb-Weston the United States Patent Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Serial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._06', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('/525,115', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'115", 'CD', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('encompassed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
more than one
__NEW_SENT__
('37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('C.F.R.¡±', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1.141', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
37 1995
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('elected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('proceed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('solely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4523,503', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'503_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('separated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'115", 'CD', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('divisional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Serial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._06', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('/682,366', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'366", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Canada', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._898057', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Starke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._678514', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Regnier', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._2612,453', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Stahmer', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._2767,752', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Stahmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._1937,049', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Toland', 'VB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('et', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('al', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Canada Patent No._898057 Starke U.S. Patent No._678514 Stahmer II Toland et al
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3139,130', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Urschel', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._1506,166', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Boon', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Boon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cooked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('french_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('waffle-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('slicing_apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('freeze', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('waffle-cut', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boon', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('suggests', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
one Boon
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('escape', 'VB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'366", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('emphasized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('waffle-cut', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potato_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('inch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4/BIG_TOKEN__16_to_10__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('/16', 'CD', '', 'O') ('inch', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('Despite', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'366", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('23', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
January 23 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('PTO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Interferences', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston the PTO Board of Patent Appeals Interferences ( Board
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1990 Board
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'366", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slice', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_through_4', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('read', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('potato_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconstitution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cooking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sliced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ellipsoidal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('peak', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('peak', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4/BIG_TOKEN__16_to_10__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('/16', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('inch', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_sides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('longitudinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ridges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('therebetween', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ridges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('angularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ridges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depth', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('intersect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('openings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('*543', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconstitution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oil_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('6-20', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solids_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('32-40', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconstitution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cooking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('very', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crisp', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('locally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flavor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('openings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thick', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intersecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ridges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mealy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('texture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('strong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flavor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thick-cut', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('french', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('potato_strips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intermediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whose', 'WP$', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('french_fried_shoe_string_potato_strips', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first first second first about 6-20 % about 32-40 %
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oil_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('16-20', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solids_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('55-65', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reconstitution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('350¢X_F', 'CD', 'GPE', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('360¢X_F', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('135-BIG_TOKEN__165_seconds._3__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O')
1 about 16-20 % about 55-65 % 350¢X_F 360¢X_F
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oil_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('16-20', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solids_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('55-65', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconstitution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thickest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('akin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thick-cut', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('french', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('potato_strips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thinnest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('akin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potato_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('akin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('french_fried_shoe_string_potato_strips', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1 about 16-20 % about 55-65 %
__NEW_SENT__
('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('peak-to-peak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('7/16', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('inch', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I')
1 about 7/16 inch
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1985 McCain
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trademark_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unfair_competition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('trademark_dilution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston McCain
__NEW_SENT__
('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laws', 'NNS', '', 'O')
McCain
__NEW_SENT__
('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('withdrew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
McCain
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trademark', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unfair_competition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('McCain', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O')
McCain
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('waffle-cut', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('potato_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1900s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
Lamb-Weston the early 1900s
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('restaurants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('CrissCut', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston CrissCut
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('early', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1935_and_1936', 'CD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Gem', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cafe', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Plainsville', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('served', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('staple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('item', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plainsville Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1979', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'FAC', 'B') ('Plaza', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('Restaurant', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Quincy', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('waffle_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1979 the Plaza Restaurant Quincy Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('General', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Slicing/Red', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Goat', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Disposers', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('electric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('slicing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('slicing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('5/16', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('inch', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('thick', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('waffle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slices', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1981 Goat Disposers 5/16 inch
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('examined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3397,993', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Strong_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 103 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Strong_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parfry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('potato_slices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('steam-blanched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('air-dried', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'VBN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('processing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Strong_patent', 'JJ', 'LOC', 'B') ('parfry', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prepare', 'VB', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('french_fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reconstituted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('textural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston Strong_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('familiar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('waffle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('waffle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1930s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Strong_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('waffle-cut', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O')
the 1930s
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Matsler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jayne_devices', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Matsler Jayne_devices
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Matsler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jayne_devices', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('parfried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('frozen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potato', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Strong_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Matsler
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lamb-Weston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'084_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
('Lamb-Weston', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lamb-Weston
__NEW_SENT__
