('401_F.3d_1313', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MEDRAD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MRI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DEVICES', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VBP', '', 'O')
MEDRAD
__NEW_SENT__
('No._04-1134', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('March_16,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('April_11,_2005', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radio_frequency_coils', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('magnetic_resonance_imaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('MRI', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Western_District', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Terrence', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('F.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('McVerry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the Western_District of Pennsylvania Terrence F. McVerry J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1314', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McGough', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pittsburgh', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
W. Thomas McGough Reed Smith LLP Pittsburgh Pennsylvania
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Frederick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Colen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Kirsten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rydstrom', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kucler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Frederick H. Colen Kirsten R. Rydstrom Robert D. Kucler
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bradley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Medrad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Indianola', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Gregory L. Bradley Medrad Inc. Indianola Pennsylvania
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hurst', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Winston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Strawn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
James F. Hurst Winston & Strawn LLP Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Derek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sarafa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pollack', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Derek J. Sarafa Brian R. Pollack
__NEW_SENT__
('*1315', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('FRIEDMAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Medrad', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._02-2044', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MRI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Devices', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('MRIDC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Medrad', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._6396,273', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'273_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Medrad Inc. United_States_District_Court Pennsylvania No._02-2044 MRI Devices Corp. Medrad U.S. Patent No._6396,273
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('636', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 636 1
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recommended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MRIDC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Medrad', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O')
MRIDC Medrad
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magistrate_judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('recommendation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radio_frequency_coils', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('RF_coils', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('magnetic_resonance_imaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('MRI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
RF_coils
__NEW_SENT__
('MRI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('nuclear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magnetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resonance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anatomy', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Stark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bradley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Magnetic_Resonance_Imaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('1-14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ed.1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
David D. Stark & William G. Bradley Jr.
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MRI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extremely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('strong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('causes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('align', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equilibrium', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NN', '', 'O') ('creates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('net_magnetization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('time-varying', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('orthogonal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pulses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RF_coils', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('surround', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drags', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('net_magnetization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_magnetic_field', 'NNP', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('laws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('quantum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('affected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('net_magnetization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('precess', 'VB', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_magnetic_field', '-RRB-', 'ORG', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Larmor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dephasing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('realigning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_magnetic_field', 'NNP', '', 'O')
main_magnetic_field Larmor
__NEW_SENT__
('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haacke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Magnetic_Resonance_Imaging', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Physical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Principles', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sequence', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Design', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('5-8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1999', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
E. Mark Haacke 1999
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('precession', 'NN', '', 'O') ('induces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('RF_coils', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('measured', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reconstruct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tissues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('RF_coils', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('detected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('much', 'RB', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('signal-to-noise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ratio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'NN', '', 'O') ('RF_coils', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('phased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('precessing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('advantageous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coils', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time-varying', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('precessing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reception', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pulses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('passed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('coils', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('result', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magnetic_field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('roughly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('twice', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('outside', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlap', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Misic', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'273_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('solve', 'VB', '', 'O')
George J. Misic
__NEW_SENT__
