('395_F.3d_1364', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MERCK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TEVA', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
MERCK & CO. TEVA PHARMACEUTICALS USA INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._04-1005', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Jan._28,_2005', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Farnan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('288_F.Supp.2d_601', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware J. Farnan Jr. J. 288_F.Supp.2d_601
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gajarsa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Gajarsa Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('70/35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alendronate_monosodium_trihydrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
70/35
__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rader', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dissented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1365', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lynch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howrey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Simon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
John F. Lynch Howrey Simon Arnold & White LLP Houston Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nicolas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barzoukas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Nicolas G. Barzoukas Richard L. Stanley
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Matukaitis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gerard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Devlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rahway', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Paul D. Matukaitis Edward W. Murray Gerard M. Devlin Merck & Co. Inc. Rahway New Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Galbraith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
James Galbraith Kenyon & Kenyon New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Maria', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Luisa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palmese', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Maria Luisa Palmese William G. James II
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('GAJARSA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Teva', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._5994,329', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nov._30,_1999', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('*1366', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Teva Pharmaceuticals USA Inc. Teva United_States_District_Court Delaware Merck & Co. 's Merck U.S. Nov._30,_1999
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('23_and_37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('constructively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I')
23_and_37 Teva Abbreviated New Drug Application 35 271 2 the Hatch-Waxman Act
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharms', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Merck & Co. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('288_F.Supp.2d_601', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharms', 'NNS', '', 'O')
USA Inc. Merck Merck & Co. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._01-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CV-0048', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del', 'NN', '', 'O')
USA Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept._24,_2003', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Final_Judgment_Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sept._24,_2003
__NEW_SENT__
('54', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Final_Judgment_Order', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')1', '.', '', 'O')
54
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('disagree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('23_and_37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
23_and_37
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('23_and_37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
23_and_37
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A.', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'329_Patent", 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Method', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Inhibiting', 'VBG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Bone', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Resorption', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('preventing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less-than-daily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Method for Inhibiting Bone Resorption ''
__NEW_SENT__
("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._15-25', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allege', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_22,_1997', 'VB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 14 1998 Merck July_22,_1997
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('288', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('606', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Merck 288 F.Supp.2d 606
__NEW_SENT__
('Bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('family', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('destruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contributes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('diseases', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._45-50', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alendronate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tiludronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pamidronate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ibandronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('zolendronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('etidronate', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at_col._1,_ll._54-65', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._28-31', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('once-weekly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alendronate_monosodium_trihydrate', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('readily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('absorbed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('tract', 'NN', '', 'O')
GI
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('rigorous_dosing_instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('take', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medicine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('empty', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('upright', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fasting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thirty', 'CD', 'TIME', 'B') ('minutes', 'NNS', 'TIME', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingestion', 'NN', '', 'O')
thirty minutes
__NEW_SENT__
("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._3-24', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('physicians', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('believed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('irritation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('esophagus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O')
GI
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._23-46', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('treatments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('consisted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('daily', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('doses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('complications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
daily GI
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at_col._1,_ll._54-61', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._34-35', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('44-46', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('side-effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('repetitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('irritation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('GI', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('tract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concern', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O')
GI GI
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('col._2,_ll._65-67', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._3,_l._57-', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._4,_l._13', 'RB', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('trumpeted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduced-frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('schedule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decreasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('irritating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compliance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigorous_dosing_instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('col._3,_ll._57-64', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._4,_ll._14-23', '.', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('23_and_37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
23_and_37
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cast', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('text', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('incorporating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
23
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('human_comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('70', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alendronate_monosodium_trihydrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alendronic_acid_basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unit_dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous_schedule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosing_interval', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once-weekly', 'JJ', '', 'O')
about 70 dosing_interval
__NEW_SENT__
('*1367', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
37
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preventing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('human_comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('35', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('mg', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alendronate_monosodium_trihydrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alendronic_acid_basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unit_dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous_schedule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosing_interval', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once-weekly', 'JJ', '', 'O')
about 35 mg dosing_interval
__NEW_SENT__
("'329_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._21,_ll._24-27', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._22,_ll._24-26', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
col._21,_ll._24-27 23 37
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('note', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('differences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alendronate_monosodium_trihydrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('70', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('preventing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O')
23 37 1 70 35 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('once-weekly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('diminished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('daily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alendronate_monosodium_trihydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Fosamax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Merck Food and Drug Administration FDA Fosamax
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('288', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('605', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Merck 288 605
__NEW_SENT__
