('198_F.3d_1363', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MARQUIP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FOSBER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_SpA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
MARQUIP Fosber_SpA Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('United_Container_Machinery', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._99-1025', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('99-1120', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._6,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Jan._27,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improvements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('handling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stacking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrugated_paperboard_sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shabaz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('30_F.Supp.2d_1142', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court John C. Shabaz
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('orders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1364', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Russell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Barron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lardner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Russell J. Barron Foley & Lardner Wisconsin
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Joan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eads', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lardner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David J. Harth Joan L. Eads Foley Lardner Madison Wisconsin
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Allen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arntsen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lardner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Madison', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Costakos', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lardner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Allen A. Arntsen Foley & Lardner Wisconsin Jeffrey N. Costakos Foley Lardner Milwaukee
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('De', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bruin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Best', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Friedrich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_SpA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
David L. De Bruin Michael Best & Friedrich LLP Milwaukee Wisconsin Fosber_America Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ahrens', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Toni', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bonney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carraway', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gary A. Ahrens Toni L. Bonney J. Christopher Carraway
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nathan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('United_Container_Machinery', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gantt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Catherine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Nyarady', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John E. Nathan Fish & Neave New_York New_York Daniel M. Gantt Catherine Nyarady
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hovel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kravit', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gass', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hovel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Leitner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O')
John F. Hovel Kravit Gass S.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fosber_SpA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_Container_Machinery', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4200,276', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'276_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wisconsin
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._96-_C-726-S', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis', 'NNP', '', 'O')
See Marquip Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept.14', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1998
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Marquip Inc. 's
__NEW_SENT__
('60', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
60
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('30_F.Supp.2d_1142', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis', 'NN', '', 'O')
See Marquip Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('1998', 'LS', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('60', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Rule 60
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'276_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shingling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stacking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('corrugated_paperboard_sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interrupting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corrugator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('runs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('continuously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('remove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('stacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interrupting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corrugator', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('stack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interrupting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corrugator', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('9_and_13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1365', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('changing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
only two 9
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conveying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('succession', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-line_conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical_stack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('traveling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('shingling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('pass', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shingled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stacking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shingled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('slowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-line_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('individually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('seccessively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstream_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('passage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('past', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respective_separate_conveyor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('slow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('traveling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upstream', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
13
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conveying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('succession', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-line_conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical_stack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('traveling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shingling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('pass', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shingled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stacking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shingled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('slowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-line_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('individually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('successively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstream_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('passage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('past', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respective_separate_conveyor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('slow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('traveling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upstream', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'276_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._7,_ll._22-39', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('col._8,_ll._31-47', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Marquip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('asserts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NN', 'FAC', 'B') ('infringe', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('9_and_13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'276_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
1 2 3 and 4 Fosber_device
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Fosber_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('shingling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('nip', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('continuously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shingles', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('overlaps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Version 2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shingled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('moves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Fosber_device first
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('grasps', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('moves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('past', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pinch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('grabs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stops', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('creates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('starts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('succeeding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('grasps', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next_group', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('events', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VBP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('downstream', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('carrying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('down', 'RP', '', 'O')
first two 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leaves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pace', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('releases', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('succeeding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fourth_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fourth_conveyor', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('slows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('downstacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discharges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('room', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stack', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Fosber', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('differs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism-namely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('midway', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Version 2
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('closes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('moves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('exactly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('speeding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('widen', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*1366', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gap', 'NN', '', 'O')
Version 1 Version 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('replace', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('always', 'RB', '', 'O') ('run', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_speed', 'NN', '', 'O')
Version 1 two
__NEW_SENT__
('Version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('replace', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_conveyor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('always', 'RB', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_speed', 'NN', '', 'O')
Version 2 two
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('suffices', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('discuss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Version', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('varying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('speeds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Version 2
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'276_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4273,325', '.', '', 'O')
two Marquip
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Fosber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Fosber two
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._96-_C-726-S', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis', 'NNP', '', 'O')
See Marquip Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('June_10,_1997', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Fosber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'276_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Marquip Fosber
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('155_F.3d_567', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1998_WL_314628', 'CD', '', 'O') ('No._97-1441', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
See Marquip Inc. Fosber_America Inc. 155_F.3d_567 No._97-1441 Marquip II
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accumulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._96-_C-726-S', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis', 'NNP', '', 'O')
See Marquip Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept.14', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Marquip_III', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1998 Marquip_III
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('critical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marquip_III', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('element', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('9_and_13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marquip_III
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('performs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('slowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conveyors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obtains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decreasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('traveling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upstream', 'RB', '', 'O')
Fosber_device
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
10
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('performs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fundamentally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('different_way', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Fosber_device
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('functional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interrupt_mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('change', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('timing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('operate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('different_way', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Fosber_device
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
13
__NEW_SENT__
('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Marquip
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('refusal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('set', 'VB', '', 'O') ('aside', 'RP', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Marquip
__NEW_SENT__
('60', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
60
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fosber_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._96-_C-726-S', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Wis', 'NNP', '', 'O')
See Marquip Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Dec.8', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1998 Marquip IV
__NEW_SENT__
('Marquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fosber_device', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('withheld', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fosber', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marquip Fosber_device
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consolidates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('addresses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('60', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
two Rule 60
__NEW_SENT__
