('874_F.3d_724', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MERCK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SHARP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('DOHME', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORP.', 'VBP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
MERCK SHARP & DOHME CORP.
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HOSPIRA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2017-1115', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2017', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
October 26 2017
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ertapenem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibiotic_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (':14-cv-00915-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:14-cv-00916-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Andrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2016_WL_5872620', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
the District of Delaware Nos._1 Richard G. Andrews J. 2016_WL_5872620
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('*725', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-00915-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:14-cv-00916-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Andrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Richard G. Andrews
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*726', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jessica', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ellsworth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hogan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lovells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('US', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jessica Lynn Ellsworth US LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Catherine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Emily', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stetson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eng', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Valentine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pezzano', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dougherty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nitya', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Anand', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Gerard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Devlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alysia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('A.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Raynard', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Yuro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rahway', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Catherine Emily Stetson Joseph D. Eng Tony Valentine Michael P. Dougherty Nitya Anand New_York NY Gerard M. Devlin Jr. Yuro Merck &
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Meloro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Willkie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Farr', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gallagher', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomas J. Meloro Willkie Farr & Gallagher LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hughes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Newman Lourie Hughes
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lourie', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Merck_Sharp', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dohme_Corp.', 'PRP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('21-34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6,486,150', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Merck_Sharp & Dohme_Corp. Merck the District of Delaware 21-34 6,486,150 35 103 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Merck_Sharp', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dohme_Corp.', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
Merck_Sharp & Dohme_Corp. Hospira Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('CV', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('14-915-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2016_WL_5872620', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*21', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Del', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
D. Del
__NEW_SENT__
('July_10,_2016', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Decision', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ertapenem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibiotic_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('Ertapenem', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('unstable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reactions-hydrolysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lactam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nitrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('highlighted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('red', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circle', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dimerization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('via', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyrrolidine_nitrogen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('highlighted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blue', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('square', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ertapenem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stabilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dimerization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyrrolidine_nitrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dioxide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('carbon_dioxide_adduct', '.', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibiotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('purportedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('minimizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dimerization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hydrolysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pathways', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Br', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('12-14', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 21 21
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_formulation_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Ia', 'VB', '', 'O') ('*727', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hydrates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('R4', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('R5', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R6', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C1-C6', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-alkyl', ':', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alkali-metal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alkali_earth-metal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkali-metal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alkali_earth-metal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lithium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cesium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rubidium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('calcium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('magnesium', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbon_dioxide_source', '$', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('12.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction_vessel', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mole', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ratio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction_vessel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbon_dioxide_source', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('maintain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature_range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('-3¢X_C.', ',', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('15¢X_C.', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('lyophilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Step', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('yield', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_formulation_product', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Ia', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 about 6.0 about 12.0 2 about 6.0 about 9.0 about 15¢X_C. 3 Step 2 about 10 %
__NEW_SENT__
("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('18_ll._11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('-43', '.', '', 'O')
18_ll._11
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_29,_2014', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('notified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('InvanzTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('principal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbon_dioxide_adduct', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ertapenem', 'NN', '', 'O')
May_29,_2014 Hospira Inc. Hospira Merck Merck carbon_dioxide_adduct
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents-the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5,952,323', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'323_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Merck Hospira two 5,952,323
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'323_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'323_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PCT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('WO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('98/18800', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Almarsson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
PCT Almarsson
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2016_WL_5872620', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*11', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('*16', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*21', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('individually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('recipe', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('leading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nothing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('routine_experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O')
three 21 three
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*17-20', '.', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbon_dioxide_adduct', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('pH-dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hydroxide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('adjust', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbon_dioxide_adduct', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lyophilization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
about 6.0 about 9.0
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*16-17', '.', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('temperature_range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('explicitly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('understood', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('minimized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('temperatures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('wanted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('keep', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('freezing', 'VBG', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*18', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*728', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entirely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rebutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('narrower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('routine_experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Merck 21 Hospira
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*21', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reviewed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('objective_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('copying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objective_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('strong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Merck Hospira
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('weak', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ened', 'VBD', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('blocking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5,478,820', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'820_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-directed', ':', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ertapenem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself-of', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O')
5,478,820 Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('aside', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zeneca', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('incentive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('develop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ertapenem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fear', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'820_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Zeneca Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*9', 'FW', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('copying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('tried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('alternative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('attempt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('copying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'150_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Hospira five
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*10', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('copy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'is", 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('indicium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hospira', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Hospira Merck Hospira
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*10', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*21', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Diversitech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Century', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Steps', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('850_F.2d_675', 'CD', '', 'O') ('679', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Diversitech Corp. Century Steps Inc. 679 Fed
__NEW_SENT__
('Cir', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Wyers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Master', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('616_F.3d_1231', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1246', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
1988 Wyers Master Lock Co. 616_F.3d_1231 1246 Fed
__NEW_SENT__
('Cir', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2010
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
