('190_F.3d_1300', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MITSUBISHI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ELECTRIC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AMPEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Cross-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._97-1502', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('97-1538', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._30,_1999', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Aug._30,_1999
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('En', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Banc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Declined', 'VBD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nov._1,_1999', 'RB', 'ORG', 'I')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing En Banc Declined Nov._1,_1999
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rafeedie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury_verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California Edward Rafeedie J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('preserve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('objection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2 first 3 second
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1301', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Wayne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wayne M. Smith Graham & James LLP California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Les', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weinstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vincent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Belusko', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Les J. Weinstein Vincent J. Belusko
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morgan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cross-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert C. Morgan Fish & Neave New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Norman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Beamer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Marta', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gross', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.B', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Norman H. Beamer E. Gross Kevin
__NEW_SENT__
('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kurtis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MacFerrin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Johnson Kurtis D. MacFerrin
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hentschel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Porter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Craig N. Hentschel Arnold & Porter California
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SKELTON', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._4336,612', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._4665,533', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'533_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')1', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'533_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Electric Corporation United_States_District_Court California Mitsubishi 1
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('requests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Ampex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'533_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Ampex
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('post-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_PATENT", 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Error', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Correction', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Encoding', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Decoding', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('*1302', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_22,_1982', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('correcting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('errors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reproduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O')
`` Error Correction Encoding and Decoding System ''
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('digital', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('music', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('magnetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('errors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dust', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dust', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('strings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('binary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('burst', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('transmitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recorded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('encoded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('errors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('corrected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('accurate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('divided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-dimensional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rectangular_array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('k1_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('horizontal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('k2', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correcting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('add', 'VB', '', 'O') ('check', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correcting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correcting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('horizontal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('directions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'612_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('encoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('decoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rectangular_array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('k1_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('k2', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('orthogonal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('encoding_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('encoding', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adapting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('codes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('C2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dividing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('k1_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('b_bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('apiece', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('k2_X', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') ('bit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rectangular_arrays', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('b_bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('k2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('C2_encoder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('k2_X', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('b', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rectangular_arrays', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('n2', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('X', 'NN', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rectangular_arrays', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('b_bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('n2_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('C1_encoder', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('k1_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('n1_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('n1-k1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('check', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('k1_bits', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('timing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('timing_signals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('controlling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('encoding_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('encode', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('codeword', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generalized_product_code', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('n1_bits', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('n2_bits', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('decoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('operatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('connected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('encoding_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transmission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decoding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('encoded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('encoding_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('C1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('C2_encoders', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('operative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('encode', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('timing_signals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('timing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('C1_encoder', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('C2_encoder', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('generalized_product_code', '.', '', 'O')
n1_bits C2_encoders
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('adds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('information_matrix-forming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arranging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rectangular_array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('information_matrix-forming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('RAM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Claim 2 3 RAM
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('adds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erasure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('calculation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erasure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('calculation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explanation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('much', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discussion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('technological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('significance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('expert_witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Experts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('testified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1303', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('indeed', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('complex', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('competence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('admissibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Kumho', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tire', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Carmichael', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('526_U.S._137', 'CD', '', 'O') ('119_S.Ct._1167', 'CD', '', 'O') ('143_L.Ed.2d_238_(1999)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('expressed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('drawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert_witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kumho Tire Co. Carmichael 143_L.Ed.2d_238_(1999)
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reviewing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Al-Site', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('VSI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Int', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('l', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('174_F.3d_1308', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1314', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('50_U.S.P.Q.2d_1161', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1164', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interpreting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instructed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Shatterproof', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Glass', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Libbey-Owens', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('758_F.2d_613', 'CD', '', 'O') ('626', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('225_U.S.P.Q._634', 'CD', '', 'O') ('643', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1985', 'ADD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reviewing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('whole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('misled', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Al-Site Corp. VSI Int 1314 1164 Shatterproof Glass Corp. Libbey-Owens Ford Co. 626 643
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
