('190_F.3d_1335', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MERCK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MYLAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
MERCK & CO. MYLAN PHARMACEUTICALS INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1044', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B')
No._99-1044
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Sept._3,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Parkinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('disease', 'NN', '', 'O')
two Parkinson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Eduardo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robreno', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('19_F.Supp.2d_334', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('elect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('species', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polymers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history_estoppel', 'NNP', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1336', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Mary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nichols', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Arsht', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Tunnel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mary G. Graham Morris Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sutton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Maryellen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Noreika', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard L. Sutton Maryellen Noreika
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Matukaitis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('McGough', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Merk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rahway', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Paul D. Matukaitis Kevin J. McGough Merk & New Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wallace', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fielding', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
James H. Wallace Jr. Wiley Rein & Fielding Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('*1337', 'VB', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lyons', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Skalaban', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Holbrook', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gregory R. Lyons Peter J. Skalaban Jr. Timothy R. Holbrook
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN LOURIE CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patents', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nos._4832,957', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'957_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,900,755', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'755_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Merck & United_States_District_Court Mylan Pharmaceuticals Inc. Merck United States Patents 4,900,755
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'957", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'755_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Parkinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('disease', 'NN', '', 'O')
Parkinson
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('release_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side_effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('wearing-off', 'UH', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('on-off', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('phenomena', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ameliorates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side_effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('polymeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vehicles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('implement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('achieved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('delivering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'957_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broadest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polymers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('5-25', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydroxypropyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cellulose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2-50', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polyvinyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acetate-crotonic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PVACA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Merck 1 HPC PVACA 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release_oral_dosage_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uniform_dispersion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('25-100', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('100_to_400', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1-10', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('tablet', 'JJ', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('lubricant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5-25', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water-soluble_hydroxypropyl', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cellulose', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2-50', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('less_water-soluble_polyvinyl_acetate-crotonic_acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PVACA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('copolymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'IN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('released', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('slowly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O')
25-100 100_to_400 1-10 mg of a tablet HPC
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('acronyms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'755_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('division', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'957_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controlled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('release_oral_dosage_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('uniform_dispersion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('25-100', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('100_to_400', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5-25', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water-soluble_hydroxypropyl', '``', '', 'O') ('cellulose', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2-50', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('less_water-soluble_polyvinyl_acetate-crotonic_acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PVACA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('copolymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'IN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('released', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('slowly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O')
25-100 100_to_400 HPC
__NEW_SENT__
('Mylan', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('50', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbidopa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('200', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mg', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('levodopa', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('29.3', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mg', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water-soluble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('12.8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydroxypropyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methylcellulose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HPMC', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Mylan Abbreviated New Drug Application the Food and Drug Administration 50 200 mg 29.3 mg HPC 12.8
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1338', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'957", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'755_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Merck 35 2 2 Mylan 1-3 Mylan
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('asserts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('29.3', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('12.8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HPMC', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('polymer_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5-25', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2-50', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PVACA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Merck Mylan 29.3 mg HPC 12.8 Merck HPC PVACA
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('insubstantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('HPMC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PVACA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('interchangeable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('less_water-soluble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Merck HPMC PVACA HPC
__NEW_SENT__
('Mylan', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('histories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'957", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'755_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('prevented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mylan Merck Mylan Mylan
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history_estoppel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('preclude', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalency', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('de', 'FW', '', 'O') ('novo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correctness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('EMI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('North', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Intel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('157_F.3d_887', 'CD', '', 'O') ('891', 'CD', '', 'O') ('48_USPQ2d_1181', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1184', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Loctite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ultraseal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('781_F.2d_861', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('870', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('228_USPQ_90', 'CD', '', 'O') ('96', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1985', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
EMI Group North America Inc. Intel Corp. Loctite Corp. Ultraseal Ltd. 870 96
__NEW_SENT__
