('874_F.2d_804', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MERCK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BIOCRAFT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
MERCK & CO. BIOCRAFT LABORATORIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._88-1513', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('May_10,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_7,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Suggestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('July_3,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nicholas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Politan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('690_F.Supp._1376', 'CD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nicholas H. Politan J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Mayer Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bissell', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('dissented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('grant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bissell Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*805', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Joseph M. Fitzpatrick New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nicholas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cannella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Alaburda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Nicholas M. Cannella Lawrence Alaburda
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Francis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shanley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fisher', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Morristown', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('N.J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
John J. Francis Jr. Shanley & P.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Henderson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Farabow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Garrett', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dunner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Donald R. Dunner D.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bajefsky', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Carol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Einaudi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert D. Bajefsky Carol P. Einaudi
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beryl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Snyder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Biocraft_Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Elmwood', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('Park', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('N.J.', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Beryl L. Snyder Elmwood Park N.J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BISSELL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BENNETT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('OPINION', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MAYER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Biocraft_Laboratories', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3781,430', '.', '', 'O')
Merck & Co. Inc. Biocraft_Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Biocraft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Biocraft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('diuretic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey Biocraft Biocraft
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Biocraft_Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('690_F.Supp._1376', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.N.J.1988', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Merck & Co. Inc. Biocraft_Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Biocraft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('combinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Biocraft 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'430_Patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3781,430', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'430_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Diuretic', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Formulations', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Merck `` Diuretic Formulations ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Inducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('diuresis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('urine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excretion', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('saluresis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('electrolyte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excretion', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diuretics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cardiovascular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('renal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diseases', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('therapeutic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diuretics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('often', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lifesaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cause', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hypokalemia', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('excessive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('excretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potassium_ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('condition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manifested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('severe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('weakness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('physical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('exhaustion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'430_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('amiloride_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('amiloride', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conserving', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('diuretic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('induces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excretion', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrochlorothiazide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excreting', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('diuretic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('induces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excretion', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objective', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('co-administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potassium_ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('eliminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('eliminated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('co-administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('medically..', 'UH', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('synergistic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('therapeutic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('accomplishment', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('eliminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('forecast', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('natriuretic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excreting', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
medically..
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'430_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
six
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stand', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fall', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_3', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 2 2_and_3 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amiloride_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('*806', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('hydrochlorothiazide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ratio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amiloride_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrochlorothiazide', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') (':', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('1_to_1', 'CD', '', 'O') (':10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O')
about 1
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('amiloride_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hydrochlorothiazide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ratio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1_to_1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('0', 'CD', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amiloride_hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('50', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrochlorothiazide', 'NN', '', 'O')
5 50
__NEW_SENT__
