('747_F.3d_1326', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INNOVATIONS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HUNTER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MFG.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
MRC INNOVATIONS INC. HUNTER
__NEW_SENT__
('CDI_International', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._2013-1433', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('April_2,_2014', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ornamental_design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('football', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('baseball_jerseys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dogs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patricia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gaughan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('921_F.Supp.2d_800', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court Northern_District Ohio Patricia A. Gaughan J. 921_F.Supp.2d_800
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Prost Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('design_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('football_jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('express', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verbal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('design_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('basically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('visual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('impression', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('design_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('baseball_jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1328', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Randolph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Digges', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rankin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('North', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Olmsted', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('OH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Randolph E. Digges III Rankin Hill & Clark LLP North Olmsted
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sidoti', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert A. Sidoti
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jonathan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Withrow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jonathan A. Withrow
__NEW_SENT__
('Perry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Saidman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Saidman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DesignLaw', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Group', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Silver', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Spring', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Perry J. Saidman Saidman DesignLaw Group LLC Silver Spring MD
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dorisio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trevor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Graves', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('King', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schickli', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lexington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('KY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Manzo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murphy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Husch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Blackwell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Andrew D. Dorisio Trevor T. Graves King & Schickli PLLC Lexington Edward D. Manzo Mark J. Murphy Husch Blackwell Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CHEN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PROST CHEN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PROST', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MRC_Innovations', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Design', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos', 'NNP', '', 'O')
MRC_Innovations Inc. the U.S. District Court Northern_District Ohio U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('D634,488', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬488_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('D634', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('487', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('S', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬487_patent', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
S ¡¬488_patent 487 S ¡¬487_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
MRC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬488_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ornamental_design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('football_jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dog', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬487_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('baseball_jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
¡¬488_patent ¡¬487_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1329', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Mark_Cohen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('principal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shareholder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O')
MRC
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('retailer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sports', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pet_jerseys', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Hunter Manufacturing LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Prior', 'RB', 'DATE', 'B') ('to', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('9', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('purchased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pet_jerseys', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dogs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mark_Cohen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('affiliated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Prior to September 9 2009 Hunter
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('supplied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('V2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('football_jersey', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gould', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fun-in-Games', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FiG', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Cohen Hunter the Stephen Gould Corporation Fun-in-Games Inc. FiG
__NEW_SENT__
('Similarly', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('supplied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FiG', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('green', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Eagles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('logo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('third-party', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('retailers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wal-Mart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PetSmart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_30,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Similarly Cohen Hunter FiG Philadelphia Eagles Hunter Wal-Mart PetSmart
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('V2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Eagles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('jerseys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1330', 'LS', '', 'O') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('asserts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('V3', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('jersey', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('become', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬488_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Cohen 2009 V3
__NEW_SENT__
('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('purchasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('V3_jersey', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FiG', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('sometime', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Hunter V3_jersey FiG September 8 2009
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('V3_jersey', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('baseball', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('become', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('487', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
September 8 2010 Cohen V3_jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('informed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('no', 'RB', '', 'O') ('longer', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('do', 'VB', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('difficulty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('payments', 'NNS', '', 'O')
December 2010 Cohen Hunter Hunter Hunter
__NEW_SENT__
('Hunter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proposals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('supply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pet_jerseys', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('V3', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('contracted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('supplier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CDI_International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('supply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pet_jerseys', 'NNPS', '', 'O')
Hunter CDI_International Inc. Hunter
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_15,_2011', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
March_15,_2011
__NEW_SENT__
('MRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CDI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MRC Hunter
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CDI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Hunter 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('MRC_Innovations', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hunter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mfg.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('921_F.Supp.2d_800', 'NN', '', 'O') ('812', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ohio', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2013', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
MRC_Innovations Inc. Hunter Mfg. LLP 812 N.D.Ohio 2013
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O')
35
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('810-11', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
MRC
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
