('599_F.3d_1290', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('MARRIN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Etch-It', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('GRIFFIN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Claudia_Griffin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Michael MARRIN Etch-It Inc. Jeffrey GRIFFIN
__NEW_SENT__
('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Griffin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Claudia_Griffin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Heidi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Marrin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Marrin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Etch-It', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Jeffrey Griffin Heidi Marrin Michael Marrin Etch-It Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2009-1031', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('March_22,_2010', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
March_22,_2010
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('May_14,_2010', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scratch-off', 'FW', '', 'O') ('label', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mark', 'VB', '', 'O') ('beverage_containers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('removal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consolidation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2008_WL_4184643', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California George H. Wu J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('preamble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim_limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('distinguishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1292', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Associates', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('PC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Irvine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert D. Fish Fish & Associates Irvine CA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Andrew Mar
__NEW_SENT__
('Geoffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dowell', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Oak', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Park', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('IL', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Geoffrey A. Baker Baker Oak Park IL
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN BRYSON DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DYK', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Claudia_Griffin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Griffins', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Appellants Jeffrey Claudia_Griffin `` the Griffins '' United_States_District_Court California
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Griffins', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._5154,448', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬448_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
the Griffins ' United States Patent No._5154,448 35 102
__NEW_SENT__
('Marrin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Griffin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Nos', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Marrin Griffin Nos
__NEW_SENT__
('CV07-239-GW', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CV07-2100-GW', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('2008_WL_4184643', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2008', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dist', 'NNP', '', 'O')
CV07-2100-GW 2008
__NEW_SENT__
('LEXIS', 'NN', '', 'O') ('79708', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1-2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C.D.Cal', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sept._4,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Griffins', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preamble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_limitation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Griffins
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Claudia_Griffin', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('conceived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scratch-off', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('label', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mark', 'VB', '', 'O') ('beverage_containers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attendees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gathering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('keep', 'VB', '', 'O') ('track', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('beverage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cups', 'NNS', '', 'O')
July of 1990 Jeffrey Claudia_Griffin
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Griffins', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬448_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Scratch-Off', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Marking', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Label', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('13', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Griffins April 1991 `` Scratch-Off Marking Label '' October 13 1992
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 four 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scratch-off', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('label', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('write', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thereon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('marking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('implement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('colored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('near_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('normally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('visible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('far', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scratch-off', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-transparent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('color', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contrasts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('color', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('near_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('near_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thickness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obscure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('color', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('scratched', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('reveals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('color', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('near_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_base', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬448_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4_ll._35', 'CD', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('-48', ':', '', 'O')
4_ll._35
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('comprise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('preamble', 'NN', '', 'O')
first two Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬448_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
