('873_F.2d_1418', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MERCK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DANBURY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
MERCK & CO. DANBURY PHARMACAL INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._89-1046', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
No._89-1046
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('May_2,_1989', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
May_2,_1989
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Murray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schwartz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('694_F.Supp._1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Murray M. Schwartz Chief_Judge 694_F.Supp._1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Markey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relaxant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('procurement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('withholding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('misrepresenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ordinarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nervous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depressants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Markey Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1418', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Joseph M. Fitzpatrick New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nicholas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cannella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Frederick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zullow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Nicholas M. Cannella Frederick M. Zullow
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Norman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Veasey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whetzel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richards', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Layton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Finger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rahway', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('N.J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Alfred', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Engelberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carmel', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('N.Y.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
E. Norman Veasey Robert W. Whetzel Richards Wilmington Delaware Edward W. Murray Merck & Co. Inc. Rahway N.J. Alfred B. Engelberg Carmel
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weiner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Del', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Jeffrey M. Weiner Wilmington Del
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MARKEY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SMITH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
MAYER Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MARKEY', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Schwartz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C.J', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Merck & Merck United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('694_F.Supp._1', 'LS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.1988', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._3882,246', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'246", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Presuming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('familiarity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Schwartz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('comprehensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('describe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Chief_Judge Schwartz ' Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'246_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('types', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skeletal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'246_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_7,_1970', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('Canadian', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'I') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('May_21,_1971', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1419', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abandoned', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('31', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c-i-p', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interview', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('allowable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('April_9,_1974', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('c-i-p', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
four July_7,_1970 Canadian May_21,_1971 United States January 31 1973 1-5
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_6,_1975', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'246_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1970', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Investigational', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('studies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('amitriptyline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relaxants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
September 1970 Food and Drug Administration FDA Merck FDA Investigational New Drug
__NEW_SENT__
('Cyclobenzaprine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('selectivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emphasized.1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('report', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summarizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('evaluating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predominant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('drowsiness', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cyclobenzaprine July 1973 Merck FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1975', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Drug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skeletal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relaxant', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 1975 Merck FDA NDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('submissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('submissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('propensity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('drowsiness', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Merck NDA
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adjunct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('physical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('therapy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spasm', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('acute', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('painful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('musculoskeletal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conditions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
FDA Merck
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('package', 'NN', '', 'O') ('insert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('drowsiness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('frequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('31', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmacal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cyclobenzaprine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O')
October 31 1986 Danbury Pharmacal Inc. Danbury FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Supp', 'NNP', '', 'O')
35 2
__NEW_SENT__
('IV', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1987
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 17 Merck Danbury
__NEW_SENT__
