('952_F.2d_1320', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MALTA', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Malmark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SCHULMERICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CARILLONS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ronald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('O', 'UH', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jacob H. MALTA Malmark Inc. Ronald O
__NEW_SENT__
('Beach', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendants/Cross-Appellants', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Beach Defendants/Cross-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Kelly-Michener', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Handchime', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kelly-Michener Inc. the Handchime Company Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._90-1250', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('90-1269', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._26,_1991', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Suggestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('March_9,_1992', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('handbells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Edmund', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ludwig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('n.o.v', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Pennsylvania Edmund V. Ludwig J.
__NEW_SENT__
('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('absent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('explaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('why', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('why', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('plastic/slotted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('plastic/felt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rich Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Michel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('concurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Michel Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Pauline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('dissented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Pauline Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1321', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pa.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Charles N. Quinn Miller & Quinn Philadelphia Pa.
__NEW_SENT__
('Albert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Preston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Woodcock', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Washburn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kurtz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mackiewicz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Norris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pa.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants/cross-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Albert W. Preston Jr. Woodcock Pa.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Donohue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John P. Donohue Jr.
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RICH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malta', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Malmark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Malmark', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Malta', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('notwithstanding', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JNOV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Schulmerich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Carillons', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Schulmerich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jacob H. Malta Malmark Inc. Malmark November 20 1989 Pennsylvania JNOV Schulmerich Carillons Inc. Schulmerich
__NEW_SENT__
('Malta', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Schulmerich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Carillons', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('13_USPQ2d_1900_(E.D.Pa.1989)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Schulmerich Carillons Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Schulmerich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cross-appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('insofar', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Schulmerich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JNOV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('right', 'RB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Schulmerich November 20 Schulmerich JNOV
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Suit', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Suit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._3941,082', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'082_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Malta', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improvements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('handbells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('music', 'NN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('churches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('schools', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('like', 'JJ', '', 'O')
U.S. No._3941,082 Jacob Malta
__NEW_SENT__
('Quoting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('chorus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('players', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tuned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('bells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tune', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('falls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('notes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Handbells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pivotably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('circular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('striker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handbell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('swung', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('strikes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ring', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'082_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improvements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('handbell', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Malta', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('provision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('loudness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adjusted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fly', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('played', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Malta
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1322', 'FW', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('peripheral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('differing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('hardness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rotating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('change', 'VB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('struck', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('loudness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adjusted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('played', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'082_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('striking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('differing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('hardness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('periphery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('releasably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('locked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('rotated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handbell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('played', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'082_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
two Figs
__NEW_SENT__
('3_and_7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'082_patent", 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fig._3', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('opposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('striking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
first Fig._3 three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('66', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rubber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O')
first 66
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('68', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('striking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cut', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rubber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O')
second 68
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('70', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('piece', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('soft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O')
third 70
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('striking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('loud', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medium', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('soft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fig._7', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('82', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper', 'NN', '', 'O')
second Fig._7 three 82
__NEW_SENT__
('Each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hardness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fig._3', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('soft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('loud', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('depending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('button', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('aligned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('strike', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fig._3
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('somewhat', 'RB', '', 'O') ('confusing', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hardness', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 3 3
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handbell', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('removably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('carried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('centrally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper_shaft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pivotally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('centrally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('carrying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper_member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('extremity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clapper_member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('circular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('striker_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rotatably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('normal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clapper_shaft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('striking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('periphery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hardness', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clapper_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('coacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rotatable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('striker_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('striker_assembly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clapper_shaft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('positioning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('striking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('relation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bell', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('detent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('cooperating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rotatable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('striker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('releasably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('striker_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preselected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ours', 'JJ', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('very', 'RB', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('differs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('respects', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1323', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('coacting', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('indexing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clapper_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('buttons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('opposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('pairs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hardness', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Claim 2 3 two one 3 2 two 3 2 at least three
__NEW_SENT__
