('864_F.2d_757', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('NEWELL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('COMPANIES', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('KENNEY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MANUFACTURING', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant/Cross-Appellant', '.', '', 'O')
NEWELL
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._85-2232', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('86-711', 'CD', '', 'O') ('86-BIG_TOKEN__742_and_86__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-1018', '.', '', 'O')
Nos._85-2232
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._29,_1988', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_3,_1989', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Suggestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_15,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shades', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LOC', 'I') ('Rhode_Island', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Boyle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('606_F.Supp._1282', 'CD', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('notwithstanding', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Rhode_Island Francis J. Boyle
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nies', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('resolved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Nies Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pauline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Pauline Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*759', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Staples', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('McKenzie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
James G. Staples Baker McKenzie Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Philip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zadeik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Philip J. Zadeik
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bush', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blish', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cavanagh', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Providence', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rhode_Island', 'NNP', '', 'O')
John H. Bush Blish & Cavanagh
__NEW_SENT__
('Lars', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kulleseid', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant/cross-appellant', 'CD', '', 'O')
Lars I. Kulleseid Fish & Neave New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Herman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laughon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Kenneth B. Herman C. Joseph Laughon II
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NIES NEWMAN ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('NIES', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Companies', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LOC', 'I') ('Rhode_Island', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('606_F.Supp._1282', 'CD', '', 'O') ('226_USPQ_157_(D.R.I.1985)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Boyle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C.J', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Newell Companies Inc. United_States_District_Court the District of Rhode_Island
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Kenney Manufacturing Company
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('interrogatories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('responding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('No._4006,770', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'770_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reserved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6_and_7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United States Patent No._4006,770 Newell 35 103 1982 Kenney Kenney 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'770_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('retractable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('up', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('down', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shades', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ferguson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manager', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('division', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vinyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shade_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Newell Sean Corcoran
__NEW_SENT__
('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('scored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('partially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lengthwise', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('torn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O')
Corcoran one
__NEW_SENT__
('Its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('advantage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scored', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shade_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('shade_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('640_F.2d_1331', 'IN', '', 'O') ('208_USPQ_867_(CCPA_1981)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predecessor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('addressed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Corcoran Corcoran 208_USPQ_867_(CCPA_1981) Corcoran
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Corcoran_material', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1972', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('/¡±', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
the United States 1972 more than a year Corcoran Corcoran 35 102 103 1982
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shade_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denominated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('nothing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('attach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1334', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('208', 'CD', '', 'O') ('USPQ', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('870', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1334 USPQ 870
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Corcoran_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alone', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unprotectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('freely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anyone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('learning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Corcoran_material', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1974', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sensing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('potential', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contacted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('resided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ireland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sample', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shades', 'NNS', '', 'O')
late 1973 early 1974 Ferguson Corcoran Ireland
__NEW_SENT__
('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sent', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shades', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('supply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1975', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('better', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('supply', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cheaper', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('America', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Corcoran Newell 1975 America
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correspondence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('meetings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Corcoran Newell
__NEW_SENT__
('Ferguson', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('develop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'770_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('attaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Corcoran_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('able', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('slide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('larger', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ferguson
__NEW_SENT__
('Ferguson', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('advantage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('assembled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consumers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tools', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Ferguson
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*760', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('larger_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adjusting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('roller', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('removes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('strip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('presses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('shades', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supplied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Corcoran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Clopay', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Newell Corcoran Clopay Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infra', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clopay_roller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('came', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cardboard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sleeve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('fitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'NN', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O')
Clopay_roller
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sleeve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unnecessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discarded', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Ferguson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Clopay_roller', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3203,468', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'468_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gossling', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Clopay', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Clopay_roller United States Gossling Clopay
__NEW_SENT__
('Shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ferguson
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'770_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1977', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extensible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('retractable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('roll', 'NN', '', 'O') ('window_shade_assembly', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('width', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('installable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tools', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('roller_assembly', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('roller_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('external', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diameter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end_portion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end_portion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outer_end_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('window_shade_assembly', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inner', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end_portion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_roller_section', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nominal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('external', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diameter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end_portion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end_portion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outer_end_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_roller_section', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('window_shade_assembly', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_roller_section', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('telescopically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('slidably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('precluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_roller_sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flexible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('secured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weakness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adjusted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bounded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outside', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inside', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weakness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('wide', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('severance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('securement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('securing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aligned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_roller_section', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('external', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diameter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('securing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('force', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('point', 'VB', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_roller_section', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('beyond', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('positions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_roller_sections', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('fixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('throughout', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('overlap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1 Ferguson February 1977 first first second second first first first second second second second_roller_section first second_roller_sections
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('successful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consumers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1975', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Newell October 1975
__NEW_SENT__
('Other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('do-it-yourself', 'CD', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appeared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('K-Mart', 'NNP', '', 'O')
July 1981 Kenney
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Kenney_shade', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scored', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('larger_roller_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('wrap', 'VB', '', 'O') ('loosely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O')
Kenney_shade Ferguson
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dispositive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'770", 'CD', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('*761', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Corcoran_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('securing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('roller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('strips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('securement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Kenney_shade', 'NN', '', 'O')
Kenney
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('presentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reserved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('answer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'770_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Yes', 'UH', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Newell Kenney
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receipt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("Kenney's.1", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('detail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('unpatentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art.2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Newell 1 2 6 and 7 35 103 one
__NEW_SENT__
('Newell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Newell Kenney
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kenney
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kenney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees.3', 'ADD', '', 'O')
Kenney
__NEW_SENT__
