('916_F.2d_1561', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('NEW', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('IDEA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('FARM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('EQUIPMENT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SPERRY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('New_Holland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
New_Holland Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._87-1216', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Oct._12,_1990', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Eastern', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Division', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Grady', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('centerpivot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('harvesting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('tell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conception', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('corroborated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('warrant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('half', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('wrongful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('refusal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('admit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Grady J. the Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 1 2 3 only one half
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1562', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Raymond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mehler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lockwood', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Alex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fitzgibbon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cummings', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Raymond M. Mehler Alex Fitzgibbon & Cummings Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pastirik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lesht', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alex', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Daniel R. Pastirik David Lesht John L. Alex
__NEW_SENT__
('Berton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sheppard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leydig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Voit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Berton Scott Sheppard Leydig Voit & Mayer Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conklin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leydig', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Voit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
John B. Conklin Leydig Voit & Mayer Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Frank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Daily', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Zaleski', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Quarles', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Brady', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wis.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Daily Michael L. Zaleski Quarles & Brady Madison Wis.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MARKEY*', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BROWN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('**District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
MARKEY* LOURIE Circuit_Judges BROWN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('New_Idea', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Farm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Equipment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('New_Idea', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('No._84-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C-10665', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Sperry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('New_Holland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Sperry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
New_Idea United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois January 28 1987 Sperry Corporation New_Holland Inc. Sperry U.S
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3,868,811', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'811", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,018,036', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'036", 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_Idea', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
3,868,811 4,018,036 New_Idea
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('49', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('g', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Rule 49 35 102 102
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Inventions', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Prior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('New_Idea', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sperry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('harvesters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('windrowers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('conditioners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('farm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('industry.1', '.', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1960', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1970', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'DATE', 'I') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Harvester', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hesston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Hesston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('farm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equipment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor-drawn', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conditioner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('operate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('outboard', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('running', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crop', 'NN', '', 'O')
New_Idea Sperry the late 1960 's early 1970 's International Harvester IH Hesston Corporation Hesston
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('wanted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('flexibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('efficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cutting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patterns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('self-propelled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('harvesters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('expensive', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1968_and_1969', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Hesston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('performed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('begin', 'VB', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor-drawn', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('utilized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('header', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pull', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O')
1968_and_1969 Hesston
__NEW_SENT__
('Merle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Burkhart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hesston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('engineer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('continued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O') ('envisioned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('locations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center', 'NN', '', 'O')
Merle Burkhart Hesston 's
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('fall', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1972', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hesston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Burkhart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('built', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('operated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('utilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('embodied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
the fall of 1972 Hesston Burkhart
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1971', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Burkhart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pull-type', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hydraulically-powered', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('forage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('header', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pivoted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('side-pivot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
October 21 1971 Burkhart one
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figs', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
Figs
__NEW_SENT__
('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3,832,837', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'837", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O')
1_and_2 U.S. 3,832,837
__NEW_SENT__
('*1563.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prototype', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hesston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('near', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Phoenix', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('Arizona', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_8,_1972', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Hesston Phoenix Arizona May_8,_1972
__NEW_SENT__
('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cicci', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Guy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Tufts', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('employees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('saw', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inspected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conceived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('putting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('middle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('operated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('fully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('outboard', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor', 'NN', '', 'O')
George Cicci Guy Tufts IH
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('spring', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('day', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arizona', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Cicci', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Tufts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sketch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
that spring day Arizona Cicci Tufts
__NEW_SENT__
('Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_20,_1973', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'811", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'036_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', '.', '', 'O') (')2', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('purchased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predecessor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_Idea', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
April_20,_1973 two IH New_Idea
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cicci', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'811_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('utilizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ends', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pivotally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hitch', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('operate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cicci
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'036_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('harvesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('standing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('crops', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harvester', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figs', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Figs
__NEW_SENT__
('1_and_2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'811_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
