('357_F.3d_1319', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('NATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('STEEL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CAR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CANADIAN', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('PACIFIC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('RAILWAY', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Canadian_Pacific_Railway_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3942503', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Canada', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hudson_Railway_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NATIONAL STEEL CAR LTD. Plaintiff-Appellee CANADIAN PACIFIC RAILWAY LTD. 3942503 Canada Inc. Delaware &
__NEW_SENT__
('No._03-1256', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._29,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_18,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Rail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('railroad', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('254_F.Supp.2d_527', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Mary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McLaughlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('railroad', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court Pennsylvania Mary A. McLaughlin J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Clevenger Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('rail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('came', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('temporary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('exemption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1321', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Krupka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert G. Krupka Kirkland & Ellis Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Swenson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McManus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Linda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Resh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leavell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jamie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McDole', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lugtu', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
David P. Swenson Robert J. McManus Kirkland & Ellis Washington DC Linda S. Resh Craig D. Leavell Jamie H. McDole Alma M. Lugtu Kirkland & Ellis Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Alexandra', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DeNeve', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Alexandra DeNeve Kirkland Ellis Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Banner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Banner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Witcoff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mark T. Banner Banner & Witcoff Ltd. Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cooperman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pieter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('van', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Es', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Janice', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('V.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mitrius', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Theodore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Field', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Marc S. Cooperman J. Pieter Theodore L. Field
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MAYER CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('National_Steel_Car', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('National_Steel_Car', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Canadian_Pacific', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Railway', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Canadian_Pacific_Railway_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3942503', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Canada', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('*1322', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hudson_Railway_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Canadian_Pacific', 'NN', 'LOC', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CPR', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4951,575', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬575_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
NSC 3942503 Canada Inc. Delaware Canadian_Pacific CPR Pennsylvania U.S. Patent No._4951,575
__NEW_SENT__
('NSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('NSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CPR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('272', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lacked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('merit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CPR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('raise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O')
NSC NSC NSC CPR 35 272 CPR
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Nat', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('l', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Steel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Car', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Canadian', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('Pac', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Canadian
__NEW_SENT__
('Ry.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('254_F.Supp.2d_527', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Pa.2003', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Ry. Ltd. E.D.Pa.2003
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('careful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('advanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CPR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
CPR NSC
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬575_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('National_Steel_Car', 'NNS', 'GPE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('railway', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('addresses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('railway', 'NN', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('haul', 'VB', '', 'O') ('lumber', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('depressed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('center-beam_flat_car', 'NN', '', 'O')
National_Steel_Car
__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬575_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('longitudinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')
1 one
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬575_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('center-beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('truss-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('beam', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('element', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('runs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('end_truck_assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('back', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬575_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Center-beam_cars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hauling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lumber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('piled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('laterally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center_beam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('secured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center_beam', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Canadian_Pacific', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('currently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('operates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fleet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('center-beam_flat_cars', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬575_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('depressed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('drop-deck', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end_truck_assemblies', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lowered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('height', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end_truck_assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬575_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drop-deck', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('center-beam_flat_car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('advantages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-drop-deck', 'NN', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('carry', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('volumetrically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('larger', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('center-beam_cars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('volume', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inefficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('under-loaded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dropping', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deck', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lowers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gravity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('permitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('safer', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('loading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unloading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gravity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('renders', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('vulnerable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tipping', 'NN', '', 'O')
Second
__NEW_SENT__
('NSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5-9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('20-23', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬575_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
NSC 1-3
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('2_and_20', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('define', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 2_and_20
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim_terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('need', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reproduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exhaustive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('*BIG_TOKEN__1323_and_5__BIG_TOKEN', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim_terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('emphasized', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flat_car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end_truck_assemblies', 'CD', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('longitudinally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('draft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bulkheads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('side_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposite_sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vertical_center_beam_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upward', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vertical_center_beam_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_center_sill', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bulkheads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('upper_center_sill', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('columns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('carried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('floor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opposite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('floor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('floor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('lying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('horizontal_plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intermediate_depressed_floor_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('horizontal_plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('horizontal_plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('side_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side_sill_assemblies', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposite_sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('center_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('side_sill_assemblies', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('axis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intermediate_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('axis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('axis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('intermediate_depressed_floor_section', 'NN', '', 'O')
first second first first
__NEW_SENT__
('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flat_car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('side_sill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('side_sill', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('transition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('joining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('side_sill_assemblies', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('intermediate_section', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬575_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col._5,_l._49-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._6,_l._9', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
