('504_F.3d_1223', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Ole', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NILSSEN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('OSRAM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SYLVANIA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Osram_Sylvania_Products', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
Ole K. NILSSEN Geo_Foundation Ltd. OSRAM SYLVANIA INC. Osram_Sylvania_Products Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2006-1550', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Oct._10,_2007', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Jan._16,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Inventor', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exclusive_licensee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compact', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_light_bulbs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ballasts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gas_discharge_lamps', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_light_bulbs', 'ADD', '', 'O')
Inventor
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Darrah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('440_F.Supp.2d_884', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois John W. Darrah J. 440_F.Supp.2d_884
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('submitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('affidavits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('points', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('distinction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('informing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('affiant', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('eligible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small_entity_maintenance_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mislead', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('status', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('maintenance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('exculpability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('credible', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')
Patent and Trademark_Office
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('intentional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('ones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('inference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unreasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('withholding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1226', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jenner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Block', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Paul M. Smith Jenner & Block LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hirsch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Caroline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lewis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wolverton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Roper', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Raymond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nimrod', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jonathan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Aaron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barlow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Sam Hirsch Lewis Wolverton Harry Roper Raymond N. Nimrod Jonathan Hill Chicago Aaron A. Barlow
__NEW_SENT__
('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sieve', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Brian D. Sieve Kirkland & Ellis LLP Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Garret', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kal', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Serena', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gondek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Landau', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Garret A. Leach Kal K. Shah Serena J. Gondek Christopher Landau Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINARES', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
MAYER LOURIE Circuit_Judges LINARES District
__NEW_SENT__
('**', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ole', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sylvania', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Osram_Sylvania_Products', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fifteen', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exclusively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ole K. Nilssen the Geo_Foundation Ltd. United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of Illinois Osram Sylvania Inc. Osram_Sylvania_Products Inc. Osram fifteen Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lighting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('fifteen', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('eleven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('withdrawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('U.S', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
fifteen first eleven Osram four U.S
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4,857,806', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ806_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,164,637', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ637_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,233,270', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ270_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,343,123', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('123', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,402,043', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ043_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,416,386', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ386_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,432,409', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ409_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,479,074', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ074_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,481,160', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ160_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,510,680', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ680_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5,510,681', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,677,345', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ345_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,047,690', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ690_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5,189,342', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ342_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5,341,067', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ067_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
4,857,806 5,164,637 5,233,270 5,343,123 123 5,402,043 5,416,386 5,432,409 5,479,074 5,481,160 5,510,680 5,510,681 4,677,345 5,047,690 5,189,342 5,341,067
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compact', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_light_bulbs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ballasts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gas_discharge_lamps', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_light_bulbs', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ballast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('converts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alternating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('current_power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('utility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alternating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('current_power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gas_discharge_lamps', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorneys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prosecute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('prosecuting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('*1227', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('understanding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('better', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O')
1983 Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('knowledgeable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('practice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Manual', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Examining', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Procedure', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('MPEP', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('statutes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('regulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Nilssen the Manual of Patent Examining Procedure MPEP
__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('established', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('not-for-profit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('charitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('organization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Cayman', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('Islands', 'NNPS', 'LOC', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Nilssen the Cayman Islands 1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive_licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
June 2000 Geo_Foundation Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('Prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('licensed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('North', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Nilssen Philips Electronics North America Corp. Philips
__NEW_SENT__
('Apparently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('canceled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('revoked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Geo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sublicensing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNS', 'GPE', 'B') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('execution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Geo Philips Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('receives', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('revenue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('awards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('settlements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lawsuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enforce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('pays', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('pays', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('twenty-five', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('percent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('gross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('income', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic_ballasts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('eleven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Appellants Osram 2000 Osram eleven Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('Among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('procurement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Osram Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six-day', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Osram
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('affidavits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dale', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Fiene', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('one', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ345_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ690_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('affidavits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Fiene', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('personal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('professional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('association', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fiene', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('financial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
First Nilssen two Dale Fiene ÁÂ345_patent Fiene Nilssen Fiene Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ345_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ270', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('share', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relatedness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ345_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ270', 'NNS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('681', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infectious_unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
ÁÂ270 ÁÂ681_patent three three ÁÂ270
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('incorrect', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('payment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small_entity_maintenance_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Second Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Compact', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fluorescent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lamp', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Agreement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CFLA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Nilssen Philips December 7 1995
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFLA', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('expects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('offer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('CFL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('running', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('royalty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('CFL_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('starting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('first', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('quarter', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
CFLA Nilssen the first quarter of 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('offer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('take', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('CFL_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('royalties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('payments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('accrue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('CFL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('10', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('Dollar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('share', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CFL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O')
Nilssen Philips Nilssen Philips Nilssen Nilssen one at least 10 % U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFLA', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('covered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ806', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ637', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ270', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ123', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ680', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('681', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
CFLA
__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('License', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Agreement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PLA', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Nilssen PLA Philips January 1 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PLA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('covered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ806', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ637', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ043', 'UH', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ386', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ409', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ074', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ160', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ680', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent_s.', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('agreements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('obligation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('license', 'VB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1228', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Philips', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('500', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('employees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obligated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('large_entity_maintenance_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('date', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFLA', 'NN', '', 'O')
PLA Philips more than 500 Nilssen December 7 1995 the date
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('twenty-one', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('improper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('payments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('payments', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Nilssen at least one eight
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('credit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('explanation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('believe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('payments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('once', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonprofit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Geo_Foundation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Nilssen 2000
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('large_entity_maintenance_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Third', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('intentionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('misclaimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_20,_1978', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'FAC', 'B') ('ÁÂ637', 'NN', 'FAC', 'I') ('ÁÂ043', 'UH', 'FAC', 'I') ('ÁÂ386', 'RB', 'FAC', 'I') ('ÁÂ409', 'VBP', 'FAC', 'I') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('160', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ÁÂ680', 'NNS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent_s.', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('copendency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross-reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('satisfied', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Third Nilssen March_20,_1978 the ÁÂ637 ÁÂ043 ÁÂ386 ÁÂ409 160 ÁÂ680
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('false', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('potentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('letters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sent', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Advance', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Transformer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('protection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ballast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('representing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
two Nilssen Advance Transformer Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'B') ('ÁÂ637', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ÁÂ043', 'UH', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ÁÂ386', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ409', 'VBP', 'FAC', 'B') ('ÁÂ160', 'DT', 'FAC', 'I') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('680', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('false', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dates', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the ÁÂ637 ÁÂ043 ÁÂ409 ÁÂ160 ÁÂ 680 ÁÂ681_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Fourth', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ongoing_litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motorola', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Fourth Nilssen Motorola
__NEW_SENT__
('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motorola_alleging_infringement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('19', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Nilssen six October 19 1993
__NEW_SENT__
('Motorola', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('observe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O')
Motorola 35
__NEW_SENT__
('Those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prejudice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_23,_1996', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
July_23,_1996
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motorola_alleging_infringement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('plus', 'CC', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
six nine Nilssen September 3 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pertained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('matter-electronic_ballasts-claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('leading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ123', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ043', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ386', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ409', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ074', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ160', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('680', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Motorola', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('inform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ681_patent Motorola Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('intended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mislead', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('credit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unaware', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('duty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ongoing_litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nilssen the United States Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ123', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ043', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ386', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ409', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ074', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ160', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ680', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('report', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('existence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Motorola', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Motorola
__NEW_SENT__
('Fifth', 'NNP', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nilssen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ342_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ067_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('806', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ043', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ681_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('identify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fifth Nilssen
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('descendant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ123', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ043', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ386', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ409', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ160_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ342_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infectious_unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
ÁÂ342_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Osram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unclean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hands', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Osram
__NEW_SENT__
('*1229', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
