('521_F.3d_1351', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('O2', 'UH', '', 'O') ('MICRO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LIMITED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BEYOND', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INNOVATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TECHNOLOGY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CO.', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('LTD.', ',', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
MICRO INTERNATIONAL LIMITED Plaintiff-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('FSP_Group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SPI_Electronic_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
SPI_Electronic_Co. Ltd. Defendants-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Lien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Enterprise', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lien Chang Electronic Enterprise Co. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2007-1302', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2007-1303', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2007-1304', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_3,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_11,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inverter_controllers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('low_voltage_direct_current', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('higher_voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alternating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('AC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
DC AC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ward', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_869576', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('inter_alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent_owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Prost Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('waive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')
Markman
__NEW_SENT__
('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('significance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent_owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Vacated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1353', 'DT', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pooley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Morrison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Foerster', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
James Pooley Morrison & Foerster LLP Palo Alto
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bryan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Bryan Wilson
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard S.J
__NEW_SENT__
('Hung', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Duane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mathiowetz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howrey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Su', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('East', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Duane H. Mathiowetz San_Francisco CA Richard C. Lin Henry C. Su East Palo Alto
__NEW_SENT__
('Stanley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Young', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ehrman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Menlo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Park', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1354', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Beyond', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Innovation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technology', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sarah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Houghland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Stanley Young Heller Ehrman Menlo Park Beyond Innovation Technology Co. Ltd. Sarah R. Houghland
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Johnny', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cheng-Teh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chiu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Joshua', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosenkranz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ethan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Glass', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Johnny Cheng-Teh Chiu Washington DC E. Joshua Rosenkranz New York Ethan C. Glass
__NEW_SENT__
('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('FSP_Group', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SPI_Electronic_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Theodore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shiells', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gregory W. Carr Carr LLP Dallas Theodore F. Shiells
__NEW_SENT__
('Mao-Sen_Yieh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Offices', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mao-Sen_Yieh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Lien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Enterprise', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
Houston Lien Chang Electronic Enterprise Co. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PROST', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Beyond', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Innovation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Technology', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('BiTEK', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('SPI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('FSP_Group', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('SPI/FSP', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Enterprise', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Lien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
BiTEK SPI Electronic Company Limited SPI/FSP Lien Chang Lien Chang Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('O2_Micro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Beyond', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Innovation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._2', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':04-CV-32', ':', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_869576', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Tex', '.', '', 'O')
Beyond Innovation Tech Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('Mar', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('21', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 2007
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('induced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6259,615', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('¡¬615_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('12_and_16', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6396,722', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('¡¬722_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6804,129', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬129_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('O2_Micro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('O2_Micro', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1 15 35 and 39 `` the ¡¬615_patent `` the ¡¬722_patent `` 13 16 and 17 Plaintiff-Appellee O2_Micro International Ltd. O2_Micro ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Patents-in-Suit', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I')
A. Patents-in-Suit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DC-to-AC_converter_circuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('low_voltage_direct_current', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('higher_voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alternating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('AC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
AC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inverter_controllers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cold', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cathode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CCFLs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('backlight', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('laptop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('computers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('televisions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('powered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('battery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CCFL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DC-to-AC_converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CCFLs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O')
DC AC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('employs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_control_loop', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('drive', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CCFL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
DC
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬615_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('80', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2 80 12 20
__NEW_SENT__
('Drive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('circuitry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('50', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('long', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('turned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'RP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ON', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
50 ON
__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('path', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('ON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('deliver', 'VB', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O')
ON
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adjusting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", '``', '', 'O') ('ON_times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('precisely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1355.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬615_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_control_loop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('affect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ON_times', 'NNS', '', 'O')
40
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_control_loop', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('indicative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total_current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference_voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('REF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('indicative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conditions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('total_current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
FB REF
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amplifier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('32', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('compares', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference_voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('REF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('comparison_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CMP', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
32 FB REF
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('normal_operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drive_circuitry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('50', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('receives', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('comparison_signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('94', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('adjust', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ON_times', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('regulating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O')
50 94 ON_times
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('protect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circuitry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open-circuit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('condition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CCFL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('breaks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('becomes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disconnected', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FB', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference_value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('current_sense_comparator', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('42', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2 42
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference_value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preferably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reflects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('maximum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('permitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FB', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('normal_operation', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('current_sense_comparator', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('42', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('comparison_signal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CMP', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('flow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('38', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('short', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('condition', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('current_sense_comparator', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('substitutes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimum_voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Vmin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('comparison_signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CMP', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('38', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
42 38 current_sense_comparator Vmin 38
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimum_voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('minimizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ON_times', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('safer', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('level', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('avoiding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('shutdown', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('remains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('operable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
ON_times
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬615_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unpatentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5384,516', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kawabata', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Kawabata', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6011,360', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gradzki', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Gradzki', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 103 U.S. No._5384,516 Kawabata Gradzki Gradzki
__NEW_SENT__
('*1356', 'FW', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('observed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Gradzki', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('et', 'FW', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('al', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Gradzki et al
__NEW_SENT__
('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('utilization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drive_circuitry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supplying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indicative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('supplied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('7638', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
7638
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Gradzki', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inverter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('controller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('regulates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('irrespective', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('level', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Gradzki
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('O2_Micro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('O2_Micro', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('615', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_control_loop_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conduction_state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('threshold', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'only", 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ("'", '``', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Claim 1 615
__NEW_SENT__
('O2_Micro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('little', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('explanation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('n', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Applicant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inter_alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DC/AC_converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_control_loop_circuit..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('generate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('pulse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signal..', 'RB', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('threshold', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1 second
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('7626', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('allowance', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'I') ('¡¬615_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1 of the
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DC/AC_converter_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_control_loop_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indicative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('supplied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('load', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('generate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pulse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('controlling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conduction_state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('feedback_signal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('threshold', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'615_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('l.67-col.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', '', 'O') ('l.5', '.', '', 'O')
second second 10
__NEW_SENT__
