('808_F.3d_509', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('OPENWAVE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SYSTEMS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('nka', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
OPENWAVE SYSTEMS INC. Unwired_Planet Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('APPLE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Motion', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motion_Corp.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
APPLE INC. Research in Motion Ltd. Research
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2015-1108', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._15,_2015', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('setting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('architecture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interactive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('two-way', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Andrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2014_WL_651911', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim_term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Richard G. Andrews J. 2014_WL_651911
__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("O'Malley", 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals O'Malley Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disavowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('repeated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('disparagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('portable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('two-way_communication_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer_module', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*510', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Theodore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Stevenson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKool', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Theodore Stevenson III McKool Smith Dallas
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Meredith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Anne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Elkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jared', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hoggan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nicholas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mathews', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Geyser', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stris', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Maher', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Meredith Anne Elkins Jared M. Hoggan Nicholas M. Mathews Daniel L. Geyser Stris & Maher LLP Los_Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gibson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crutcher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Apple_Inc.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Buroker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Alexander', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Josh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Krevitt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('N.Y.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Hervey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lyon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stuart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosenberg', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('Alto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Brooke', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Myers', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wallace', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Mark Andrew Perry Gibson Dunn & Crutcher LLP Apple_Inc. Brian Buroker Alexander N. Harris San Francisco CA Josh Krevitt New York N.Y. Mark Lyon Stuart Rosenberg Palo Brooke Myers Wallace Los_Angeles CA
__NEW_SENT__
('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heinrich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Irell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Manella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Motion', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Research', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motion_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gavin', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('Snyder', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wessel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Alan J. Heinrich Irell & Manella LLP Research in Motion Ltd. Gavin Bruce A. Wessel
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MOORE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("O'MALLEY", 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CHEN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MOORE O'MALLEY CHEN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("O'MALLEY", 'LS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Openwave', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NKA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._6405,037', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬037_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('6,430,409', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬409_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('6,625,447', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬447_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*511', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Openwave Systems Inc. NKA Unwired_Planet Inc. Unwired_Planet U.S. Nos._6405,037 6,430,409 6,625,447
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('share', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specification.1', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Unwired_Planet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Apple_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Motion', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Motion_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('31', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Apple_Inc. Research in Motion Ltd. Research Defendants August 31 2011 the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('Shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initiated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trade', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Commission', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ITC', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
October 7 2011 the International Trade Commission ITC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ITC_proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unfavorable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Administrative', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Law', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ALJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('overseeing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ITC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('investigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('entirety', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Administrative Law ALJ ITC
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('13', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ITC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('terminated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')
November 13 2012 ITC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lifted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('stay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
December 28 2012
__NEW_SENT__
('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('informed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim_term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('matched', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ITC_proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('concede', 'VB', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('terminate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('considering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('briefing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adopting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('closely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('tracked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('employed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ALJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
ALJ
__NEW_SENT__
('Believing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stipulate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
one two Unwired_Planet
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('footnote', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('employing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('employing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('microprocessors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('remained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unresolved', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('refusal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('concede', 'VB', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unclear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('actually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fell', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('premised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('summary-judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distinction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('microprocessors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unclear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prohibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('changed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('course', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'RB', '', 'O')
Unwired_Planet Unwired_Planet
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2014', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Defendants October 14 2014
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claim_terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬037_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mobile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephone', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬409_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('two-way_communication_device', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬447_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ALJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('analyzed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O')
ALJ
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('construe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('umbrella', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('repeated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('disparagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*512', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('disclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('address', 'NN', '', 'O') ('perceived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
patents-in-suit
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('intelligent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('updated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('physically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('changing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('themselves', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('physically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('burned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('read-only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ROMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ROM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('card', 'NN', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('install', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('need', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('re-burn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ROM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('install', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ROM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('card', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬037_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('2_ll._33', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-40', 'NFP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('intelligent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephone', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('day', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('moreover', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('big', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('expensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('battery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('life', 'NN', '', 'O')
the day
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('9_ll._21', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-25', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention-1995-mobile_devices', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('processors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('powerful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('operate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('running', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercialization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difficulties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('devised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ways', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('divide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('remote', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('server', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('eliminat', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('employ', 'VB', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Op', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Br', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('microcontrollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('-which', ',', '', 'O') ('facilitate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('communications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('client', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('server-or', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('robust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('-which', ',', '', 'O') ('serve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('localize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computational', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself.3', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('answering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('encompass', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Openwave', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sys.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apple_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
Openwave Sys. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('CV-11-765-RGA', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('2014_WL_651911', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*3', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del', 'UH', '', 'O')
2014_WL_651911
__NEW_SENT__
('Feb._19,_2014', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Feb._19,_2014
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('passages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disparage', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('implementation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('repeated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('derogatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statements..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('viewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disavowal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('p', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('atent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('alterations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('quotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('marks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Bd', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Options', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Exch.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Sec', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Options Exch. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Exch.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('677_F.3d_1361', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1372', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2012', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('patents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disclaim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
(';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('specifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('patents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mobile_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('computer_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
9
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disavowal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mobile_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two-way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*513', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Openwave', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2014_WL_651911', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*3', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('footnote', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ma', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('microcontrollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('n.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Id.at 3
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hesitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Unwired_Planet
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Unwired_Planet', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Unwired_Planet
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
17
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
