('355_F.3d_1353', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('COMPUTER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PRODUCTS', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FOXCONN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Precision', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', '', 'O')
PSC COMPUTER PRODUCTS INC. FOXCONN INTERNATIONAL INC. Hon Hai Precision Industry Co. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._03-1089', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._20,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('retainer_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat_sinks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Dean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pregerson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California Dean D. Pregerson J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gajasa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('plastic_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Gajasa Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1354', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Adams', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Peacock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Myers', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Adams', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Albuquerque', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Paul Adams Myers & Adams P.C. Albuquerque NM
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reynolds', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lewis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brisbois', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bisgaard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David E. Reynolds Lewis Brisbois Bisgaard & Smith LLP Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Watnick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Kenneth D. Watnick
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MAYER CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('GAJARSA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Computer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Precision', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._6061,239', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
PSC Computer Products Inc. United_States_District_Court California Foxconn International Inc. Hon Hai Precision Industry Co. Ltd. Foxconn U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Computer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prods.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Int', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("'", "''", 'PERSON', 'I') ('l', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._01-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CV-6414', 'NNP', '', 'O')
PSC Computer Prods. Inc. Foxconn Int '
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plastic_clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('explicitly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Cam-Type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Retainer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Clip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Heat', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sinks', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Integrated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
The United States Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('significant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complex', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('product-the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microchip', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1355', 'UH', '', 'O') ('components', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('microchip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microchip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('flow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('logic_gates', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('outputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('microchip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proportional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('logic_gates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('modern', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('enough', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('risk', 'VB', '', 'O') ('becoming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('self-destructive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('need', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('heat_sinks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dissipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dissipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('life', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('microchip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('securing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam-type_retainer_clip', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('engagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('retainer_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('flat', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('engagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semiconductor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upper_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('channel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('retainer_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resilient_metal_strap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('received', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('channels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('engagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spaced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Claim 1 of at least one resilient_metal_strap one
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam-type', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('latch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pivotally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pivot_access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pivot_access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fixedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('arm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('rotated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('causing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('forced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('placing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('force', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('engagement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'239_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._6,_ll._6-31', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam-type_retainer_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_sink_assembly', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I')
only two Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('One', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('vendors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('differentiate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O')
One
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('choice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('retainer_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('competing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cam-type_retainer_clips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat_sink', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Foxconn
__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O')
PSC Foxconn
__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('239', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California Foxconn 239
__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resilient_metal_strap', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nonetheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('plastic_clip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Foxconn Claim 1 Foxconn Foxconn
__NEW_SENT__
('Foxconn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic_parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O')
PSC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reviewed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('plastic_clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O')
Foxconn PSC
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('recent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Johnston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Associates', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R.E', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Foxconn Johnson & Johnston Associates
__NEW_SENT__
('Service', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('285_F.3d_1046_(Fed.Cir.2002)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1356', 'XX', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reclaim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Service Co. 285_F.3d_1046_(Fed.Cir.2002)
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('outlined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Maxwell', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('86_F.3d_1098_(Fed.Cir.1996)', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Maxwell J. Baker Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic_parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('plastic_clips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Foxconn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('plastic_clips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('domain', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resilient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stainless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('steel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resilient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strap', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._4,_ll._49-51', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('o', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ther', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('use', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('molded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cast', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('forged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('expensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('operations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2.', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ll', 'UH', '', 'O')
2.
__NEW_SENT__
('39-41', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
39-41
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('passages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('knew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬239_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('plastic_parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('explicit', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unclaimed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('239', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O')
Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dedication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prevented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SciMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Life', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Advanced', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Cardiovascular', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('242_F.3d_1337_(Fed.Cir.2001)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('deemed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('encompass', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O')
SciMed Life Systems Advanced Cardiovascular Systems
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1341', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1341
__NEW_SENT__
('Having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('criticized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invoke', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('embrace', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('excluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1345', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1345
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('precedents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-metallic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resilient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invoke', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('embrace', 'VB', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
PSC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Foxconn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Foxconn
__NEW_SENT__
('PSC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
