('839_F.3d_1131', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('POLY-AMERICA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.P.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('API', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INDUSTRIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
API INDUSTRIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('2016-1200', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2016', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
October 14 2016
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('elastic_drawstring_bag', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Sue', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('L', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Sue L
__NEW_SENT__
('Robinson.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2015_WL_4608135', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robinson. J. 2015_WL_4608135
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('disavowal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('short_seal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inwardly', 'RB', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Reyna Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1132', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-00599-SLR-SRF', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Sue L. Robinson
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('AARON', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MAURER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Williams', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Connolly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
AARON P. MAURER Williams & Connolly LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SANJIV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PRAKASH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LAUD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CRAIG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SINGER', 'NNP', '', 'O')
SANJIV PRAKASH
__NEW_SENT__
('JACK', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('BLUMENFELD', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nichols', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Arsht', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Tunnell', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
JACK B. BLUMENFELD
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHAEL', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('FLYNN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('MARK', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('KOFFSKY', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('EFREM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SCHWALB', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Koffsky', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Schwalb', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
MICHAEL J. FLYNN MARK I. KOFFSKY LLC New York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hughes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PROST Reyna Hughes
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reyna', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('disavowal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Poly-America', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('L.P.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'GPE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Poly-America', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._8702,308', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'308_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unequivocal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trash_bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('upper_corners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('inwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('narrow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O')
Poly-America L.P. 's Poly-America U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('disavowal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('short_seal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('inwardly', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1133', 'FW', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A.', 'LS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patented', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technology', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
A. Patented Technology
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'308_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drawstring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trash_bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'308_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3_ll._46', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-47', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('fig._1', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('panels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polymeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fold', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('piece', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('folded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'RP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hem', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drawstring', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('3_ll._46', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-54', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('4_ll._66', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('-67', '.', '', 'O')
4_ll._66
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_corners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'LS', '', 'O') ('5_ll._25', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-30', ':', '', 'O')
5_ll._25
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('bind', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('hem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ends', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drawstrings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('therein', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('principal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Poly-America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trash_bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('elastic_drawstrings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('narrowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drawstrings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('wrap', 'VB', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trash_receptacle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('securely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art_trash_bags', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('narrowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'LS', '', 'O') ('6_l._32', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-col.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('7_l._19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
7_l._19
__NEW_SENT__
('Throughout', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'308_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('significance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('short_seal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upper_opening_width', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('start', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('title', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Opening', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Elastic', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Drawstring', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bag', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('*1134', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('w', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('hen', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present_invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relaxed_state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upper_opening_width', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('elastic_drawstring_bag', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bag', 'VB', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pull', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastic_drawstring_bag', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trash_receptacle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastic_drawstrings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('snugly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trashcan', 'NN', '', 'O')
the elastic_drawstring_bag elastic_drawstring_bag
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Background', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Invention', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art_trash_bags', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trash_receptacle', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('2_ll._15', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-54', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Summary', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Invention', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elastic_drawstring_bag', 'CD', '', 'O') ('contemplated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present_invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('97', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('virtue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
less than 97 %
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('4_ll._4', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-7', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'308_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reveal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('virtue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('depicts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drawstring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bags', 'NNS', '', 'O')
five
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('figs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('1-5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1-5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reiterates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art_trash_bags', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('5_ll._46', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-57', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upper_opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present_invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('looking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FIG._1', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('FIG._2', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('note', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present_invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relaxed_state', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended_short_seals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('6_ll._11', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-15', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
