('587_F.3d_1324', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('PERFECT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WEB', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TECHNOLOGIES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('INFOUSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', 'ORG', 'I')
INFOUSA INC. Defendant-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2009-1105', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._2,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Feb._23,_2010', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('managing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bulk_e-mail_distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('targeted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('consumers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Southern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Florida', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ryskamp', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2008_WL_6153736', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Southern District Florida Kenneth L. Ryskamp 2008_WL_6153736
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invocation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('try', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1325', 'UH', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rodriguez', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Greenberg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Miami', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('FL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
John C. Carey Greenberg & Paul LLP Miami
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Allison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cammack', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Allison J. Cammack
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rozendaal', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kellogg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Huber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hansen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Evans', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Figel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.L.L.C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
John C. Rozendaal Kellogg Huber Hansen Todd Evans & Figel P.L.L.C. Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bird', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Wan J. Kim Daniel G. Bird
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LINN DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Perfect_Web', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Technologies', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Perfect_Web', 'PRP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6631,400', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Perfect_Web U.S. ¡¬400_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Perfect_Web', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('InfoUSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._07-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CV-80286', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.Fla', '.', '', 'O')
Perfect_Web Techs. Inc. InfoUSA Inc. CV-80286
__NEW_SENT__
('Oct._24,_2008', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Opinion
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1326', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('managing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bulk_e-mail_distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('targeted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('consumers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬400_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_13,_2000', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fervent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬400_patent 's April_13,_2000
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬400_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.25-27', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recognizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('email', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('often', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.27-28', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('describing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('opt-in', 'CD', '', 'O') ('bulk_e-mailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('services', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('distributors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('access', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('lists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('customers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('express', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preferences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('e-mail', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('l.56', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('comparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('successfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('e-mail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('messages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('delivery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('delivery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('repeating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('e-mailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('customers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('messages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('achieved', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Perfect_Web', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('InfoUSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
1 15 InfoUSA Inc
__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('managing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bulk_e-mail_distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('matching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recipient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('profile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('target_recipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('transmitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bulk_e-mails', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('target_recipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('matched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('calculating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('e-mails', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bulk_e-mails', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('successfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('target_recipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('calculated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exceed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prescribed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('minimum_quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('successfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('e-mails', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('repeating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('calculated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exceeds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('prescribed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('minimum_quantity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('adds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('choosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subset', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('targeted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('e-mail_distribution', 'NN', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('specifies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('targeted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('recipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('opt-in', 'NN', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Claim 5 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('readable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('performs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 11 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('12_and_15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('depend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mirror', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
12_and_15 11
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('joint', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memoranda', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('addressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('InfoUSA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
InfoUSA
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issuing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('convened', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O')
Markman
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('InfoUSA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assuming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Perfect_Web', 'PRP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O')
InfoUSA Perfect_Web
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1_n._1', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appear', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('virtually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anyone', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
first 1 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
7
__NEW_SENT__
('Moreover', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('EmailChannel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('public', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('critical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 35 102 EmailChannel
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
15
__NEW_SENT__
('Additionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('merely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('algorithms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1 35 101
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
18
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ineligible', 'VB', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Perfect_Web', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('*1327', 'NN', '', 'O') ('DISCUSSION', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('de', 'FW', '', 'O') ('novo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reapplying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('applicable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Young', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lumenis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('492_F.3d_1336', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1345', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2007', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Lumenis Inc. 1345
__NEW_SENT__
('Summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('56', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
56
__NEW_SENT__
