('73_F.3d_1085', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('PARA-ORDNANCE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MANUFACTURING', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('IMPORTERS', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant/Cross-Appellant', '.', '', 'O')
PARA-ORDNANCE MANUFACTURING INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._94-1486', 'NN', '', 'O') ('94-1487', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Dec._28,_1995', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('March_20,_1996', 'NNP', '', 'O')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conversion_kit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('expanding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ammunition_capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('semiautomatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('handguns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Selby', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Virginia Thomas Selby Ellis III J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schall', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one-piece', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('converging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('conversion_kit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Schall Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Archer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dissented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1086', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Henderson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Farabow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Garrett', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dunner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Donald R. Dunner
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jenkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Linda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wadler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas H. Jenkins Linda A. Wadler
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marvin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Petry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Linda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ring', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Larson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taylor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marvin Petry Linda M. Ring Larson & Taylor Arlington Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('Sumner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosenberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Needle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rosenberg', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Georgia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant/cross-appellant', 'CD', '', 'O')
Sumner C. Rosenberg Needle P.C. Atlanta Georgia
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nagendra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Setty', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Nagendra
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Saunders', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Roger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Furey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Arter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hadden', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mary Jane Saunders Roger P. Furey Arter & Hadden Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ARCHER Chief_Judge CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('SCHALL', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Para-Ordnance', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Para-Ordnance', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_2,_1994', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_9,_1994', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Para-Ordnance Manufacturing Inc. June_2,_1994 June_9,_1994 United_States_District_Court Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('Para-Ordnance', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mfg.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Importers', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Docket', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._94-117-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Para-Ordnance', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Importers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._4862,618', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Para-Ordnance SGS Importers International Inc. United States 1 35 103 1988 2
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('conversion_kit', 'FW', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('expanding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ammunition_capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('semi-automatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('handguns', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expansion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ammunition_capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('accomplished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('handgun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('widened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ammunition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('magazine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('accommodate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cartridges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('staggered', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side-by-side', 'IN', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('kit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one-piece', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('handgun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grip_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1087', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('wide', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enlarged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magazine', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('thirteen', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('twelve', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
thirteen one twelve
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows:1', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conversion_kit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('convert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semi-automatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hand-gun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('round', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hand-gun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('round', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('piece', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elongated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('throughout', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('flat', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('external_side_faces', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open-ended', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groove', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'NN', '', 'O') ('guides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('slide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('hand-gun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('downwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('depending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intermediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('grip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('width', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('external_side_faces', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('merging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('external_side_faces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('through-bore', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magazine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chamber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('grip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bottom_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('through-bore', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opposite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('faces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('axis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('straight', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('starting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bottom_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('zone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('just', 'RB', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('top_part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intermediate_face_portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('converging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('grooves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('uninterrupted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('slidably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('retain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('slide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reciprocating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latter', 'JJ', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Para-Ordnance', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement,2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Llama', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('IX-C', 'VB', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('IX-D', 'NN', '', 'O') ('handguns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
SGS Llama IX-C
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('countered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('SGS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('items', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('191145', 'CD', '', 'O') ('caliber_handgun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Browning_Hi-Power', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('9mm', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('handgun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Llama', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Omni45', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('caliber_handgun', 'NNP', '', 'O')
SGS Colt Browning_Hi-Power 9mm the Llama Omni45
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1911', 'CD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('magazine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Browning_Hi-Power', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magazine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Llama', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Omni', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('magazine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'618_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Browning_Hi-Power the Llama Omni the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Llama', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Omni', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('handgun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O')
Llama Omni
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1 one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Findlay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David Findlay
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('differs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('implement', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('transition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handgun', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('widened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('grip_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('narrower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('intermediate_face_portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('converging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
