('412_F.3d_1284', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('PRIMA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('TEK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('II', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
PRIMA TEK II
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Southpac_Trust_International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Trustee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Family_Trust_U/T/A', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('dated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('12/8/95', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('POLYPAP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.A.R.L.', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Philippe_Charrin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Andre_Charrin', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Southpac_Trust_International Inc. Trustee 12/8/95 Appellants Andre_Charrin
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._04-1411', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('04-1421', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('June_22,_2005', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Aug._31,_2005', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('decorative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('assemblies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('flower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arrangements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Southern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reagan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('316_F.Supp.2d_693', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('induced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contributory_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Southern District Illinois Michael J. Reagan J. 316_F.Supp.2d_693
__NEW_SENT__
('Parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cross-appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1285', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Titterington', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunlap', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Codding', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rogers', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Oklahoma', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Oklahoma', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Joseph P. Titterington Oklahoma City Oklahoma
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('McKenzie', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David I. Roche Baker Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DYK', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Polypap', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.A.R.L.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Philippe_Charrin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Andre_Charrin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._5410,856', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'856_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._5615,532', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'532_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enjoining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('instructing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')
Andre_Charrin Polypap 15 United_States_Patent_No._5410,856 9 Polypap Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('Prima_Tek_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sarl', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('316_F.Supp.2d_693', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.III.2004', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Prima_Tek_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Southpac_Trust_International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Trustee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Family_Trust_U/T/A', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('dated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('12/8/95', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Prima_Tek', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('induced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contributory_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Southpac_Trust_International Inc. Trustee 12/8/95 Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'856", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'532_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moot', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Prima_Tek', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O')
Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('Polypap', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('French', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Bouquett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('O', 'XX', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
French the United States Bouquett
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semicircular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('piece', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disposable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('floral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arrangements', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_29,_1999', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Prima_Tek', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1286', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'856_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'532_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
March_29,_1999 Polypap 15 9
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('Prima_Tek_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.A.R.L.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('318_F.3d_1143', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1145', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1145
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('incorrect', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('1154', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Id.at 1154
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('floral_holding_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('peripheral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floral_holding_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('constructed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floral_grouping', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floral_grouping', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('floral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('foam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('soil', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1149', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1152', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
1149 1152
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('instructing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')
Polypap Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Prima_Tek', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('induced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contributory_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Polypap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Prima_Tek', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Polypap
__NEW_SENT__
('Polypap', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Prima_Tek', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('induced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contributory_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
