('522_F.3d_1299', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('POWEROASIS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_Networks', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('T-MOBILE', 'CD', '', 'O') ('USA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
POWEROASIS INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2007-1265', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_11,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Aug._13,_2008', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('telecommunications_access', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Hampshire', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Barbadoro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2007_WL_962937', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Hampshire Paul Barbadoro J. 2007_WL_962937
__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Moore Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('come', 'VB', '', 'O') ('forward', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entitlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('asserted_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CIP', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('user_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('remotely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('laptop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('effective_filing_date', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('user_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unitary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vending', 'NN', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')
continuation-in-part
__NEW_SENT__
('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('original_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possession', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inherently', 'RB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('narrower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1301', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Sibley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reppert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lahive', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cockfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Sibley P. Reppert Lahive & Cockfield LLP Boston Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scofield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cutler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pickering', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hale', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dorr', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
William A. Scofield Jr. William F. Lee Wilmer Cutler Pickering Hale Dorr LLP Boston Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bassett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('O.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
David B. Bassett Amr O. Aly New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN SCHALL
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MOORE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_Networks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Hampshire', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'GPE', 'I') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('18', 'CD', '', 'O') ('31', 'CD', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', '', 'O') ('38', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('49', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._6466,658', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'658_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('6,721,400', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'400_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
MOORE Circuit_Judge PowerOasis Inc. PowerOasis_Networks LLC PowerOasis United_States_District_Court the District of New_Hampshire 's 15 38 40 and 49 U.S. 6,721,400 35 102
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('120', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benefit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('original_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O')
two 35 120 PowerOasis 35
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬658_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('telecommunications_access', 'NN', '', 'O')
two ¡¬658_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('virtually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specifications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PowerOasis_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('enables', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('connect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('laptop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telecommunications', 'NN', '', 'O') ('channel', 'NN', '', 'O')
PowerOasis_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬658', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filing_dates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('15', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
¡¬658 November 6 2001 October 15 2002
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬658', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬658
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Original_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._5812,643', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'643_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
first February 6 1997 U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬643_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
PowerOasis ¡¬643_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('18', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abandoned', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_15,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('CIP_Application', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6314,169', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'169_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
PowerOasis September 18 1998 2000 CIP_Application U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬169_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬169_patent PowerOasis
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('CIP_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('considerable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
2000
__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('T-Mobile', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*1302', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._05-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('cv-42-PB', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_962937', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*2', 'FW', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.N.H', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B')
PowerOasis Inc. T-Mobile *1302 USA Inc. D.N.H
__NEW_SENT__
('Mar._30,_2007', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬658_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬400_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
PowerOasis two two first
__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('T-Mobile', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('T-Mobile', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('HotSpot', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Network', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('18', 'CD', '', 'O') ('31', 'CD', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', '', 'O') ('38', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('49', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
PowerOasis T-Mobile T-Mobile `` HotSpot Network '' 1 15 38 40 and 49 PowerOasis_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('Each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
1 PowerOasis
__NEW_SENT__
('Except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('minor', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('variations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
PowerOasis_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('telecommunications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('channel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('payment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obtaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('initiate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('transaction', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indicating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('status', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electronic_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('transaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telecommunications_channel_access_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('external_telecommunications_channel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('external_telecommunications_channel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beginning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('transaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('transaction', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('telecommunications', 'NN', '', 'O') ('channel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('telecommunications_channel_access_circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('external', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telecommunications', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
at least one at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('payment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('controlling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('electronic_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('telecommunications_channel_access_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('enables', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('passed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hardware', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disagreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('location', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('laptop', 'NN', '', 'O')
PowerOasis
__NEW_SENT__
('T-Mobile', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('entirely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('CIP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('encompasses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('laptop', 'NN', '', 'O')
2000 PowerOasis
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('T-Mobile', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MobileStar_Network', 'NNP', '', 'O')
customer_interface '' T-Mobile
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_15,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MobileStar_Networks', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acquired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('T-Mobile', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('deployed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('publicly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MobileStar_Network', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high-speed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wireless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O')
T-Mobile 2002 MobileStar_Network
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_15,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MobileStar_Network', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1303', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('features', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('form', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('T-Mobile', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('HotSpot', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Network', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PowerOasis
__NEW_SENT__
('T-Mobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('offer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_15,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('CIP_Application2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('constituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PowerOasis_patents', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
more than one year 2000 ¡± 102 PowerOasis_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 102
__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benefit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('going', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Original_Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('antedate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MobileStar_Network', 'NN', '', 'O')
PowerOasis February 6 1997
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Original_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Original_Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Original_Application
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('arrive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('accorded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('customer_interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('exclusively', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('CIP_Application', 'NN', '', 'O')
2000
__NEW_SENT__
('PowerOasis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('2007_WL_962937', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*8', 'FW', '', 'O')
PowerOasis
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬658', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('400', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective_filing_date', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Original_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬658
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
