('225_F.3d_1315', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('PERSEPTIVE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('BIOSYSTEMS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PHARMACIA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BIOTECH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmacia_Biotech_AS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sepracor_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmacia_LBK_Biotechnology_AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Biosepra', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia_Biotech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Biopress', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technology', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Procordia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
PHARMACIA BIOTECH INC. Sepracor_Inc. Pharmacia_LBK_Biotechnology_AB Biosepra Inc. Pharmacia_Biotech Pharmacia Biopress Technology Procordia AB
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1325', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._29,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('En', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Banc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Declined', 'VBD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nov._22,_2000', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing En Banc Declined Nov._22,_2000
__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high-speed_chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('perfusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('incorrect', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('correct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patti', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Saris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('12_F.Supp.2d_69', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('correct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
the District of Massachusetts B. Saris J. 12_F.Supp.2d_69 the Patent and Trademark_Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('falsehoods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Clevenger Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pauline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Pauline Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1317', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Henderson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Farabow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Garrett', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dunner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Donald R. Dunner Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jenkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas H. Jenkins
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blackman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Scott H. Blackman
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Godkin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sanders', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Testa', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hurwitz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Thibeault', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
David S. Godkin David C. Berry Richard S. Sanders Hurwitz & Thibeault LLP Boston Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Carl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bromberg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bromberg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sunstein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Lee Carl Bromberg Bromberg & Sunstein LLP Boston Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pierce', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Atwood', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Portland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Maine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert H. Stier Jr. Portland Maine
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Adamo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Day', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pogue', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cleveland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Kenneth R. Adamo Jones Reavis & Pogue Cleveland Ohio
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN PLAGER CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PAULINE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('PerSeptive_Biosystems', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patents', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Nos._5019,270', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'270_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('5,228,989', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'989_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5,384,042', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'042_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
PerSeptive_Biosystems Inc. PerSeptive the District of Massachusetts PerSeptive United States Patents 5,228,989 5,384,042 the United States Patent and Trademark_Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia_Biotech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmacia_Biotech_AS', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sepracor_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmacia_LBK_Biotechnology_AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Biosepra', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'270", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'989_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'042_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
1993 PerSeptive Pharmacia_Biotech Inc. Sepracor_Inc. Pharmacia_LBK_Biotechnology_AB and Biosepra Inc. Pharmacia 1995 PerSeptive
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('concerned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high-speed_chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('separation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('biological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('perfusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'270_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('practicing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('perfusive_chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'989_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('perfusive_chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'042_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matrix', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('perfusive_chromatography', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('list', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Noubar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Afeyan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Professor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fred', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Regnier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Dean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
three Noubar Afeyan Fred Regnier Robert Dean
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('name', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('practiced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O')
PerSeptive Pharmacia
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cross-motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1318', 'FW', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('list', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_Biosystems', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia_Biotech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._93-12237', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('32-33', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Mass', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Pharmacia_Biotech Inc. No._93-12237
__NEW_SENT__
('Jan._9,_1996', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jan._9,_1996 PerSeptive
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('incorrect', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('genuinely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unnamed_inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deceptive_intent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('precluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('then-current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('understanding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('256', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Pharmacia 35 256 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('slip', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('31', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('T', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('remains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mind', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preventing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('256', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('correct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PerSeptive section 256
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ten-day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('correct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('basing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pattern', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('false', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('timing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
March 1997 PerSeptive
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_Biosystems', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia_Biotech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._93-12237', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('126', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Mass', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Pharmacia_Biotech Inc. No._93-12237
__NEW_SENT__
('Mar._31,_1997', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_II', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Soon', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Stark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Advanced', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Magnetics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('119_F.3d_1551', 'IN', '', 'O') ('43_USPQ2d_1321_(Fed.Cir.1997)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Federal_Circuit Stark Advanced Magnetics Inc. 43_USPQ2d_1321_(Fed.Cir.1997)
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stark', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('256', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('authorizes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('correction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('deceptive_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inquiry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('originally-named', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Stark 256
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('understanding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('reconsidered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_II', 'ADD', '', 'O')
January 1998
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_Biosystems', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia_Biotech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('12_F.Supp.2d_69', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('70', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Mass.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_III', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Pharmacia_Biotech Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_III', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('256', 'CD', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unnamed_inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PerSeptive
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('71', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
71
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reexamine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('factual_findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Pharmacia
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('71', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
71
__NEW_SENT__
('Adopting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual_findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('prosecuting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('yielded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('73', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
73
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('54', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
54
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('PerSeptive_Biosystems', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pharmacia_Biotech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._93-12237', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('slip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Mass', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Pharmacia_Biotech Inc. No._93-12237
__NEW_SENT__
('Mar._13,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1 1994
__NEW_SENT__
