('597_F.3d_1288', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('RICHARDSON', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('STANLEY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('WORKS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellee', 'VBN', '', 'O')
David A. RICHARDSON STANLEY WORKS INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2009-1354', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('March_9,_2010', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('May_24,_2010', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('design_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('multi-function', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carpentry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conventional_hammer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stud', 'NN', '', 'O') ('climbing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('crowbar', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arizona', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Neil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wake', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('610_F.Supp.2d_1046', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Arizona Neil V. Wake J. 610_F.Supp.2d_1046
__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('factored', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('functional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('demand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('untimely', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1290', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Geoffrey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kercsmar', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kercsmar', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Feltus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Scottsdale', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('AZ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Geoffrey S. Kercsmar Kercsmar & Feltus PLLC of Scottsdale
__NEW_SENT__
('Bryan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Collins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pillsbury', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Winthrop', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Shaw', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pittman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('McLean', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bryan P. Collins McLean VA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fuhrer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kathy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Peng', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert M. Fuhrer Kathy Peng
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('KENDALL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
LOURIE DYK Circuit_Judges KENDALL
__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Richardson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arizona', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
David Richardson United_States_District_Court District Arizona
__NEW_SENT__
('Richardson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stanley_Works', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('610_F.Supp.2d_1046', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Ariz.2009', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stanley_Works', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('D507,167', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬167_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Stanley_Works Inc. Stanley U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Richardson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬167_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multi-function', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carpentry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('combines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conventional_hammer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stud', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('climbing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crowbar', 'NN', '', 'O')
Richardson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Stepclaw', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Stepclaw
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬167_patent', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ornamental', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
¡¬167_patent 1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('*1291.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('FIG.1', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('FIG.2', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Stanley', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('manufactures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tools', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Stanley
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tools', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Fubar', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
2005 Stanley U.S. Fubar
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fubar', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carpentry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('demolition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fubar five
__NEW_SENT__
('Stanley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('successfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('D562,101', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬101_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Fubar', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
Stanley U.S. Patent D562,101 Fubar
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('built', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Fubar', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
five Fubar
__NEW_SENT__
('Figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬101_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('illustrative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Fubar', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
Fubar
__NEW_SENT__
