('864_F.3d_1343', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('REGENERON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MERUS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('N.V.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2016-1346', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('July_27,_2017', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('modifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('eukaryotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-01650-KBF', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('Katherine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Forrest', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('144_F.Supp.3d_530', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Katherine B. Forrest J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genetically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('modified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mouse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('germline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unrearranged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('variable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gene', 'NN', '', 'O') ('segments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('inserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('endogenous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mouse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('immunoglobulin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('locus', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mouse', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('international', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chimeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('transgenic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('animals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antibodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but-for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior_journal_article', 'FW', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('targeted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('insertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gene', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immunoglobulin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heavy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('locus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but-for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior_journal_article', 'FW', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cre-loxp-mediated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('gene', 'NN', '', 'O') ('replacement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but-for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drawing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse_inference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('withheld', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O')
the District Court the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('*1346', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (':14-cv-01650-KBF', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Katherine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Forrest', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court No._1 Katherine B. Forrest
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('NEAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('KUMAR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('KATYAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hogan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Lovells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('US', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
NEAL KUMAR KATYAL Hogan US LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CHRISTOPHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('BORELLO', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MICHAEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ENZO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('FURROW', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('BRENDAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('M.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("O'MALLEY", 'NN', '', 'O') ('ROBERT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SETH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SCHWARTZ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
CHRISTOPHER P. BORELLO
__NEW_SENT__
('PATRICIA', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('CARSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
PATRICIA A. CARSON Kirkland & Ellis
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SAUNAK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DESAI', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('AARON', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('RESETARITS', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('JOHN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'QUINN", 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('PETER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('B.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SILVERMAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Merus', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('US', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cambridge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
SAUNAK AARON D. RESETARITS JOHN C. O'QUINN Washington DC US
__NEW_SENT__
('KEVIN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('EDWARD', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NOONAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McDonnell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Boehnen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hulbert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Berghoff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amicus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Curiae', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Seven', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lawyers', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
KEVIN EDWARD McDonnell Boehnen Hulbert & Berghoff LLP Chicago Amicus Curiae Chicago Patent Lawyers
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JEFFREY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PALMER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ARMSTRONG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('AARON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('VINCENT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('GIN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('JAMES', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('LEE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LOVSIN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('JEREMY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('E.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NOE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ANDREW', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('W.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WILLIAMS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DONALD', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('LOUIS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ZUHN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('JR.', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Prost', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wallach', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
JEFFREY GIN JAMES LEE Wallach Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Circuit Newman
__NEW_SENT__
('Prost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Regeneron_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._8502,018', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'018_patent", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron_Pharmaceuticals Inc. Regeneron U.S. Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('engaged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'018_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2014', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Merus_B.V.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Merus', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'018_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
March 2014 Regeneron Merus_B.V. Merus
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Regeneron_Pharm.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Merus_B.V.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4-cv-1650', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2014_WL_6611510_(S.D.N.Y._Nov._21,_2014)', '.', '', 'O')
See Regeneron_Pharm. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('declared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'JJ', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*23-24', 'NN', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('Merus', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prosecutors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('withheld', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Withheld_References', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'018_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Regeneron four the U.S. Patent and Trademark_Office
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third-party', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('patent_prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('European', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('opposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('briefs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but-for', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('withheld', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Merus U.S. European Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('knew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Withheld_References', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'018_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Regeneron Withheld_References
__NEW_SENT__
('Regeneron', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('but-for', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cumulative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('actually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'RP', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scheduled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bifurcated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Withheld_References', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron two Withheld_References second
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Therasense', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Becton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dickinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('649_F.3d_1276', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1287', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
See Therasense Inc. Becton Dickinson & Co. 1287 Fed
__NEW_SENT__
('Cir', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2011
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lengthy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('detailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Withheld_References', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('*1347', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Regeneron_Pharm.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Merus_B.V.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('144_F.Supp.3d_530', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron_Pharm. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')1', 'XX', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('never', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scheduled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
2015 second Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_bench_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exhaustively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misconduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('throughout', 'IN', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sanctioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drawing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse_inference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('repeated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('violations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('orders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('improper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('secreting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('non-privileged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('documents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('misconduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse_inference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Withheld_References', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('Having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('but-for', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Withheld_References', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drawn', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse_inference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('specific_intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'018_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Withheld_References Regeneron Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('Regeneron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Regeneron
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
