('212_F.3d_1365', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('RIVERWOOD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MEAD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Plaintiff-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1274', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('May_17,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('June_22,_2000', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cartoners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('group_articles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('load', 'VB', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('paperboard_cartons', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Georgia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Moye', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Georgia Charles A. Moye Jr.
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Mayer Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1365', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Wellington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Manning', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dority', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Manning', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Greenville', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('South', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Carolina', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wellington M. Manning Jr. Dority & Manning P.A. Greenville South Carolina
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Neil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Killen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Neil C. Jones Craig N. Killen
__NEW_SENT__
('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Coll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Orrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Herrington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sutcliffe', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
J. Peter Coll Jr. New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murtha', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kristen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Bancroft', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James J. Murtha Kristen Bancroft
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Edell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert T. Edell Robert J
__NEW_SENT__
('Glance', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Merchant', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gould', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Glance Merchant & Gould Minneapolis
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
GAJARSA Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MAYER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mead', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Mead', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Georgia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mead', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._5241,806', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'806_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Riverwood_International', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Riverwood', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Mead Corporation Mead United_States_District_Court Northern_District Georgia Mead 1_and_13 U.S. Patent No._5241,806 Riverwood_International Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Riverwood_Int', 'FW', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mead_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':94-CV-0090-CAM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ga', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Jan._13,_1999', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jan._13,_1999 Order
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erroneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1366', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cartoners', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cartoners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('group_articles', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('beverage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cans', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bottles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('load', 'VB', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('paperboard_cartons', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cartoners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('usually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('industrial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('beverage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bottling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('facilities', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Riverwood', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'806_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('embodied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('practice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('TwinStack', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O')
TwinStack
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'806_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1 13
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cartoner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('incoming', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('streams', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('barrel_cam_loader', 'NN', '', 'O')
two three
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cartoner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three-conveyer_cartoner', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('loader', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('usually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('barrel_cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('guide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('forces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cartons', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('barrel_cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pushes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('horizontal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('escalator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('guide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('works', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('passively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('merely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('static', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('divert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('path', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('propelled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mead', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('marketed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('DuoStack', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three-conveyer_cartoner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('barrel_cam_loader', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Riverwood', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'806_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Mead DuoStack barrel_cam_loader Riverwood
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appointed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Civil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Procedure', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('53', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hear', 'VB', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Federal Rule of Civil Procedure 53
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1_and_13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'806_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1_and_13
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Riverwood_Int', 'FW', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mead_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':94-CV-0090-CAM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ga', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Mar._11,_1998', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Report', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Mar._11,_1998 Report
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accepted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('modification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special_master', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('Mead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
