('778_F.3d_1311', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SOVERAIN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SOFTWARE', 'VB', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('VICTORIA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'S", 'POS', '', 'O') ('SECRET', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DIRECT', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('BRAND', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MANAGEMENT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Avon_Products', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2012-1649', 'RB', '', 'O') ('2012-1650', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Feb._12,_2015', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('virtual_shopping_carts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hypertext_statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('permit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('access', 'VB', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('past', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('orders', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2011_WL_111869', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('899_F.Supp.2d_574', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United States District Court Texas Leonard Davis
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fair', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opportunity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('litigate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('independent_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('collaterally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dependent_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1312', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lamken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MoloLamken', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jeffrey A. Lamken MoloLamken LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anastasia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fernands', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Emanuel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Urquhart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nelson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ellsworth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quillin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Baluch', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lardner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert B. Wilson Anastasia M. Fernands Quinn Emanuel Urquhart & Sullivan LLP New_York NY David A. Nelson Chicago IL George Ellsworth Andrew S. Baluch Foley & Lardner LLP Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('*1313', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rhoad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dechert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Princeton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Victoria', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Secret_Direct_Brand_Management', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert Rhoad Dechert LLP Victoria
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ruhland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ashbrook', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Masterson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Epstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mountain', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('View', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Christopher S. Ruhland Los Angeles CA Robert W. Ashbrook Jr. Robert Louis Masterson Philadelphia PA Daniel B. Epstein
__NEW_SENT__
('Daryl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Joseffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('King', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Spalding', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Avon_Products', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conrad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Charlotte', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Gaston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kroub', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Locke', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lord', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Daryl L. Joseffer King & Spalding LLP Avon_Products Inc. Adam M. Conrad Charlotte NC Gaston Kroub
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('TARANTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HUGHES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DYK', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Victoria', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Secret_Direct_Brand_Management', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Victoria', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Secret', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Avon_Products', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Avon', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Victoria LLC Victoria 's Secret '' Avon the District Court Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('34_and_51', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5715,314', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5909,492', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
15 17 and 39
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Soverain_Software_LLC', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newegg_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('705_F.3d_1333_(Fed.Cir.2013)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reh', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", '``', '', 'O') ('g', 'NN', '', 'O') ('728_F.3d_1332', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1336', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2013', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Newegg', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1336 Newegg
__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('34_and_51', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('41', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('61', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
34_and_51 ¡¬314_patent 17 41 and
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1341', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1344', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
1341 1344
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue_preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Newegg', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Newegg
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Soverain_Software_LLC', 'XX', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Soverain', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Soverain Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('fall', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('34_and_51', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('virtual_shopping_carts.BIG_TOKEN__1_Claims_15__BIG_TOKEN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1314', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hypertext_statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('access', 'VB', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('past', 'NN', '', 'O') ('orders.2', 'PRP', '', 'O')
¡¬314_patent 17 39
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('18', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
November 18 2011
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Soverain', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Soverain
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
September 7 2012
__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2013', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Newegg', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Soverain', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('There', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
January 22 2013 Newegg Texas Soverain
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('34_and_51', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('41', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('61', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬492_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
34_and_51 ¡¬314_patent 17 41 and
__NEW_SENT__
('Newegg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('705_F.3d_1333', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1347', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Newegg 705_F.3d_1333 1347
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('clarified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
35
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('confirm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ed', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'shopping", 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cart', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dependent_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
34 35 35
__NEW_SENT__
('Soverain_Software_LLC', 'VB', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newegg_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('728_F.3d_1332', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1336', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2013', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Newegg', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')3', '.', '', 'O')
1336 Newegg II
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('regional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue_preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applies', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Del.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pac', 'NN', '', 'O')
RF Del. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Keystone', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('326_F.3d_1255', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1261', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Keystone Techs. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('precedent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('substantive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue_preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('implicate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substantive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue_preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('implicate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('previous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decisions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ohio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Willow', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wood', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alps', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('735_F.3d_1333', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1342', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2013', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Aspex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Eyewear', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Zenni', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Optical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('713_F.3d_1377', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1380', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2013', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Ohio Willow Wood Co. Alps S. LLC Aspex Eyewear Inc. Zenni Optical Inc. 1380
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('T', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('collateral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('de', 'FW', '', 'O') ('novo', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bradberry', 'VB', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Jefferson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cnty.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tex.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('732_F.3d_540', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('549', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5th', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Cir.2013', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jefferson Cnty. 732_F.3d_540 549
__NEW_SENT__
