('336_F.3d_1298', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SUNRACE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ROOTS', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ENTERPRISE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CO.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LTD.', ',', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sun_Victory_Trading_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SRAM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
SUNRACE Sun_Victory_Trading_Co. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._02-1524', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_17,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bicycle_gear-shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Vaughn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Walker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of R. Walker J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1299', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Darin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Snyder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Melveny", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Myers', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Darin W. Snyder O'Melveny & Myers LLP San Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laura', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bremer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lori', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Behun', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Steven L. Smith Laura C. Bremer Lori L. Behun
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Walsh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lewis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rice', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fingersh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('St.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('MO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Richard B. Walsh Jr. St. Louis
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Janoski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grady', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hickey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Frank B. Janoski Keith J. Grady Michael J. Hickey
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('SRAM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('SunRace', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Roots', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Enterprise', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sun_Victory_Trading_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('SunRace', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SRAM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bicycle_gear-shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SRAM Corporation United_States_District_Court Northern_District California SunRace Roots Enterprise Co. Ltd. Sun_Victory_Trading_Co. Inc. SunRace
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SRAM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SRAM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._4900,291', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬291_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('produces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('shift_actuators', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('twist-shifters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bicycle_rider', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('change', 'VB', '', 'O') ('gears', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('twisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handlebar', 'NN', '', 'O')
I. SRAM U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bicycle_gear-shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('typically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shifter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('near', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handlebars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('connects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shifter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬291_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gear-shifting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('multi-speed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bicycles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('effect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('precise', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬291_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('indexed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bicycle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('precise', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('effect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gear', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shift', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('One', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('indexed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('implemented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('twist-shifter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O')
One
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cylindrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handlebar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('peaks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('valleys', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('interacts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rotated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬291_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('handgrip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('handgrip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indexing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('employ', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬291_patent 16
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬291_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬291_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rotatably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handlebar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bicycle_rider', 'NN', '', 'O') ('need', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('remove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('hands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handlebar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('shift', 'VB', '', 'O') ('gears', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('*1300', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('handgrip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('embodying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('helical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('defines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('movements', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('compensates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cumulative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shifter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('take', 'VB', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('slack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('begins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('precise', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('index', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('produces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('optimum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('overshift', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('down-shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('manual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('define', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overshift', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Overshifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beyond', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('destination_sprocket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('destination_sprocket', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('¡¬291_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._52-55', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('essence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('farther', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('derailleur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('easily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aligned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sprocket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('down-shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pplicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accurate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('index', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('th', 'XX', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cumulative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('actual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shift', 'NN', '', 'O') ('increment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('travel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sprockets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('down-shifting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('event', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Applicant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aware', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬291_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._61-67', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('down-shifting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('sprocket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('larger_sprocket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shift_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('takes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cumulative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('transfers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('larger_sprocket', 'NN', '', 'O')
16 first
__NEW_SENT__
