('780_F.3d_1337', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SENJU', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kyorin_Pharmaceutical_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Allergan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SENJU PHARMACEUTICAL CO. Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LUPIN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LIMITED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lupin_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LUPIN LIMITED Lupin_Pharmaceuticals Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Hi-Tech_Pharmacal_Co.', 'UH', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', 'ORG', 'I')
Hi-Tech_Pharmacal_Co. Inc. Defendant-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2013-1630', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('March_20,_2015', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gatifloxacin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('topical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ophthalmic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Sue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('836_F.Supp.2d_196', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('adjudged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Sue L. Robinson J. 836_F.Supp.2d_196
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plager', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Plager Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('District_Court', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unexpected_results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('increase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corneal_permeability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('surprising', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('routine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('optimization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('District_Court', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unexpected_results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1338', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perry', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gibson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dunn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Crutcher', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mark Andrew
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Irvine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lucas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Townsend', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kelly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jonah', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('West', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('G.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Oblon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Spivak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McClelland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Maier', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Alexandria', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('VA.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Deanne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mazzochi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rakoczy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Molino', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mazzochi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Siwik', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees_Lupin_Limited', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lupin_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rakoczy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Molino', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anuj', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kumar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wadhwa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Polivick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jeffrey T. Thomas Irvine C. Townsend Washington DC Richard D. Kelly Deanne M. Mazzochi Chicago defendants-appellees_Lupin_Limited Lupin_Pharmaceuticals Inc. William A. Rakoczy Paul J. Molino Anuj Kumar Wadhwa John Polivick Brian Peter Murray
__NEW_SENT__
('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Castellano', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shaw', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Keller', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech_Pharmacal_Co.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Karen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Locke', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lord', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Jeffrey T. Castellano Wilmington DE Hi-Tech_Pharmacal_Co. Inc. Karen E. Keller Steven D. Roth New York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN PLAGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('PLAGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman_Act', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pub.L', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-417', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("98_Stat._1585_(``the_Act'')", 'CD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Act', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Senju_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kyorin_Pharmaceutical_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Allergan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees_Lupin_Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lupin_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Lupin', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech_Pharmacal_Co.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6_and_12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-16', ':', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._6333,045', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Kyorin_Pharmaceutical_Co. Ltd. Allergan Inc. Senju Lupin Hi-Tech_Pharmacal_Co. Inc. Hi-Tech 6_and_12 U.S. the ¡¬045_patent ``
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('*1339', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('adjudged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Sue L. Robinson
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment.1', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('INTRODUCTION', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('gatifloxacin', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('disodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edetate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('EDTA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition
__NEW_SENT__
('Seven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior_art_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_chemistry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Seven
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same_chemistry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('vary', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('all', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('before', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Three the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case-constructive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('countered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-are', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('familiar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Yet', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemistry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complex', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('address', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('detail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('believe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('saliency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outcome', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
first 2007
__NEW_SENT__
('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman_Act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Allergan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('gatifloxacin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ZymarTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
Apotex Corp. Apotex Abbreviated New Drug Application the Food and Drug Administration FDA Allergan
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ZymarTHE_R', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Approved', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Therapeutic', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'I') ('Equivalence', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'EVENT', 'B') ('``', '``', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Orange', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Book', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ("''", "''", 'EVENT', 'I')
ZymarTHE_R FDA Approved Drug Products With Therapeutic Equivalence the `` Orange Book ''
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-BIG_TOKEN__3_and_6__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-9', ':', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
2010
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6_and_7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enablement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('Senju_Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('717_F.Supp.2d_404', 'CD', '', 'O') ('433', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2010', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('``', '.', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Senju_Pharm Co. 433
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alternatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('amend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reopened', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('consider', 'VB', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
7 7
__NEW_SENT__
('Thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O')
2011 7
__NEW_SENT__
('Senju_Pharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('836_F.Supp.2d_196', 'CD', '', 'O') ('210-11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2011', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
210-11
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('affirmance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Senju_Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('485_Fed.Appx._433_(Fed.Cir.2012)', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
7 Senju_Pharm Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('Meanwhile', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('petitioned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ex-parte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('re-examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
February 2011 Senju the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('notify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('re-examination', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1340', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('re-examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('informed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certificate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('cancelled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-BIG_TOKEN__3_and_8__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-11', ':', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1216', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
October 2011 6 1216
__NEW_SENT__
('Then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Senju Apotex first
__NEW_SENT__
('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('res', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judicata', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim_preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('referring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('civil', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procedure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concept', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('Ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('gave', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim_preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent-at-issue', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cause', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('previous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Apotex Senju
__NEW_SENT__
('Senju_Pharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('891_F.Supp.2d_656', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('662', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2012', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
662
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('upheld', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Senju_Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('746_F.3d_1344_(Fed.Cir.2014)', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
the Federal_Circuit Senju_Pharm Co. Apotex II
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('going', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lupin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech_defendants', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman_Act', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6_and_12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-16', ':', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lupin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('earlier-filed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._202-653', 'RB', '', 'O') ('0.5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_gatifloxacin', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('202-709', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('w/v', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('%_gatifloxacin', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._203189', 'RB', '', 'O') ('0.5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_gatifloxacin', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('203190', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('0.3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_gatifloxacin', 'NN', '', 'O')
Senju 2011 Lupin second Apotex Senju 6_and_12 Lupin %_gatifloxacin 202-709 %_gatifloxacin Hi-Tech %_gatifloxacin 203190
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Lupin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech_defendants', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('copies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('gatifloxacin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ophthalmic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lupin Hi-Tech_defendants FDA Senju FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Lupin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pleadings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('narrower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('collaterally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relitigating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Lupin Apotex 3
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lupin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('succeed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Senju', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('1', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('2', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('litigations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('litigated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.01', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%', 'NN', '', 'O') ('EDTA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('collateral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply.BIG_TOKEN__3_J.A._7__BIG_TOKEN', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lupin Senju the Apotex 1 & 2 0.01
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gatifloxacin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('EDTA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('utilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
EDTA
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('April_21,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')
¡¬045_patent 's U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('raising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('corneal_permeability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('eye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('incorporating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('*BIG_TOKEN__1341_about_0__BIG_TOKEN01', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('w/v', 'RB', '', 'O') ('%_disodium_edetate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('eye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gatifloxacin Gatifloxacin above 5 about 6 about 0.3 about 0.8 %_Gatifloxacin Gatifloxacin
__NEW_SENT__
('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
12
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.01', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('w/v', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('%_disodium_edetate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
about 0.3 about 0.8 %_Gatifloxacin about 0.01 about 5 about 6
__NEW_SENT__
('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
13
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O')
aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition 12 about 0.3 %_Gatifloxacin
__NEW_SENT__
('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
14
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('w/v', 'NN', '', 'O') ('%_Gatifloxacin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O')
aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition 12 about 0.5 %_Gatifloxacin
__NEW_SENT__
('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
15
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('isotonic_agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sodium_chloride', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potassium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('glycerin', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('mannitol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('glucose', 'NN', '', 'O')
aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition 12 at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
16
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('isotonic_agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sodium_chloride', 'JJ', '', 'O')
aqueous_liquid_pharmaceutical_eye_drop_composition 14 at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reexamination', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Certificate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1:25-2:24', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2702', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
2702
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('reserved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ultimate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lupin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hi-Tech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamined_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6_and_12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-16', ':', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬045_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Lupin Hi-Tech 6_and_12
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('U.S.C.¡±¡±', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
under 28 2 1295
__NEW_SENT__
