('242_F.3d_1337', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SCIMED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LIFE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('SYSTEMS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADVANCED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CARDIOVASCULAR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('SYSTEMS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
SCIMED LIFE SYSTEMS INC. ADVANCED CARDIOVASCULAR SYSTEMS INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1499', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
No._99-1499
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('March_14,_2001', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('balloon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dilation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coronary_angioplasty_procedures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jenkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('1999_WL_398003', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District California Martin J. Jenkins J. 1999_WL_398003
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('common_specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inflation_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('guide_wire_lumen', 'CD', '', 'O') ('disclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lumens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dyk', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1338', 'UH', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('West', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howrey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Simon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
William K. West Jr. Howrey Simon Arnold & White LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ruyak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jerrold', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ganzfried', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Celine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Callahan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James F. Davis Robert F. Ruyak Celine T. Callahan
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gafner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('SciMed_Life_Systems', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Maple', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Grove', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Peter J. Gafner SciMed_Life_Systems Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Philip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Levin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malinoski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bonella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Woodcock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washburn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kurtz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mackiewicz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Norris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('PA.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Held', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Malloy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Philip S. Johnson Gary H. Levin Lynn A. Malinoski Michael J. Bonella Philadelphia Edward A. Mas II Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hampton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vander', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leest', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McCaulley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Surrette', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Timothy J. Malloy Steven J. Hampton Kirk A. Vander Leest Richard T. McCaulley Jr. Robert A. Surrette
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vogler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Headrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gregory J. Vogler David D. Headrick
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('SciMed_Life_Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('SciMed', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('drawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('balloon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dilatation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._5156,594', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('594', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('5,217,482', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬482_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5,395,334', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬334_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
SciMed_Life_Systems Inc. SciMed three U.S. U.S. 594 5,217,482 5,395,334
__NEW_SENT__
('SciMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Advanced', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Cardiovascular', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('*1339', 'IN', '', 'O') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SciMed Advanced Cardiovascular Systems Inc. ACS United_States_District_Court Northern_District California ACS three
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ACS ACS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SciMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ACS ACS SciMed
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Balloon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dilatation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coronary_angioplasty_procedures', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('remove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('restrictions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coronary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arteries', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SciMed_patents', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('describe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_shaft_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_shaft_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transition_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
SciMed_patents three two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_shaft_section', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('long', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stiff', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('tubular', 'JJ', '', 'O')
first_shaft_section
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_shaft_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('flexible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balloon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inflated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('relieve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arterial_restriction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transition_section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_shaft_sections', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gradual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('transition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stiffness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('shaft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SciMed_patents', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('passageways', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lumens', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SciMed_patents two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide-wire_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('guide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arteries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('site', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arterial_restriction', 'NN', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arteries', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide-wire_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('threaded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('guide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arteries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coronary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('restriction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SciMed_patents', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proximal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('closer', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nearer', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('leading', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide-wire_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inflation_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('terminates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balloon', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balloon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inflated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('forcing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inflation_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balloon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('compresses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('restricting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('artery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relieving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('restriction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('arrangements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lumens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('practiced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
only two two
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('lumen', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lumens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('side-by-side', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheter', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coaxial_lumen_configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_wire_lumen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('runs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inflation_lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inflation_lumen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('viewed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cross-section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('annular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('employ', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dual_lumen_configuration', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SciMed_patents', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('employs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coaxial_lumen_configuration', 'NN', '', 'O')
ACS SciMed_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('SciMed_patents', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coaxial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lumens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dual_lumen_configuration', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SciMed', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('specifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coaxial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
SciMed
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common_specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coaxial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lumen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sleeve', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contemplated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('herein', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('leaves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('no', 'RB', '', 'O') ('doubt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('skilled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('envisioned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1340', ',', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SciMed', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents-an', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intermediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sleeve', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lumens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('coaxially', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
only one SciMed
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('SciMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SciMed ACS
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lumen', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arrangements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('catheters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SciMed_patents', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two SciMed_patents
__NEW_SENT__
('SciMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O')
SciMed
__NEW_SENT__
