('164_F.3d_1372', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SPECTRUM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('STERILITE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
SPECTRUM INTERNATIONAL INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1243', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dec._9,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stackable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crates', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Whitman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knapp', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Whitman K. Knapp J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('merged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('top_edge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('examining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('harmless', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Clevenger Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1373', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Clement', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hedman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Gibson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Costigan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alan B. Clement Hedman Gibson & Costigan P.C. New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.M', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert S.M
__NEW_SENT__
('Gorman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gibson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gorman Thomas M. Gibson
__NEW_SENT__
('Ernest', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Linek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dike', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bronstein', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Roberts', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cushman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ernest V. Linek Boston Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
CLEVENGER SCHALL BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'UH', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Sterilite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Sterilite', 'VB', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('crates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_11', 'CD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._4971,202', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certificate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('B1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4,971,202', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('May_27,_1997', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Spectrum International Inc. Spectrum Sterilite Corporation 's Sterilite Spectrum U.S. November 20 1990 4,971,202 May_27,_1997
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('No._96-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CIV-8017', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('WK', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Jan._27,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sterilite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('crates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lie', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('albeit', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rationale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('articulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sterilite
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Stratoflex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Aeroquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('713_F.2d_1530', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1540', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('218_USPQ_871', 'CD', '', 'O') ('880', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1983', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('sit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('review', 'VB', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('opinions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Stratoflex Inc. Aeroquip Corp. 1540
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Titled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Stackable', 'VB', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Recycling', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Crate', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('box-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('walls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Stackable Recycling Crate '' four
__NEW_SENT__
("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Col.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('67-68', 'CD', '', 'O')
Col. 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('uncovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'202", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('walls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('back_wall', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alter', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('typical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1374', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('placement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('stacked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tandem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('kind', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'NN', '', 'O') ('retaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('confines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('once', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Two
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower_portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('cut', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('stacked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cut-out', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cut-out', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('easily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tapers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('incline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('joins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compartment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('laterally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('legs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower_portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('excised', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Second
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
16
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broadest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stackable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pair', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('opposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sidewalls', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('back_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sidewalls', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sidewalls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rectangularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'NN', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rectangularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('leg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('segment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top_edge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('leg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('segment', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
first second
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('planar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('back_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tapering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('merge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sidewalls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('back_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('define', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compartment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interior', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('apprised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Sterilite', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sterilite', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Storage_Cart', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
January 3 1994 Spectrum Sterilite Storage_Cart
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mailed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Spectrum the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protracted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('30-month', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ensued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('culminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Interferences', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('mailed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('July_26,_1996', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('affirming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
the Board of Patent Appeals Interferences 11 16 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('14-16', 'CD', '', 'O') ('survived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O')
2 11
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('14-16', 'CD', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pertinent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_11', 'CD', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('merge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_edge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'202_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Col.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('24-26', 'XX', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Col.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4-7.1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lodged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_crate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DePutter', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3682,351', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DePutter', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Col. 5 24-26 Col. 6 2_and_11 1 DePutter U.S. DePutter
__NEW_SENT__
('*BIG_TOKEN__1375_Figure_1__BIG_TOKEN', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rebut', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_crate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('merges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top_edge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central_portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('front_wall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom_edge', 'NN', '', 'O')
Spectrum
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sustained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('solely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O')
2_and_11
__NEW_SENT__
('Armed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('24', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Sterilite', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Storage_Cart', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (':', ':', '', 'O')
Board Spectrum October 24 1996 Sterilite 2_and_11 2
__NEW_SENT__
