('126_F.3d_1411', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
126_F.3d_1411
__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('STRATTEC', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('SECURITY', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GENERAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('AUTOMOTIVE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('SPECIALTY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('All-Lock_Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
STRATTEC Plaintiff-Appellee GENERAL AUTOMOTIVE SPECIALTY COMPANY INC. All-Lock_Company Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._96-1024', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
No._96-1024
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._16,_1997', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resistor_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Vehicle', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Anti-Theft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('VATS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('keys', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Vehicle Anti-Theft System VATS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hughes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The United States District Court Texas Lynn N. Hughes J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exceptional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rich Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1412', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Curfiss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Butler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Binion', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Houston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert C. Curfiss Butler & Binion L.L.P. Houston
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Paine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Louis Paine
__NEW_SENT__
('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schechter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Darby', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Darby', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Peter C. Schechter P.C. New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ira', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Levy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Ira Jay Levy
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RICH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('General_Automotive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Specialty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('All-Lock_Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1413', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('General_Automotive', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('decisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('General_Automotive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('after-market', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Security', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4250,482', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Packaged', 'VBN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Component', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Method', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Preparing', 'VBG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Same', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'482_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('General_Automotive', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O')
General_Automotive Specialty Company Inc. All-Lock_Company Inc. two the U.S. District Court 1 General_Automotive Strattec Security Corporation 's Strattec U.S. Patent `` Packaged Electronic Component and Method of Preparing the Same '' 2 Strattec
__NEW_SENT__
('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Security', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('General_Automotive', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Specialty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
Strattec Security Corp. General_Automotive Specialty Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('H-95-1031', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D', 'NNP', '', 'O')
H-95-1031
__NEW_SENT__
('Tex', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('16_Aug._1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('19_Sept._1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
16_Aug._1995 and 19_Sept._1995
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1978', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('General', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motors', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('asked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Allen-Bradley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A-B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('manufacturable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pellet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ignition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('keys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('equipped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Vehicle', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Anti-Theft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('VATS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')1', 'XX', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('VATS_keys', 'NNS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('operatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('VATS-equipped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ignition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O')
1978 General Motors Corporation GM the Allen-Bradley Company GM Vehicle Anti-Theft System VATS VATS_keys
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('on-board', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('temporarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disables', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ignition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('match', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('A-B', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('packaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O')
GM
__NEW_SENT__
('A-B', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'482_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('10_February_1981', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O')
A-B
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('A-B', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('27_February_1995', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Strattec 27_February_1995
__NEW_SENT__
('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equipment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supplier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VATS_keys', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('currently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cars', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Strattec GM VATS_keys GM
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('VATS_keys', 'NNPS', 'DATE', 'B') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('incorporate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pellet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'482_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('keys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('VATS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('key', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ignition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('steering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('column', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anti-theft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Strattec VATS_keys VATS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'482_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistor_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ("'482_patent", 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'LAW', 'I') ('Summary', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LAW', 'I') ('Invention', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electronic_chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('encapsulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('package', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('runner-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('leads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'VB', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inside', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ignition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
the '482_patent 's Summary of Invention GM
__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'482_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred_embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred_embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('perforated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ribbon', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('termination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('14_and_14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('punching', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stamping', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O')
16 14_and_14
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electronic_chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('integrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('soldered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('termination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('14_and_14', 'CD', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O')
13
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('over-molded', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('packaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fig.3d', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
11 Fig.3d
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('packaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exterior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('runner-like', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('12_and_12', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trimming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('encapsulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
12_and_12 10 1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('*1414.', 'UH', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lead', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('conducts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('electricity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electronic_chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('forms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('runner-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('leads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('12_and_12', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ("'", "''", '', 'O')
16 13 12_and_12
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('VATS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('encapsulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('orientation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('runner-like', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('protrudes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O')
Strattec VATS
__NEW_SENT__
('Strattec', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('6_April_1995', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('General_Automotive', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('just', 'RB', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('after-market', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('VATS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('work', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('VATS-equipped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cars', 'NNS', '', 'O')
6_April_1995 General_Automotive VATS GM
__NEW_SENT__
('General_Automotive', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('after-market', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('supply', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('replacement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('switches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('locks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
many years
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Strattec', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('accuses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'482_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('General_Automotive', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('complete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('VATS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('blank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistor_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('over-molded', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resistor_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Strattec VATS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistor_assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molded', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cylindrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('axial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('leads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('contacts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('round', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wire', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('leads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('respective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('positions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resistor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('wrapped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('around', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('soldered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('respective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wire', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
