('199_F.3d_1295', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('TORO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WHITE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CONSOLIDATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INDUSTRIES', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WCI_Outdoor_Products', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
WHITE CONSOLIDATED INDUSTRIES INC. WCI_Outdoor_Products Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1334', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._10,_1999', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hand-held', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('convertible_vacuum/blower', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Doty', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the District of Minnesota David S. Doty J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('removably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('securing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inlet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entirely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('phrase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('restriction_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('permanently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affixed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rader', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1296', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Earl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reiland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merchant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gould', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Edell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Welter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Schmidt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Earl D. Reiland Gould Smith Edell Welter Schmidt P.A. Minneapolis Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tellekson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lindquist', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David K. Tellekson Timothy A. Lindquist
__NEW_SENT__
('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('McGuinness', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fried', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Shriver', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jacobson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
William McGuinness New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('FRIEDMAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*Senior', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
Circuit_Judge PAULINE NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Consolidated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WCI_Outdoor_Products', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('White', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*1297', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('States', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', 'ORG', 'I') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4694,528', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
White Consolidated Industries Inc. WCI_Outdoor_Products Inc. White Minnesota White infringed United States Patent No._4694,528 The Toro Company Toro
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('de', 'FW', '', 'O') ('novo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('precedent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stand', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'528_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hand-held', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('convertible_vacuum/blower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('yard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cleaner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('collecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('leaves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other_debris', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dispersing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('modes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('centrifugal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('impeller', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('rotating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sucking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('blowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('out', 'RB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_outlet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exhaust', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cleaner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('nozzle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('collection_bag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_outlet', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Debris', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sucked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('impeller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('mulched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('blown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_outlet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('collection_bag', 'NN', '', 'O')
Debris
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('directing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_outlet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet_opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('keep', 'VB', '', 'O') ('hands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('clothing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('debris', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fan', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'528_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum/blower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('velocity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('adjusted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('depending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cleaner', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blower', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('velocity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet.2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet_opening', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('twigs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other_debris', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('easily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clog', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inlet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('impeding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'528_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('fitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('restricts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('blower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prevents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('impeller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('blades', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('restriction_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('76', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('air_inlet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('cover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('apertures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
4 76
__NEW_SENT__
