('778_F.2d_775', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TITANIUM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('METALS', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('OF', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('BANNER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patents', 'NNPS', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademarks', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Appellee Donald W. BANNER Patents
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._85-1452', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Nov._7,_1985', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Civil', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patents', 'NNPS', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademarks', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('authorizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('titanium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O')
Patents Trademarks
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Penn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('authorized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Columbia John Garrett Penn J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rich', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*775', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fred', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKelvey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Deputy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sol.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Va.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fred E. McKelvey U.S. Patent and Trademark_Office Arlington Va.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nakamura', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Joseph F. Nakamura Sol
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tarring', 'VBG', 'PERSON', 'I') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Associate', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sol.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Henry W. Tarring II Associate Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bruening', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Webb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Burden', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Webb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pittsburgh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pa.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David C. Bruening Webb Burden Robinson & Webb P.A. of
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Byrne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard L. Byrne
__NEW_SENT__
('*776', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('NICHOLS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RICH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('civil', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('145', 'CD', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Banner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patents', 'NNPS', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademarks1', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('authorizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('serial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._598935', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('TITANIUM', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('ALLOY', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
the District of Columbia 35 Donald W. Banner Patents Trademarks1 1 2 and 3 `` TITANIUM ALLOY ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Loren', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Covington', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('employees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whom', 'WP', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_29,_1974', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('serial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('No._455964', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('patent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Loren C. Covington Howard R. Palmer March_29,_1974
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_25,_1975', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
continuation-in-part July_25,_1975 three
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('titanium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Ti', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nickel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Ni', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('molybdenum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mo', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alloying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ingredients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('give', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('desirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('corrosion_resistance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('brine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solutions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('retaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('workability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fabricated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rolling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('welding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('apparently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('iron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('iron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undesired', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('impurity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permissible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('above', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('precise', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('definition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('representing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('understood', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('iron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('titanium_base_alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('0.6', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('0.9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('%_nickel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('0.2', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('0.4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_molybdenum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('up', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('0.2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_maximum_iron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('balance_titanium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('corrosion_resistance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('brine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('environments', 'NNS', '', 'O')
about 0.6 % 0.2 % 0.4 0.2
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('titanium_base_alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('up', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('to', 'TO', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('0.1', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('iron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('balance_titanium', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1 up to 0.1 %
__NEW_SENT__
('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('titanium_base_alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('1_having_08', 'CD', 'LOC', 'I') ('%_nickel', 'NN', 'LOC', 'I') ('0.3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_molybdenum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('up', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('0.1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_maximum_iron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('balance_titanium', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1_having_08 %_nickel 0.3 0.1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('repeated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Answer', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('PTO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('fully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kalabukhova', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mikheyew', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Investigation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Mechanical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Properties', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ti-Mo-Ni', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Alloys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Russian', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Metallurgy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Metally', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('No._3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('pages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('130-133', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1970', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Russian_article', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', 'DATE', 'B') ('35', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('U.S.C.¡±¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102_and_103', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
Answer the Patent and Trademark_Office ( PTO ) Board of Appeals 1_and_2 3 Kalabukhova Ti-Mo-Ni Metally 130-133 1970 `` the Russian_article '' under 35
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('mistakenly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Russian_article', 'NN', 'LOC', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ignored', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O')
three 102 Russian_article
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('says', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pursue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O')
103
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('proceeds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O')
Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('affidavits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rosenberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Palmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minkler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('persuaded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Rosenberg Palmer Hall Minkler
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Russian_article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('short', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('pages', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('highly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('graphs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discussion', 'NN', '', 'O')
3 10
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('title', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ternary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Ti-Mo-Ni', 'PRP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alloys', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ti-Mo-Ni
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('skilled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*777', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('allowable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O')
one 1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('little', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thinking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('knowledgeable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Ti-Ni-Mo', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('alloys', 'NNS', '', 'O')
one Ti-Ni-Mo
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thinking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lc', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('graph', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ternary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('titanium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Mo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ni', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ratio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1:3', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Amongst', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('actual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('points', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('graph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_Mo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('+', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ni', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Amongst 1
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ni', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('0.25', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('0.75', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
0.25 % 0.75 %
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appears', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('graph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('...', ':', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('deny', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_points', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('affidavit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('points', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('1.25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_Mo', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('+', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ni', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('represent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alloys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('falling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Hall at least two 1 % 1.25
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('alloys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Russian_article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('corrosion-resistant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('property', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contemplated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consequence', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Russian_article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discuss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('corrosion_resistance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ductility', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('points', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('authors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_points', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('dissatisfied', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Titanium', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Metals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Covington', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Palmer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('145', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('profert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('copy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('papers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('file', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('copy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Russian_article', 'NN', 'LOC', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sole', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('refusal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Titanium Metals Corporation of America Covington the District of Columbia 35 145 Russian_article
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('prayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjudge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('authorize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('grant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
1-3
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Commissioner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('answer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alloys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('patentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('profert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Examiner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Answer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O')
first Examiner Answer the Board of Appeals '
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('came', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'RP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('24', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Honorable', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Penn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('half', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('hours', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
January 24 1980 John G. Penn two and a half hours
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('witness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Williams', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('professor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carnegie-Mellon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('University', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pittsburgh', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('titanium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('metallurgy', 'NN', '', 'O')
James C. Williams Carnegie-Mellon University Pittsburgh
__NEW_SENT__
('His', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('divided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('examination', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('exchange', 'NN', '', 'O') ('took', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Associate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Solicitor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('COURT', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('All', 'RB', '', 'O') ('right', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Mr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tarring', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
Tarring
__NEW_SENT__
('MR.', 'LS', '', 'O') ('TARRING', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Your', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Honor', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tribunals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exhibit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'RBR', '', 'O')
Honor the Patent Office the Board of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('quite', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('you', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('prefer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('post-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'s", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('your', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('preference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('do', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('right', 'RB', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ("n't", 'RB', '', 'O') ('know', 'VB', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('your', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('preference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ("'m", 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('going', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('call', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('COURT', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('You', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('going', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MR.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TARRING', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('calling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('really', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('think', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*778', 'VB', '', 'O') ('THE', 'DT', '', 'O') ('COURT', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Of', 'RB', '', 'O') ('course', 'RB', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('your', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('pre-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('briefs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discussion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('settled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('briefs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transcript', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prepared', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
April May 1980
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('memorandum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
November 16 1984 November 28
__NEW_SENT__
('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Notice', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O')
January 10 1985 PTO Notice of
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('briefs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
