('347_F.3d_1355', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TALBERT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('FUEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SYSTEMS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PATENTS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CO.', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('UNOCAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Union', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Oil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
UNOCAL CORPORATION Union Oil Company
__NEW_SENT__
('Tosco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
Tosco Corporation Defendant-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1421', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Oct._28,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Consuelo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Marshall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District Court California Marshall J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('275_F.3d_1371', 'CD', '', 'O') ('affirmed.On', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('certiorari', 'NN', '', 'O') ('537_U.S._802', 'CD', '', 'O') ('123_S.Ct._70', 'CD', '', 'O') ('154_L.Ed.2d_3', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Supreme_Court', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('precedent', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 154_L.Ed.2d_3 Supreme_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1356', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Arthur', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cambridge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Talbert_Fuel_Systems_Patents_Co.', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Melvyn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weiss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Christian', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Siebott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Milberg_Weiss_Bershad_Hynes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lerach_LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Ronald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Engel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('William_E._Johnson', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Law', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Offices', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('William_E._Johnson', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Arthur R. Miller Cambridge MA Talbert_Fuel_Systems_Patents_Co. Melvyn I. Weiss Christian Siebott Milberg_Weiss_Bershad_Hynes & Lerach_LLP New York Ronald L. Engel Chicago William_E._Johnson Law Offices of William_E._Johnson Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Deborah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sturman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Milberg_Weiss_Bershad_Hynes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lerach_LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Deborah M. Sturman Milberg_Weiss_Bershad_Hynes & Lerach_LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Beehler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robins', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kaplan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Miller', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ciresi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David W. Beehler Minneapolis Minnesota L.L.P. Minneapolis
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Diane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Simerson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Diane L. Simerson
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taranto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taranto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Richard G. Taranto Farr & Taranto Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Tracy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sykes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kaplan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ciresi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Tracy A. Sykes Robins Kaplan Miller & Ciresi
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lesniak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knobbe', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Martens', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Olson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bear', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Newport', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Beach', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Tosco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
James F. Lesniak Martens Olson & Bear LLP Newport Beach Tosco Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Craig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Summers', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Giezentanner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zimmerman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Craig S. Summers John P. Giezentanner William R. Zimmerman
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Supreme_Court', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consideration1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Festo_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Shoketsu_Kinzoku_Kogyo_Kabushiki_Co.', 'XX', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('535_U.S._722', 'CD', '', 'O') ('122_S.Ct._1831', 'CD', '', 'O') ('152_L.Ed.2d_944', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('62_USPQ2d_1705_(2002)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Supreme_Court Court Shoketsu_Kinzoku_Kogyo_Kabushiki_Co. 152_L.Ed.2d_944
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Talbert_Fuel_Systems_Patents_Co.', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Unocal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('275_F.3d_1371', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1376-78', 'CD', '', 'O') ('61_USPQ2d_1363', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1366-68', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California,2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5015,356', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬356_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high-end', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('345¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precludes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬356_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Unocal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5288,393', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('interfering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Talbert_Fuel_Systems_Patents_Co. Unocal Corp. United_States_District_Court 1 Talbert United States 345¢XF 2 3 Talbert Unocal
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absolute', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Festo_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Shoketsu_Kinzoku_Kogyo_Kabushiki_Co.', '$', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('234_F.3d_558', 'CD', '', 'O') ('56_USPQ2d_1865_(Fed.Cir.2000)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deny', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Talbert Shoketsu_Kinzoku_Kogyo_Kabushiki_Co. Talbert
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Supreme_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('vacatur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('GVR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Supreme_Court GVR
__NEW_SENT__
('*1357', 'UH', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('return', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('recent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interpreting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Festo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O')
Court
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Festo_Corp.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shoketsu_Kinzoku_Kogyo_Kabushiki_Co.', 'XX', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('344_F.3d_1359_(Fed.Cir.2003)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Shoketsu_Kinzoku_Kogyo_Kabushiki_Co. 344_F.3d_1359_(Fed.Cir.2003)
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬356_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('boiling_point_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('121¢XF-345¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (':', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Talbert 121¢XF-345¢XF 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Reid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Vapor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pressure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carbureted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combustion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engine', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbon_mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intermediate_carbon_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('C4-C12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('intermediate_carbon_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('C6-C10', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('hydrocarbons', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('C9', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('C10', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('paraffinic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('boiling_point_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('121¢XF-345¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('atmosphere', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pressure..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Emphasis', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Reid Vapor C4-C12 C6-C10 hydrocarbons 121¢XF-345¢XF 1 Emphasis
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Unocal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('fuels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('endpoints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('373.8¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('472.9¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Unocal 373.8¢XF 472.9¢XF
__NEW_SENT__
('Talbert', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('345¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('confirm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('predominant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('C6-C10', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cut', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fuel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('gasifier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
345¢XF
__NEW_SENT__
('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('o', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interpret', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature_range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('restriction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low-', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('high-end', 'VB', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('contradicts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accepted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('refinery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('practice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('renders', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meaningless', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Talbert
__NEW_SENT__
('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('points', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recognizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small_amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('C6-C10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('remain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('imprecision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fractionation', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intermediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C6-C10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') (']..', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('volatile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('heavy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbon_mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('boil', 'VB', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('121¢XF-345¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('atmosphere', 'NN', '', 'O')
Talbert about 121¢XF-345¢XF one
__NEW_SENT__
('Such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('boiling_point_range', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('encompasses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('point', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lowest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C6', 'NN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('highest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('C10', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'RB', '', 'O') ('course', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('C4', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C5', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C11', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('C12', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('remain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('imperfections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fractionation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('procedures', 'NNS', '', 'O')
C12
__NEW_SENT__
("'356_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('39-48', 'CD', '', 'O')
7
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('345¢XF', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('limit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('nothing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recognition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('highest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('C10', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('paraffinic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decane', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('boilers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('small_amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Talbert 345¢XF
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accepting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fractionation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('readily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('achieve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exact', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('endpoint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('permit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('departs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('significantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('temperature_range', 'NN', '', 'O')
Talbert
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('insistence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('distinguish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hamilton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fuels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('endpoint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('390¢XF', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('420¢XF', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Hamilton
__NEW_SENT__
('Talbert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature_range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('boiling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('points', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrocarbons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gasoline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('96.8¢XF', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('345¢XF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Talbert
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('gain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('allowance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Talbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('place', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('restriction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Talbert
__NEW_SENT__
('Talbert', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('explanation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('designated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('endpoint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('345¢XF', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fuels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('endpoints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('373¢XF', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O')
345¢XF 373¢XF
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('*1358', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
