('566_F.3d_1372', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TITAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TIRE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Goodyear_Tire', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rubber_Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CASE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEW', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('HOLLAND', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CNH', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GPX_International_Tire_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Goodyear_Tire & Rubber_Company Plaintiffs-Appellants CNH America
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1078', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_3,_2009', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
June_3,_2009
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('licensor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tractor_tire', 'NN', '', 'O')
Owner
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Iowa', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gritzner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2007_WL_2914513', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Iowa James E. Gritzner J. 2007_WL_2914513
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plager', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unlikely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('withstand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness_grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Plager Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1374', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Kent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Herink', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Koehn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shors', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roberts', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Des', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Moines', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('IA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kent A. Herink Davis Brown Koehn Shors & Roberts Des Moines IA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David A
__NEW_SENT__
('Tank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Deborah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tharnish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Deborah M. Tharnish
__NEW_SENT__
('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grimm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hinckley', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Allen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Snyder', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Providence', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
William R. Grimm Providence RI
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Levin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Eric D. Levin Boston
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN PLAGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PLAGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clarify', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clarification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sought-for', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Goodyear_Tire', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rubber_Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Goodyear', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Design', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._360862', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬862_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor_tire', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Goodyear_Tire & Rubber_Company Goodyear U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellant', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tire', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enforce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬862_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellant Titan Tire Corporation Titan
__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬862_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('perspective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tractor_tire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1375', 'UH', '', 'O') ('FIG-1', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Goodyear', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Holland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Iowa', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
February 2007 Goodyear Titan Titan Appellee Case New Holland Inc. Case Iowa
__NEW_SENT__
('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('backhoes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('equipped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tires', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('862', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Titan Case
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prohibit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('backhoes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('tires', 'NNS', '', 'O')
May 2007 Titan
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('CNH', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CNH', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GPX_International_Tire_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GPX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Titan Appellees CNH America CNH
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CNH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('apparently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('answer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CNH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corporate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('backhoes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
CNH Case CNH Case the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('GPX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Easy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rider', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬862_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Titan
__NEW_SENT__
('Titan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tire', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Holland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':07-CV-00063', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2007_WL_2914513', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.Iowa', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Oct.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Preliminary', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Titan Tire Corp. Case New Holland Inc. Oct. 3 2007
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('succeed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('withstand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬862_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('functional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('withstand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness_grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Titan Case Titan Case
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('factors-irreparable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('balance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hardships', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interest-weighed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('defeat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Titan
__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unnecessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('decide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CNH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GPX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
CNH
__NEW_SENT__
('Titan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Titan
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1292 1
__NEW_SENT__
