('642_F.3d_1370', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United_States', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United_States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TYCO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HEALTHCARE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('GROUP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mallinckrodt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MUTUAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_Research_Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
TYCO HEALTHCARE GROUP LP Mallinckrodt Inc. MUTUAL PHARMACEUTICAL COMPANY INC. United_Research_Laboratories Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2010-1513', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_22,_2011', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sleep-inducing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Competitor
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United_States', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('R.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Chesler', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2010_WL_1799457', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United_States District Court the District of New Jersey Stanley R. Chesler J. 2010_WL_1799457
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1370', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Renk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Henry J. Renk New York
__NEW_SENT__
('Jeremy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lowe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Axinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Veltrop', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harkrider', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hartford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Jeremy C. Lowe Axinn Veltrop & Harkrider LLP Hartford CN
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Veltrop', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Francis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morrison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James D. Veltrop Francis H. Morrison III
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hedemann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murata', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas K. Hedemann Jason T. Murata
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1371', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Healthcare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mallinckrodt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5211,954', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Tyco Healthcare Group LP Mallinckrodt Inc. Tyco two U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Temazepam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hypnotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sleep-inducing', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('benzodiazepines', 'NNS', '', 'O')
I. Temazepam
__NEW_SENT__
('Pharmacological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('marketed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('internationally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('insomnia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1970s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')
the 1970s United_States 1981
__NEW_SENT__
('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Tyco ¡¬954_patent two
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gelatin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capsule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('6_to_8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('milligrams', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('crystalline_temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.BIG_TOKEN__65_to_1__BIG_TOKENBIG_TOKEN__1_m_2__BIG_TOKEN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('/g', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('95', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('size', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('65', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('microns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('admixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1 0.BIG_TOKEN__65_to_1__BIG_TOKENBIG_TOKEN__1_m_2__BIG_TOKEN /g 95 % less than 65
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('7.5', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('milligrams', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('crystalline_temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 2 7.5 milligrams
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('priority_date', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
May 1993 a priority_date of September 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('predecessor-in-interest', 'CD', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('7.5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Tyco 7.5 1991
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Mutual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('7.5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg_temazepam_capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O')
November 2006 Mutual Pharmaceutical Company Inc. Abbreviated New Drug Application the U.S. Food and Drug Administration FDA 7.5
__NEW_SENT__
('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_Research_Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Tyco March 2007 United_Research_Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tentative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminarily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capsule', 'NN', '', 'O')
July 2009 Mutual FDA ANDA Tyco
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('uncontroverted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crystalline_temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('2.2', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('square', 'JJ', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('meters', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gram', 'NN', '', 'O')
Tyco Mutual at least 2.2 square meters
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Elan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Pharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
See Bayer AG Elan Pharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('212_F.3d_1241', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1249', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2000', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Research Corp. 1249
__NEW_SENT__
('Mutual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mutual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_claims', 'NNPS', 'NORP', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mutual Mutual ¡¬954_claims
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosages', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
first 15 30 more than a year
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('looked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('volume', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('British', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('National', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Formulary', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('BNF', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medical_reference_book', 'NN', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Kingdom', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('physicians', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('5_and_15', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('insomnia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elderly', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Second 1983 BNF the United Kingdom
__NEW_SENT__
('Third', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('observed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('physicians', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('always', 'RB', '', 'O') ('seek', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prescribe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lowest_effective_dose', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hypnotics', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Third
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preexisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('capsule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BNF_reference', 'NN', '', 'O')
15
__NEW_SENT__
('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_claims', 'NNPS', 'NORP', 'B')
Tyco ¡¬954_claims
__NEW_SENT__
('*1372', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('physical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('distinguishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_claims', 'NNPS', 'NORP', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('capsule', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬954_claims 15
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('predecessor-in-interest', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Supplemental', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('7.5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg_temazepam_capsules', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬954_claims', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B')
1987 Tyco Supplemental New Drug Application FDA 7.5 mg_temazepam_capsules ¡¬954_claims
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Capsules', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('7.5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('15_and_30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('milligram', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capsules..', 'NN', '', 'O')
15_and_30
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('differs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dose..', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('capsule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('exactly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('currently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('marketed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('doses', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('uncontested', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('¡¬954_claims', 'NNPS', 'NORP', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('RestorilTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O')
two ¡¬954_claims
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BNF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('medical_reference_book', 'NN', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('semiannually', 'RB', 'DATE', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('British', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Medical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Association', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Society', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Great', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Britain', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
BNF semiannually the British Medical Association the Pharmaceutical Society of Great Britain
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Preface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BNF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('serves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pocket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('book', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reference..', 'XX', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prescribing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dispensing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('entries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('help', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('choice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
BNF
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('BNF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Indications', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('insomnia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elderly', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Cautions', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Side-effects', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nitrazepam,1', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hangover', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('uncommon', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('doses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('cumulative', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1983 BNF Side-effects Nitrazepam,1
__NEW_SENT__
('Less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wakening', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dose', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('10-30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('elderly_patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('5-15', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('severe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('insomnia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('60', 'CD', 'TIME', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', 'TIME', 'I') ('30', 'CD', 'TIME', 'I') ('minutes', 'NNS', 'TIME', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bedtime', 'NN', '', 'O')
10-30 60 mg 30 minutes
__NEW_SENT__
('BNF', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('127', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
BNF 127
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'XX', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('plainly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('tells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('insomnia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elderly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('5_to_15', 'CD', 'NORP', 'B') ('mg.', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('physician', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prescribe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lowest_effective_dose', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('elderly_patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hypnotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
one 5_to_15 2 15
__NEW_SENT__
('Ordinarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('falls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1373', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Iron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Grip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Barbell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sports', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('392_F.3d_1317', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1322', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2004', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('accord', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Lazare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kaplan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Photoscribe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('628_F.3d_1359', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1380-81', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2010', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Iron Grip Barbell Co. USA Sports Inc. 1322 Lazare Kaplan Photoscribe Techs. Inc. 628_F.3d_1359 1380-81
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rebuttable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unexpected_results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Iron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Grip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barbell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('392', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1322', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Iron Grip Barbell 1322
__NEW_SENT__
('Tyco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BNF_reference', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('direct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temazepam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('5_to_15', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O')
Tyco first BNF_reference
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('whole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('6_to_8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Tyco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unexpected_results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('support', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
