('418_F.3d_1379', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('TERLEP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRINKMANN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORP.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wal-Mart_Stores', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Home_Depot', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Stephen K. TERLEP The BRINKMANN CORP. Wal-Mart_Stores Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._04-1337', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._16,_2005', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('omni-directional_light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('diode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('retail', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('distributors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arkansas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Harry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barnes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Western_District Arkansas Harry F. Barnes J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1380', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nathan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Price', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chaney', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nolan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fayetteville', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Arkansas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nolan Henry Fayetteville Arkansas
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Murphey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Aubrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fussell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark Murphey Henry James Aubrey Fussell
__NEW_SENT__
('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Clark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sheppard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mullin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Richter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hampton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gary A. Clark Sheppard Mullin Richter & Hampton LLP Los Angeles California
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hermann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ivester', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mitchell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Williams', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Selig', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gates', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Woodyard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.L.L.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Little', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Arkansas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Hermann Ivester Mitchell Williams Selig Gates & Woodyard P.L.L.C. Little Rock Arkansas
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
BRYSON LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Terlep', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Terlep', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arkansas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brinkmann_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wal-Mart_Stores', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Home_Depot', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._5594,433', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'433_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Stephen K. Terlep Terlep Western_District Arkansas The Brinkmann_Corp. Wal-Mart_Stores Inc. Home_Depot U.S.A. Inc. U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Terlep', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann_Corp.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('No._02-_CV-5127', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Ark', 'NN', '', 'O')
No._02-_CV-5127
__NEW_SENT__
('March_29,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Order I ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Brinkmann
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'433_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('omni-directional_light', 'VB', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('diode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LED', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LEDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substitute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('traditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('incandescent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('lifetime', 'NN', '', 'O') ('higher', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('resistance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vibration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('incandescent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('emits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('light', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('omni-directionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('forward', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('90', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('degrees', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I')
less than 90 degrees
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'433_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('omni-directional_light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reflecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O') ('off', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semi-spherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('convex', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('underlined', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('omni-directional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('traffic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('warning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('reflects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('360', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('degree_circumferential_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rotate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_LED', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('semi-spherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('convex', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('semi-spherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_LED', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_LED', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reflected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('360', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('degree', 'NN', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('circumference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rendering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_LED', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('omni-directional', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
360 first first 360 degree
__NEW_SENT__
('*1381', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tubular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tightly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('semi-spherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('oriented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_LED', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stationary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non', 'AFX', '', 'O') ('rotating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('semi-spherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reflects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('360', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('degree_circumferential_direction', 'NN', '', 'O')
first first first 360
__NEW_SENT__
("'433_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._6,_ll._13-28', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('semi-spherical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mirror', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finish', 'NN', '', 'O') ('deposited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1 first
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._6,_ll._57-59', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Terlep', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'433_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
November 28 1997 Terlep Brinkmann Brinkmann 1_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('solar-powered', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pathway_lighting', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('retailers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Wal-Mart', '.', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Home_Depot', '.', '', 'O')
Wal-Mart
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('use', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('convex', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('half', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('sphere', 'NN', '', 'O')
half
__NEW_SENT__
('Further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pathway_lighting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('orientation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('lights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('use', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ribbed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('align', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('position', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reflector', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('front', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LED', 'NN', '', 'O')
Brinkmann
__NEW_SENT__
('Brinkmann', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prejudice', 'NN', '', 'O')
Brinkmann
__NEW_SENT__
('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_14,_2004', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Terlep', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
April_14,_2004 Terlep
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('lacked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Brinkmann
__NEW_SENT__
('Terlep', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann_Corp.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('127_Fed.Appx._498_(Fed.Cir.2005)', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prejudice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unresolved', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Brinkmann
__NEW_SENT__
('Terlep', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Brinkmann_Corp.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('No._02-_CV-5127', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('W.D.Ark', 'NN', '', 'O')
No._02-_CV-5127
__NEW_SENT__
('March_24,_2005', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
March_24,_2005
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_10,_2005', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Terlep', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reinstate', 'VB', '', 'O')
March_10,_2005 Terlep
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', 'LOC', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('April_11,_2005', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recalled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mandate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reinstated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Order April_11,_2005
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
