('166_F.3d_1172', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('THOMSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('QUIXOTE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Disc_Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
THOMSON S.A. QUIXOTE CORPORATION Disc_Manufacturing Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._97-1485', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Jan._25,_1999', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Jan._25,_1999
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('optical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('digital', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('audio', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compact', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discs', 'NN', '', 'O') ('violated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
four
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Longobardi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('979_F.Supp._286', 'CD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Joseph J. Longobardi JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purported', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unpatented_laser_videodisc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('corroboration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rich Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1173', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Badenoch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
George E. Badenoch Kenyon & Kenyon
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Flock', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard L. Mayer John Flock Robert F. Perry
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Giannetti', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Thomas L. Giannetti Fish & Neave
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Harold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blanchard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brinks', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hofer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lione', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Harold V. Johnson James B. Blanchard Brinks Hofer Gilson & Lione Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RICH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_24,_1997', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomson S.A. Thomson June_24,_1997 United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Quixote_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('979_F.Supp._286', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.1997', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Thomson S.A. Thomson I ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Matter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sustained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nos._4868,808', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('5,182,743', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4,961,183', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5,175,725', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('g', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Thomson U.S. Patent Nos._4868,808 5,182,743 4,961,183 5,175,725 35 102
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('optical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('information-storage', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compact', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discs', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Thomson
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('markets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('play', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('CDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('grants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('licenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('CDs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Thomson
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Quixote_Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Disc_Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Quixote', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('make', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('CDs.1', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Defendants-Appellees Quixote_Corp. and Disc_Manufacturing Inc. Quixote
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Quixote', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomson Quixote
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('base', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outcome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('representative_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4868,808', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5182,743', 'NNP', '', 'O')
three 1_and_13 U.S. Patent No._4868,808 1 U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1174', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conducted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Markman_hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('representative_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1972', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Thomson August 25 1972
__NEW_SENT__
('Quixote', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('purporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('representative_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unpatented_laser_videodisc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1972', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-party', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('MCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Discovision', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('MCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Quixote August 1972 MCA Discovision Inc. MCA
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('special', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('representative_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('g', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('aside', 'RP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Matter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('grant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomson JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('insufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Markman_hearing', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomson JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('videodisc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomson Thomson MCA
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Thomson', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('979', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('F.Supp.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('292-98', 'CD', '', 'O')
Thomson 979
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('came', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('live', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('people', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('worked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('laser', 'NN', '', 'O') ('videodisc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('project', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('report', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('deposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('exhibits', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('MCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('documents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reviewed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
one two MCA MCA
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('288', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('292-98', 'CD', '', 'O')
288
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Quixote', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('every', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('representative_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('MCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')
Quixote MCA
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('298', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
298
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Thomson JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
