('204_F.3d_1360', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ULTRA-TEX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SURFACES', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dryvit_Systems', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HILL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BROTHERS', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('CHEMICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Omega_Products_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
SURFACES INC. Dryvit_Systems Inc. HILL BROTHERS CHEMICAL CO. Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Vincent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chacon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Defendant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Vincent Chacon
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._99-1018', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('99-1024', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Feb._29,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('low-cost', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ornamental_concrete_surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taylor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California Gary L. Taylor J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1361', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schwartz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Christie', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Parker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hale', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pasadena', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('California', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Edward R. Schwartz Pasadena California
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hawes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Levin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hawes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Laguna', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Beach', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
James E. Hawes Levin & Hawes Laguna Beach California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dawe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Nancy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tragarz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Prenovost', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Normandin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bergh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dawe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Santa', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Michael G. Dawe Nancy R. Tragarz Prenovost Normandin Bergh & Dawe Santa Ana California
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Senior', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')
MAYER ARCHER Senior
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ultra-Tex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Surfaces', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dryvit_Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Ultra-Tex', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brothers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chemical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Omega_Products_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5,502,941', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Ultra-Tex Surfaces Inc. Dryvit_Systems Inc. Ultra-Tex United_States_District_Court California Hill Brothers Chemical Co. 6 U.S. 5,502,941
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ultra-Tex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Surfaces', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bros.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chem', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nos', 'NNP', '', 'O')
See Ultra-Tex Surfaces Inc. Hill Bros. Chem Co.
__NEW_SENT__
('SA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('CV', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('96-1230', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-1232', ':', '', 'O') ('GLT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('EEx', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C.D.Cal', 'VBN', '', 'O')
SA
__NEW_SENT__
('Aug._21,_1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Hill', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Brothers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Omega', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Hill Brothers Omega 6 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Claimed', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Accused', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Processes', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('low-cost', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ornamental_concrete_surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('imitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brick', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('considerably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inlaying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('actual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bricks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._52-58', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 6 5 5
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decorative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_batch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liquid_mortar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesive_resin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('liquid_mortar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cure', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flexible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pattern', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('grout', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adhesive_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('backing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('backing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('expose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('adhesive_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('securing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_batch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous_solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesive_resin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('color', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pigment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contrasting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('color', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_batch', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_batch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liquid_mortar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dry', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('above', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('finish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('curing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sealer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('mortar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first second
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('flexible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heavy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wax', 'NN', '', 'O') ('impregnated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('backing', 'NN', '', 'O')
5
__NEW_SENT__
('*1362', 'NFP', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._7,_l._13', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('col._8,_l._14', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('paragraphing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('8_and_11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('slightly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('modified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clarity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depict', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
8_and_11
__NEW_SENT__
