('412_F.3d_1319', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('UPSHER-SMITH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PAMLAB', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
UPSHER-SMITH LABORATORIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('formerly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Pan_American_Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pan_American_Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('L.L.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Pan_American_Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Metabolite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Metabolite Laboratories Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._04-1405', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_17,_2005', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Ann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Montgomery', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2003_WL_22999551', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2004_WL_902176', 'CD', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the District of Minnesota Ann D. Montgomery J. 2003_WL_22999551
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1320', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Holdreith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robins', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kaplan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Miller', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ciresi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jacob M. Holdreith Minneapolis Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ronald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schutz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Misti', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nelc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kimberly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jonathan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Goins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Ronald J. Schutz Misti Nelc Kimberly G. Miller Jonathan D. Goins
__NEW_SENT__
('Glenn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Beaton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gibson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crutcher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Denver', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Glenn K. Beaton Gibson Dunn & Crutcher LLP Denver Colorado
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whitehair', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amanda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tessar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
J. Gregory Whitehair Amanda J. Tessar
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mark A. Perry Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MICHEL
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Upsher-Smith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Upsher-Smith', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._5932,624', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Aug._3,_1999', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('6,605,646', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Aug._12,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
U.S. Aug._3,_1999 6,605,646
__NEW_SENT__
('Upsher-Smith', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('8-10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pan_American_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Upsher-Smith 1 8-10 1-7
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pamlab', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.L.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Pamlab', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')1', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('orders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pamlab', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Pamlab two Pamlab
__NEW_SENT__
('Upsher-Smith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pan_Am', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Upsher-Smith Labs. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Labs', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._01-352', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I') ('2003_WL_22999551', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Minn', '.', 'PERSON', 'B')
Labs Inc. No._01-352 D.Minn
__NEW_SENT__
('Dec.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('19', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NN', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Upsher-Smith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pan_Am', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Dec. 19 2003 Upsher-Smith Labs. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Labs', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._01-352', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('2004_WL_902176', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Minn', '.', 'PERSON', 'B')
Labs Inc. D.Minn
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'646", 'CD', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
26 2004
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('optionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('*1321', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anticipates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('excludes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses_vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('serum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('homocysteine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('levels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('protect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vessel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'624_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses_vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('brain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('nervous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('damage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pernicious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anemia', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('folic_acid', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('folate', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B6', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'624_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._15-19', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('II', 'CD', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('25-29', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('states', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vitamin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('supplement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('folic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('folic_acid', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B6', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('folic_acid', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-antioxidant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vitamin', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('folic_acid', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('non-antioxidant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vitamins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('oxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'624_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', '', 'O')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('21-32', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Importantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('be', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('folate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B6', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('folate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B6', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vitamins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('health', 'NN', '', 'O') ('benefits', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Victor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('destroys', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('folate', 'VB', '', 'O')
Victor Herbert
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Herbert', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dr._Herbert
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Herbert', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('distinguished', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Dr._Herbert
__NEW_SENT__
('Indeed', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Upsher-Smith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('admits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('negative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('teaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('vitamin_supplement_compositions', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('folate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B6', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('destroy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('folate', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('forty', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitamins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('C', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('E', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('incompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'ADD', '', 'O')
more than forty years
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Macek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Beate', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Feller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crystalline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Vitamin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('B12', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Preparations', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('41', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Journal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ('Am', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Thomas J. Macek & Beate A. Feller Vitamin B12 Pharmaceutical Preparations 41 Journal of the Am
__NEW_SENT__
('Pharm', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Assoc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('No._6', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('285', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1952', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Assoc. No._6 285 1952
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hebert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('twenty', 'CD', '', 'O') ('years', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('teaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('vitamin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') ('destroys', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'ADD', '', 'O')
Hebert
__NEW_SENT__
('Victor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('JD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Elizabeth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Destruction', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Vitamin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('B12', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Asorbic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Acid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('230', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Journal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ('Am', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Victor Herbert JD & Elizabeth Jacob Vitamin B12 Asorbic Acid 230 Journal of the Am
__NEW_SENT__
('Med', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Assoc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('No._2', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('241', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Oct._14,_1974', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Assoc. No._2 241
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('destroy', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('vitamin_B12', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antioxidizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('responsible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('destruction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Herbert', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('discovered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dr._Herbert
__NEW_SENT__
('Against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('background', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Pamlab', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1322', 'FW', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Pamlab
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('European', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._9331147623', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Sept._14,_1993', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('European_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') (')2', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("'624", 'JJR', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('11-12', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'646", 'CD', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4-5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
European Patent Application No._9331147623 Sept._14,_1993 4-5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('European_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('European_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('optionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('European_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antioxidants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('anticipates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'624", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'646_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'624", 'CD', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'646", 'CD', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('4-5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
11 4-5
__NEW_SENT__
('Upsher-Smith', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
