('602_F.3d_1325', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('VERIZON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SERVICES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORP.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Verizon_Communications', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MCI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Communications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Verizon_Business_Global_LLC', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('COX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('FIBERNET', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('VIRGINIA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cox_Virginia_Telecom', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cox_Communications_Hampton_Roads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Coxcom', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cox_Communications', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O')
VERIZON SERVICES CORP. Verizon_Communications Inc. MCI Communications Corp. Verizon_Business_Global_LLC COX Cox_Communications Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2009-1086', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2009-1098', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_16,_2010', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
April_16,_2010
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('telephone_calls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('packets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Claude', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('M.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hilton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('some', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('subvert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('fairly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('decide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('incorporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('harmless', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('telephony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('anticipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') ('protocols', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('regardless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misconstrued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1328', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taranto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taranto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Richard G. Taranto Farr & Taranto Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kellogg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rozendaal', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Joffre', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kellogg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Huber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hansen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Evans', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Figel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thorne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Griffen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Verizon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Communication', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Suchyta', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Basking', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ridge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Michael K. Kellogg John C. Rozendaal Michael E. Joffre Kellogg Huber Hansen Todd Evans & Figel Washington DC John Thorne Robert H. Griffen Verizon Communication Inc. Arlington Leonard C. Suchyta Basking Ridge NJ
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitchell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stockwell', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kilpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Stockton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mitchell G. Atlanta GA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Boice', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Audra', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
William H. Boice
__NEW_SENT__
('Dial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Verizon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Services', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Verizon_Communications', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MCI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Communications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Verizon_Business_Global_LLC', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1329', 'UH', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Verizon', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('5_and_6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6282,574', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬574_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6104,711', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬711_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6430,275', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬275_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('27', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6292,481', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬481_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6137,869', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬869_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6636,597', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('¡¬597_patent', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('``', '``', 'LAW', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cox', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fibernet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cox_Virginia_Telecom', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cox_Communications_Hampton_Roads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Coxcom', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cox_Communications', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Cox', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Verizon Services Corp. Verizon_Communications Inc. MCI Communications Inc. Verizon_Business_Global_LLC Verizon United_States_District_Court Virginia 1 5_and_6 1 3 and 11 2 1 1 19 27 35 1 U.S._Patent_No._6137,869 12 13 and 20 the ¡¬597_patent `` Cox Fibernet Virginia Inc. Cox_Virginia_Telecom Inc. LLC Coxcom Inc. Cox_Communications Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Verizon_Servs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cox_Fibernet_Va.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._08-_CV-0157', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Va', 'CD', '', 'O')
See Verizon_Servs Corp. No._08-_CV-0157
__NEW_SENT__
('Oct._6,_2008', 'UH', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Verizon_Servs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cox_Fibernet_Va.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('08-CV-0157', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Va', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nov._7,_2008', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cross-motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Verizon_Servs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cox_Fibernet_Va.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._08-_CV-0157', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Va', 'CD', '', 'O')
Verizon_Servs Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nov._11,_2008', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('clarifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('respective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instructing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patents', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('at', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Issue', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
The Patents at Issue
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Verizon', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('packet-switched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephony-technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('telephone_calls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breaking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('voice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('packets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('need', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('traverse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('path', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O')
six Verizon
__NEW_SENT__
('Packet-switched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('increases', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('efficiency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('traditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('switching', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('relies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dedicated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('path', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('endpoints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('call', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('explain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('divide', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬711', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬574_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Feature', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patents', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('¡¬275', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('¡¬869', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬481_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('``', '``', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('Network', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('Patents', 'NNPS', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ("''", "''", 'PRODUCT', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬597_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('``', '``', 'LAW', 'I') ('Quality', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'LAW', 'I') ('Service', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ("''", "''", 'LAW', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
six three the ¡¬275 ¡¬869 ¡¬481_patent the `` Network Patents '' the `` Quality of Service Patent ''
__NEW_SENT__
('None', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('explicitly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('packet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('equated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Verizon_Servs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vonage', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Holdings', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('503_F.3d_1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1305', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2007', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Verizon_Servs Corp. Vonage Holdings Corp. 1305
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('packet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('switched', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('networks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('switched', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('networks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interlinked', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('packet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('networks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
