('616_F.3d_1231', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Philip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('WYERS', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wyers_Products_Group', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MASTER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOCK', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Philip W. WYERS
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2009-1412', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_22,_2010', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
July_22,_2010
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Oct._12,_2010', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('hitch_pin', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('locks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('removable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sleeves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('trailers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automobiles', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Lewis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Babcock', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2009_WL_1309774', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Colorado Lewis T. Babcock Senior District 2009_WL_1309774
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior_art_references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('endeavor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art_references', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Linn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1232', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hogge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Greenberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Traurig', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mark Lee Hogge Greenberg Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Phillip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Charrow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Laura', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Metkoff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Klaus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert Phillip Charrow Laura Metkoff Klaus
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Aaron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bradford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lathrop', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gage', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Denver', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('CO.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Aldo', 'VB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Noto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Andrews', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kurth', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Aaron P. Bradford Lathrop & Gage LLP Denver Aldo Noto Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Frederick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frei', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lori', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Eden', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Burgess', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Frederick S. Frei Lori Eden Burgess
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE LINN DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1233', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('DYK', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Master_Lock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Master_Lock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wyers', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wyers_Products_Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Wyers', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
LLC United_States_District_Court the District of Colorado Philip W. Wyers Wyers_Products_Group Inc. Wyers
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Master_Lock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('24', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6672,115', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬115_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._7165,426', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬426_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._7225,649', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬649_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('seal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
15 24 U.S. No._6672,115 1 1 9 and 11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Master_Lock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('renewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Wyers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Master_Lock', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._06-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('cv-00619-LTB', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2009_WL_1309774', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Colo', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
May 8 2009
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')
patents-in-suit
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('hitch_pin', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('locks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('secure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trailers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sport', 'NN', '', 'O') ('utility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vehicles', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hitch_pin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('secures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('draw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ball', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hitch_receiver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hitch_pin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('aligned_apertures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trailer_hitch_receiver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('draw', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('members', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('describe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('barbell-shaped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aligned_apertures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hitch_receiver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('towball', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trailer_hitch_receiver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬115', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬426_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5664,445', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Chang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lock', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('head', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shackle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latch', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬115 U.S. Chang
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hitch_pin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('lock', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
