('683_F.3d_1356', 'XX', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
683_F.3d_1356
__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('WM', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('WRIGLEY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('JR.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CO.', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CADBURY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ADAMS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
WRIGLEY CADBURY ADAMS USA
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2011-1140', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2011-1150', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_22,_2012', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Aug._24,_2012', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('physiological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('physiological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Illinois', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('500_F.Supp.2d_922', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('631_F.Supp.2d_1010', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'VB', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2010_WL_1325732', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of Robert M. Dow Jr.
__NEW_SENT__
('Parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Newman', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O')
Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1358', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berghoff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McDonnell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Boehnen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hulbert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Berghoff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Paul H. Berghoff McDonnell Boehnen Hulbert & Berghoff LLP Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Suggs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
James V. Suggs
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Patricia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schmidt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('K', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('L', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gates', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Patricia K. Schmidt K & L Gates LLP Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Engel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Alan L. Barry Jason A. Engel
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bollinger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Troutman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sanders', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
James M. Bollinger Troutman Sanders LLP New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Laura', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Krawczyk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Suraj', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Balusu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Laura E. Krawczyk Suraj K. Balusu
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heaton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Douglas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Salyers', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Timothy P. Heaton Douglas D. Salyers
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('FOGEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge.1', 'NNP', '', 'O')
NEWMAN BRYSON Circuit_Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Wm', 'UH', 'PERSON', 'B')
Wm
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Adams', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('compete', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wrigley Jr. Co. Cadbury Adams USA LLC
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sensation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('chewed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Historically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('makers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('achieved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sensation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('physiological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Menthol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disadvantages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('peppermint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flavor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bitterness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('concentrations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Menthol
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1970s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('1980s', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wilkinson-Sword', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('attempted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('develop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('physiological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drawbacks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O')
the 1970s 1980s Wilkinson-Sword Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coolants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('released', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('names', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('own', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coolants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wrigley Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5009,893', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('combines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._6627,233', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('combines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Wrigley U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('matured', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Cadbury July 1989
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 1 one two 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('long-lasting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('breath', 'NN', '', 'O') ('freshening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('perception', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bitterness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sweetener', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamide', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamide 1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('combines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1359', 'FW', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heightened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sensation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('edible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('embody', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('marketplace', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('WS-3/menthol', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Cadbury Wrigley
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
34 Wrigley
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('233', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2000', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬ March 2000
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('34', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 34 34
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('95', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('95', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('bulking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sweetening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
about 5 % about 95 % about 5 % about 95 %
__NEW_SENT__
('c', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('%', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('flavoring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('N-2,3-trimethyl-2-isopropyl_butanamide', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O')
about 0.1 about 10 %
__NEW_SENT__
('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('N-2,3-trimethyl-2-isopropyl_butanamide', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('WS-23/menthol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('chewing_gum', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('reformulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum_products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wrigley WS-23/menthol Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reformulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('accusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reformulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wrigley Cadbury Northern_District Illinois Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('accusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cadbury Wrigley Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wrigley Cadbury
__NEW_SENT__
('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cadbury 34
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent2', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wrigley
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Wrigley
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('narrowly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('implicitly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('excluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carboxamides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬893_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Addressing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cadbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Cadbury 34
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5688,491', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5698,181', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Luo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('M.A', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
34 Shahidi M.A
__NEW_SENT__
('Parrish', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Parrish', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Parrish
__NEW_SENT__
('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('xylitol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('copper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bis-glycinate', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1360', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('toothpaste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mouth', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rinses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lozenges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('lists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Shahidi
__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('essential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('optional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('nonessential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('optional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('nonessential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identify', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('category', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Shahidi two three
__NEW_SENT__
('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Shahidi one 23
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('every', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Shahidi 34
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('incorporated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subset', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
34
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Shahidi one 34
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Shahidi 34
__NEW_SENT__
('Luo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('achieves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('N-substituted-p-menthane_carboxamides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O')
Luo
__NEW_SENT__
('Parrish', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('replacements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O')
1987
__NEW_SENT__
('Parrish', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('highlights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side-effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Parrish', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('distinguish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('notes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('regarded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('safe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Flavor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Extract', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Manufacturers', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Association', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FEMA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Parrish FEMA
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FEMA-GRAS', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('listing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O')
FEMA-GRAS
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Luo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Parrish', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Luo Parrish 34
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Parrish', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substituting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Parrish', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('substitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Luo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Parrish two Parrish Luo
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('proffered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Wrigley 34
__NEW_SENT__
('Stratoflex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Aeroquip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('713_F.2d_1530', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1538', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1983', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Stratoflex Inc. Aeroquip Corp. 1538
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wrigley Shahidi 34 two
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim.3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('relatedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('*1361', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('enabled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('derive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('undue_experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O')
First Wrigley Shahidi 34 Second Wrigley Shahidi 34
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('anticipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Net_MoneyIN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VeriSign', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('545_F.3d_1359', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1370', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Net_MoneyIN Inc. VeriSign Inc. 1370
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Net_MoneyIN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Internet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('payment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('payment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('protocols', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subset', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1371', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1371
__NEW_SENT__
('Therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('envisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Shahidi one Shahidi Shahidi three
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('anticipates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Shahidi 34
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('merely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('species', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('turns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'RP', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('envisage', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Eli', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lilly', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Goldline', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharm.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('471_F.3d_1369', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1376', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2006', 'ADD', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Eli Lilly & Goldline Pharm. Inc. 1376 Fed.Cir.2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('coolant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apparent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi one
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Perricone', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Medicis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('432_F.3d_1368', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1377', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2005', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('distinguishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('species', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Perricone Medicis Pharm Corp. 1377
__NEW_SENT__
('Wrigley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Aventis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('545_F.3d_1312_(Fed.Cir.2008)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('stands', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pick', 'VB', '', 'O') ('items', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('assemble', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wrigley Impax Laboratories Inc. Aventis Pharmaceuticals Inc. two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('riluzole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amyotrophic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lateral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sclerosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ALS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1362', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5236,940', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬940_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1314', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1314
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬940_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('encompassed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hundreds', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('thousands', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬940_patent hundreds or thousands
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1315', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1315
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬940_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diseases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ALS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('potentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬940_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('undue_experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('distinctions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'NN', '', 'O')
Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('Unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('riluzole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ALS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amounts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Impax Shahidi 34
__NEW_SENT__
('Even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('importantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('riluzole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclaim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬940_patent..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('excludes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('riluzole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objective', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('flavor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contribute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('long-lasting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sensation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chewing_gum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('clean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('high-quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flavor..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cooling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WS-23', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('identifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('cooling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('menthol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('identifies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('flavoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ingredients.4', 'NN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Shahidi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('anticipates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬233_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shahidi Shahidi one three Shahidi Shahidi 34
__NEW_SENT__
