('103_F.3d_1571', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('WANG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MITSUBISHI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ELECTRONICS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi_Electric_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants/Cross-Appellants', '.', '', 'O')
WANG LABORATORIES INC. MITSUBISHI ELECTRONICS AMERICA INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._95-1276', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('95-1324', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._3,_1997', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('In', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Banc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Declined', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('March_12,_1997', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing In Banc Declined March_12,_1997
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-line_memory_module', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('alleged_infringer', 'NN', '', 'O')
two SIMM
__NEW_SENT__
('Alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment_action', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davies', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('partial_summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged_infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1994_WL_782694', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged_infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1995_WL_491434', 'CD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California John G. Davies J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged_infringer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rich Circuit_Judge 1 one 2 one 3 4 one
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Mayer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concurred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1572', 'LS', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Simon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomas J. Scott Howrey & D.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ruyak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sheila', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schreiber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert F. Ruyak Sheila R. Schreiber
__NEW_SENT__
('*1573', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kozak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Leydig', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Voit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants/cross-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John W. Kozak Voit & Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Phelps', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hesterberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Petersen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark E. Phelps Brett A. Hesterberg Steven P. Petersen
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Les', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weinstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Trupiano', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Woodruff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robbins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Les J. Weinstein Martin J. Trupiano James B. Woodruff Daniel E. Robbins Graham & James Los Angeles California
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('RICH', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RICH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang Laboratories Inc. Mitsubishi Electronics America Inc. two
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi_Electric_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment_action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Mitsubishi Mitsubishi California
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('partial_summary_judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi one
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('But', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dealing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('created', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('memory_modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Single', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('In-line', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Memory', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Modules', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Generally', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('SIMM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reserved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('parity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('checking', 'NN', '', 'O')
Generally Wang 's nine one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sometimes', 'RB', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('X9', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O')
nine
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stores', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('verify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'RP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('retrieved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O')
eight
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('encased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('carriers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('leads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('leaded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('protect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('connective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('terminal_pins', 'NNS', '', 'O')
nine one 30
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printed-circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('mother', 'NN', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('central', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('processing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('write', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('read', 'VB', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('binary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('64-kilobit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('64K', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O')
SIMM Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('64K_memory_chips', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('store', 'VB', '', 'O') ('512', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('kilobits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('64', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('kilobytes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('binary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('digits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('constitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('byte', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
eight 512 64 eight one
__NEW_SENT__
('More', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('recent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('256-kilobit', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('256K', 'CD', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('larger', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O')
256K
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('fall', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
James Clayton Wang Laboratories the fall of 1982
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('remained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('upgrade', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('spring', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('replaceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O')
the spring of 1983 Clayton SIMM
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM_invention', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('serial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('528,817', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
September 2 1983 Clayton Wang SIMM_invention 528,817
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_13,_1985', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B')
three the Patent and Trademark Office June_13,_1985
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O')
PTO
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cancel', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('add', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
Wang 1 2 and 3 4 5 and 6
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('clarified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('packaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('plastic_leaded_chip_carriers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('epoxy-glass', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('boards', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('office', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
PTO
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('file', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wrapper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('serial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('873,879', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_12,_1986', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('replacing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Wang 873,879 4 5 and 6 7
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abandoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('remarks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('accompanying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unique', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('distinguishable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('EDI_EDH-4816_publication', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describ', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ing', 'VBG', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in-line_memory_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1574', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ceramic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ceramic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang eight
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('thirty-two', 'NN', '', 'O') ('terminal_pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
ten
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('parity', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plastic_leaded_chip_carriers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('epoxy-glass', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dimensions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang nine eight one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('thirty', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('terminal_pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('suppress', 'VB', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spikes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
thirty eight
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_No._4656,605', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'605_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('April_7,_1987', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ours', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('installation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_motherboard_comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('data_memory_chips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('digital_data', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('address_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('packaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic_leaded_chip_carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ninth_memory_chip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('error_detection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('correction_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('data_memory_chips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ninth_memory_chip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('address_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interconnected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('writing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ninth_memory_chip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bytes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('data_memory_chips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('facilitate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('error_detection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('correction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('epoxy-glass', 'NN', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_board_substrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('width', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('thereon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interconnecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('address_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bytes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('input', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('thirty', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('terminals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('outputs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('control_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('address_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('writing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bytes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('writing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('error_detection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('correction_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('support_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('motherboard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('installed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('thereon', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
eight eight eight eight nine thirty nine eight eight
__NEW_SENT__
('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('memory_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suppressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('transient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spikes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O')
eight between the nine
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('873,879', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Wang February 20 1987 873,879
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_No._4727,513', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('23', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
two February 23 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
two 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('installation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_motherboard_comprising', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('data_memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('digital_data', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('control_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('address_input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('packaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plastic_leaded_chip_carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ninth_memory_chip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('detection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('correction_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('data_memory_chips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('epoxy-glass', 'NN', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('circuit_board_substrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('width', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('thereon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interconnecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('address_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bytes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('digital_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('input', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('thirty', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('terminals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('outputs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('control_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('address_inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('writing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('support_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motherboard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
nine eight nine thirty nine nine
__NEW_SENT__
('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suppressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('transient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltages', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('interconnected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ninth', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('*1575', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory_chips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('input', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1 all nine ninth eight
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('employees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('members', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('press', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Wang Clayton SIMM June 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('giving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('personnel', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panelists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('hoped', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('preempt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('future', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('256K_chips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japanese', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Small', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Outline', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Integrated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SOIC', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang Japanese the Small Outline Integrated Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('64K_chips', 'CD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('64-kilobyte', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('package', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('introduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('smaller', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('denser', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('option', 'NN', '', 'O')
eight Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('went', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('note', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('struggle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Joint', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Device', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Council', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JEDEC', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('committee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Association', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('invested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('responsibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('setting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('standards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('format', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('become', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory_module', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Joint Electronic Device Council JEDEC the Electronic Industries Association
__NEW_SENT__
('Clayton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('described', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preceding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upcoming', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('JEDEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('meetings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('awaiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('indication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('go', 'VB', '', 'O') ('before', 'RB', '', 'O') ('committing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('module', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
Clayton JEDEC
__NEW_SENT__
('He', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('belief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('package', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('catalyst', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sway', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('approach', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Clayton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('revealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Clayton Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('intended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('encourage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('buy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('already', 'RB', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('preparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panelist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent_rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM,1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agreements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('approached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('makers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang Wang SIMM third
__NEW_SENT__
('Panelist', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Devlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('summarized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('goal', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Hopefully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('enough', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gets', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('big', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('get', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('advantage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('volumes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Daniel Devlin Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('publications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('carried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('stories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SIMM July August 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JEDEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('persuade', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('designate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang JEDEC Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adoption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('JEDEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('accepted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang SIMM September 1983 June 1986 JEDEC SIMM
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('JEDEC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ongoing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pursuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Meanwhile', 'RB', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cooperated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('begin', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mass', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('producing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('press', 'NN', '', 'O') ('presentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('volume', 'NN', '', 'O') ('purchaser', 'NN', '', 'O')
1983 Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Mitsubishi Wang December 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('meetings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('supplied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('drawings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('details', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('repeatedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('researched', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('possibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('proceed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('project', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('256K_memory_chips', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('assemble', 'VB', '', 'O') ('256K_SIMMs', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('incorporating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi 256K_memory_chips Mitsubishi 256K_SIMMs SIMM Wang Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('assess', 'VB', '', 'O') ('engineering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('contrary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('practice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('custom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exclusively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('purchaser', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('meetings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('context', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ongoing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contacts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discussed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('256K_SIMMs.2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('meeting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('suggested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('modify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('placing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
1985 two Mitsubishi Wang Mitsubishi one Clayton Mitsubishi SIMM Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('complied', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('went', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mass', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('256K_SIMMs', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('buying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi_SIMMs', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi 256K_SIMMs 1987 Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('never', 'RB', '', 'O') ('informed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1576', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('execute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('royalties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'605", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1987_and_1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi December 22 1989 Mitsubishi 1987_and_1988
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_4,_1992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Eastern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Wang Mitsubishi the Eastern District Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'605_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('assorted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('federal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('violations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi United_States_District_Court California
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('affirmative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'605_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('decoupling_capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('beneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('SIMMs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('decoupling_capacitors..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nine', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('memory_chips', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'605_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi nine nine Mitsubishi eight nine Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjudication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('capacitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang eight
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('June_12,_1986', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('accompanying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('remarks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('distinguishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('EDI_EDH-4816_publication', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang 7 10
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('unique', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('exactly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('capacitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('partial_summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'605_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Wang eight Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('close', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
JMOL Rule 50
__NEW_SENT__
('Next', 'JJ', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('fought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')
Next Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('legal_estoppel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('objected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('equitable_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('merged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('competing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('proposals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('One', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('exclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('let', 'VB', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('do', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('acts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
one One one
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('do', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('acts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implied-in-fact', 'CD', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preponderance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('transferred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('SIMM_invention', 'NN', 'EVENT', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('valuable_consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('existence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('transferred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi 1 Wang Mitsubishi 2 Wang SIMM_invention Mitsubishi 3 4 Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deciding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('proved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('existence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('you', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('consider', 'VB', '', 'O') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('one', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('consent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('persons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang Wang Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('you', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('right', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM_invention', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('you', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
SIMM_invention Mitsubishi Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Special', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Verdict', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preponderance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('licensed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Yes', 'UH', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'605", 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nondisclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi_SIMMs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('advisory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equitable_estoppel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unclean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hands', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi
__NEW_SENT__
('*1577', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('equitable_defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('draft', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adopting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equitable_defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('objected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('drafts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('protested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('wrote', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contradicted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('undermined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi Wang Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Furthermore', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('legal_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Furthermore Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Notwithstanding', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('objections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Findings', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fact', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Conclusions', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Law', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Mitsubishi Judgment the Findings of Fact and Conclusions of Law
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_6,_1995', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')
six
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('addressed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license_defense', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('believed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('valuable_consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('legal_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O')
First Wang Rule 50 JMOL Wang Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('partial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license_defense', 'NN', '', 'O')
Second Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Third', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('amend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('theory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mandated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assuming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('promised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('royalties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Third Wang Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('contending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('admitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('knew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('wired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('symmetrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('configuration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('express', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wiring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scheme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('concealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('best_mode', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitsubishi JMOL Clayton two two Mitsubishi Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Next', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalidation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Next Mitsubishi Wang 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Last', 'JJ', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('differences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('modules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SIMM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'513_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Last Mitsubishi five Mitsubishi SIMM
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
six
__NEW_SENT__
