('350_F.3d_1365', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INNOVATIVE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PROPERTIES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Minnesota_Mining', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Manufacturing_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AVERY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DENNISON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
Minnesota_Mining AVERY DENNISON
__NEW_SENT__
('No._03-1203', 'RB', 'ORG', 'B')
No._03-1203
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dec._2,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Jan._20,_2004', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('release_liner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adhesives', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Doty', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('185_F.Supp.2d_1031', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2002_WL_31628395', 'CD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Minnesota David S. Doty
__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embossed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patterns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sequentially', 'RB', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Clevenger Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Michel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('dissented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Michel Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1367', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Porcelli', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richardson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Frank P. Porcelli Fish & Richardson Boston Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scherkenbach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hillman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Madera', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kurt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Glitzenstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Adkisson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richardson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Frank E. Scherkenbach Robert E. Hillman Gregory A. Madera Kurt L. Glitzenstein John C. Adkisson Fish & Richardson P.C. Minneapolis Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rhodes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('3M_Innovative_Properties_Company', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('St.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Kevin H. Rhodes 3M_Innovative_Properties_Company St. Paul Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('Roderick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dorman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hennigan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bennett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dorman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Roderick G. Dorman Hennigan Bennett & Dorman LLP Los Angeles California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hadley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Armand', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ayazi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Lawrence M. Hadley Armand F. Ayazi
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Campbell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Renner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Otto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Boisselle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sklar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cleveland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Jay R. Campbell Cleveland Ohio
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3M_Innovative_Properties_Company', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Minnesota_Mining', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Manufacturing_Company', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('3M', 'UH', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Avery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dennison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Avery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5897,930', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬930_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Minnesota_Mining Manufacturing_Company 3M Defendant-Appellee Avery Dennison Avery 1 U.S. No._5897,930 the District of Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Avery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Avery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬930_patent', 'NN', 'LOC', 'B') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Avery Avery ¡¬930_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inconsistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Avery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('compete', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesive-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('graphics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O')
3M Avery
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('increasingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('image-suffused', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('world', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seems', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('targeted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('places', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exterior', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('busses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('trucks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vehicles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('locations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('advertising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('images', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('So', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('advertisements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('efficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pervasively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('pre-printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sheets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adhesive-backed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('films', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bumper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stickers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('release_liners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stripped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reveal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adhesive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('just', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('affixation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sticking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('films', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('experience', 'VB', '', 'O') ('difficulties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('positioning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('repeated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adjustments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('precisely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('repositioning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('damage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mar', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sought-after', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Additionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pockets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1368', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bubbles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('blisters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('become', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entrapped', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('perfectly', 'RB', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬930_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('release_liner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('avoids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('positioning', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('air-entrapment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('difficulties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
3M
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Avery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('EZ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Film', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('liner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬930_patent', 'NN', 'LOC', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benefits', 'NNS', '', 'O')
3M Avery 's EZ Film ¡¬930_patent
__NEW_SENT__
