('544_F.3d_1341', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ABBOTT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SANDOZ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
ABBOTT LABORATORIES
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2007-1300', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Oct._21,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Feb._23,_2009', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_release_formulations', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clarithromycin', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Coar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('500_F.Supp.2d_807', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('500_F.Supp.2d_846', 'RB', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois David H. Coar J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial_likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial_likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('likely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('suffer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('irreparable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('share', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('revenue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('balance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hardships', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('favored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gajarsa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gajarsa Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1343', 'LS', '', 'O') ('Ted', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Munger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tolles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Olson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ted G. Dane
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weinberger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jennifer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Polse', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rantanen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genevieve', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cox', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Jeffrey I. Weinberger Jennifer L. Polse Jason Rantanen Genevieve A. Cox San Francisco California
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Song', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los_Angeles', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Andrew W. Song
__NEW_SENT__
('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Feder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lord', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bissell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brook_LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Scott B. Feder Lord Bissell & Brook_LLP Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Keith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Parr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hugh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Balsam', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nelson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Keith D. Parr Kevin M. Nelson
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Shashank', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Upadhye', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Princeton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Shashank Upadhye Sandoz Inc. Princeton NJ
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Abramowitz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Myoka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Peterka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lord', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bissell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Brook_LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
David B. Abramowitz Myoka M. Kim James T. Peterka Lord Bissell & Brook_LLP Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Light', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Patents', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Patients', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Patents', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Castanias', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Day', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inventors', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Association', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Jeffrey L. Light Washington Gregory A. Castanias Jones Day Washington DC United Inventors Association
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Perry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Christopher S. Perry
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('concurs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('joins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Parts', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('VI', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge NEWMAN ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit.1', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('grant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pendente', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lite', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sandoz Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Abbott_Laboratories_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_release_formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibiotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clarithromycin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('BiaxinTHE_RXL', 'NN', '', 'O')
two Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clarithromycin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extended_release_formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
2005
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended_release_formulation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effectiveness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requisite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('extended_release_formulation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clarithromycin', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('approved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('charging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent_No._6010,718', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬718_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Patent_No._6551,616', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬616_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Sandoz Abbreviated New Drug Application the Food and Drug Administration August 25 2005 September 16 2005 Abbott Northern_District Illinois Sandoz United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('charged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1344', 'UH', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patent_No._6872,407', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('withdrawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬718_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended_release_pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specified', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parameters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬718_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 4 and 6 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal_environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('ingested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('orally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('induces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('statistically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('significantly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('mean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fluctuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('index', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plasma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immediate_release_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('maintaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bioavailability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immediate_release_composition', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O')
about 5 about 50 %
__NEW_SENT__
('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal_environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('maximum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('peak', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concentrations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immediate_release_pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concentration-time', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('curve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plasma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concentrations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immediate_release_pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O')
about 5 about 50 %
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extended_release_pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable_polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('taste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('profile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('immediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬616_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬718_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 2 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extended_release_pharmaceutical_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_polymer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erythromycin_derivative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clarithromycin', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sandoz
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preserving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('status', 'NN', '', 'O') ('quo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pendency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('Sandoz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
