('908_F.3d_1343', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ANCORA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('TECHNOLOGIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
ANCORA TECHNOLOGIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('HTC_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
HTC AMERICA INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('2018-1404', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2018', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
November 16 2018
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amended', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2018', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
November 20 2018
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('running', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('authorized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Western_District', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._2', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':16-cv-01919-RAJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('287_F.Supp.3d_1168', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the Western_District of Washington Richard A. Jones J. 287_F.Supp.3d_1168
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Taranto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ineligible', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Taranto Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Posture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dismiss', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('State', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NN', '', 'O')
State
__NEW_SENT__
('*1344', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('No._2', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') (':16-cv-01919-RAJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court Western_District No._2 Richard A. Jones
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lorelli', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brooks', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kushman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('PC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Southfield', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marc Lorelli Brooks Kushman Southfield MI
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cantor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Le', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rondini', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark A. John S. Le Roy John P. Rondini
__NEW_SENT__
('Irfan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lateef', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knobbe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Martens', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Olson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bear', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Irvine', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Irfan A. Lateef Knobbe Martens Olson & Bear LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Claassen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kiang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Re', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Brian Christopher Claassen Daniel C. Kiang Joseph R. Re
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wallach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Taranto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Dyk Wallach
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Taranto', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ancora_Technologies', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6,411,941', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Method', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Restricting', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Software', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Operation', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Within', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('License', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Limitation', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Ancora_Technologies Inc. 's U.S. 6,411,941 `` Method of Restricting Software Operation Within a License Limitation ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('running', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('authorized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2002', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('confirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
2002 2010
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ancora_Technologies', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apple', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('744_F.3d_732_(Fed._Cir._2014)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apple', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ancora_Technologies Inc. Apple Inc. 2011 Apple
__NEW_SENT__
('Ancora', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HTC_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2016', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Ancora HTC America 2016
__NEW_SENT__
('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('ineligible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', 'DATE', 'B') ('35', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('U.S.C', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
HTC under 35 101
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('HTC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'NN', '', 'O')
HTC
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Enfish', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Microsoft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('822_F.3d_1327_(Fed._Cir._2016)', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('authorities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ineligible', 'VB', '', 'O') ('subject_matter', 'NN', '', 'O')
Enfish LLC Microsoft Corp. 822_F.3d_1327_(Fed._Cir._2016)
__NEW_SENT__
('Rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('advance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concrete', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('assignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('functions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('computer_security', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computer_functionality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('eligible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
101
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Describing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior-art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('states', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('n', 'RB', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('umerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('identifying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('restricting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unauthorized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('12-14', 'CD', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('software-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('exist', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('writing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('hard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drive', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flaw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('signature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('changed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hackers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computer_functionality', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('19-26', 'CD', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Hardware-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('exist', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('inserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dongle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('port', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('authenticate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('authorization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('costly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inconvenient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('downloaded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('internet', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('27-32', 'CD', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assigning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('functions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1345', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('interact', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ways', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('relies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('40-41', 'CD', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unique', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('identification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('code', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('embedded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('read-only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ROM', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Basic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Input', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Output', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('modified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Basic Input Output System BIOS
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('45-51', 'CD', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('author', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('network', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('52-57', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('innovation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('check', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('modifiable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BIOS_memory-not', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('memory-to', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('store', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O')
BIOS_memory-not memory-to
__NEW_SENT__
('BIOS_memory', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('typically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('programs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('assist', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('start-up', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('verification_structures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('comparable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('software-licensing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('embodied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
BIOS_memory
__NEW_SENT__
('Using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('BIOS_memory', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other_memory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('computer_security', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('successfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hacking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('BIOS_memory', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('altering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rendering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inoperable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('much', 'RB', '', 'O') ('harder', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hacking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('store', 'VB', '', 'O') ('license-verification_information', 'NN', '', 'O')
BIOS_memory BIOS_memory
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4-17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Ancora', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('744', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('F.3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('733-34', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hardware', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('eliminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inconvenience', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hardware', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification_information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('harder', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('riskier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hacker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('tamper', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O')
3 4-17 Ancora 744 733-34
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('More', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('calls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('verification_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('created', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BIOS_memory', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ROM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('erased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('modified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('-for', ':', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Electrically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Erasable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Programmable', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Read', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Memory', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E2PROM', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('altered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('E2PROM', ':', '', 'O') ('manipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('commands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
BIOS_memory BIOS
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('65', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 65 2 5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('role', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('indicate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('60-62', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 60-62
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('implemented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('encrypting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer-specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') (')..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('encryption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('59-67', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('loaded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('volatile_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Random', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Access', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Memory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('verify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('authorization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('accesses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('retrieves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('therefrom', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('encrypts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('utilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('unique', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('key..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('compares', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('encrypted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('erasable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('modifiable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NN', '', 'O')
Random Access Memory
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('10-19', 'CD', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('encrypted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('match', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('halted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')
BIOS
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('lines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('19-26', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'941_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discuss', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('restricting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erasable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-volatile_memory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('volatile_memory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('*1346', 'FW', '', 'O') ('selecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('residing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('volatile_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('set', 'VB', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erasable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-volatile_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accommodating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('license_record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('erasable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-volatile_memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('BIOS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
BIOS BIOS at least one BIOS
__NEW_SENT__
('acting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('program', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verification', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('59', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6 59 7 4
__NEW_SENT__
