('633_F.3d_1042', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ASTRAZENECA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('APOTEX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'WRB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ASTRAZENECA LP AstraZeneca_AB APOTEX Apotex_Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2009-1381', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2009-1424', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nov._1,_2010', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Nov._1,_2010
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Jan._31,_2011', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pediatric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('asthma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Renee', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Marie', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bumb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('623_F.Supp.2d_579', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supplementing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('623_F.Supp.2d_615', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey Renee Bumb J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('budesonide', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('budesonide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dispersed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('label', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('generic_drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('induce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('consumers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1044', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denise', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Loring', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ropes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gray', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Denise L. Loring Ropes & New York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harnett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pablo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hendler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Derek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kato', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Christopher J. Harnett Pablo D. Hendler Derek M. Kato
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Basile', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('St.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Onge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Steward', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Johnston', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Reens', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stamford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Richard J. Basile Stamford CT
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aldrich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Roy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gross', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David W. Aldrich Roy D. Gross
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Shashank', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Upadhye', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Intellectual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Property', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Law', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toronto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ontario', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Shashank Upadhye Intellectual Property Law Apotex Inc. Toronto Ontario CA
__NEW_SENT__
('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rakoczy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rakoczy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Molino', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mazzochi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Siwik', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Breath', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
William A. Rakoczy Chicago Breath Limited
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Deanne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mazzochi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brody', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Deanne M. Mazzochi Amy D. Brody
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ruzich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Duane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Xttrium', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bennett-Paris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Anthony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kroon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('*1045', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mousley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kerry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McTigue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Richard T. Ruzich Duane Chicago Xttrium Laboratories Inc. Joseph M. Bennett-Paris Atlanta GA Anthony J. Fitzpatrick Christopher S. Kroon Boston MA Matthew C. Mousley Philadelphia PA Kerry B. McTigue Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*BRYSON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('concurring-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissenting-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'PRP$', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('launching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('budesonide', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distributed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('kit_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
LINN Circuit_Judge Apotex Inc. Apotex_Corp. Apotex United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey Apotex the United States Food and Drug Administration FDA AstraZeneca LP AstraZeneca_AB AstraZeneca AstraZeneca U.S
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('No._6598,603', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬603_Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('No._6899,099', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬099_Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Patents No._6598,603 No._6899,099
__NEW_SENT__
('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('kit_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('kit_claims', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Approval', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Process', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
The Drug Approval Process
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('procedures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obtaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('permission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('generic_drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cosmetic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('ch', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
the Federal Food Drug and Cosmetic Act
__NEW_SENT__
('675', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('52_Stat._1040_(1938)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('codified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scattered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
675 21
__NEW_SENT__
('Under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Act', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('approve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('distributed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interstate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('commerce', 'NN', '', 'O')
Act FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 355
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Drug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Application', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('examples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('label', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('clinical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('demonstrating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('safe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')
NDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('F', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
NDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('publishes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('names', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('associated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Approved', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Therapeutic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Equivalence', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Evaluations', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('commonly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Orange_Book', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
FDA the Approved Drug Products Therapeutic Equivalence Evaluations Orange_Book
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('505', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('paper_NDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Abbreviated New Drug Application 505 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('safety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('efficacy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bioequivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('route', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('strength', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_drug', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('unless', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('suitability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('requesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('permission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('differs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respects', 'NNS', '', 'O')
First FDA one
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iii', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('changes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('regulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('successful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('suitability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('labeling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_drug', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('labeling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('*1046', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Second FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('v', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('Third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Orange_Book', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('requesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('certifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('section_viii_statement', '.', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Third one four
__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chooses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('submit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('certify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('I', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that..', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('such_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('III', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') (')..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('such_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('expire', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('such_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_drug', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
II III IV
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('I', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2 IV
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('II', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('III', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('IV_certifications', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
IV_certifications
__NEW_SENT__
('Assuming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('regulatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('satisfied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('immediately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O')
FDA II
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
5
__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('delay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
a Paragraph III
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iii', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 2 21 355 5
__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('submit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section_viii_statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('viii', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 355 2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('remove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('carve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented_method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('label', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('C.F.R.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('314.92', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Novo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Nordisk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A/S', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Caraco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pharm', 'NNP', '', 'O')
21 314.92 1 Novo Nordisk
__NEW_SENT__
('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('601_F.3d_1359', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1361', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2010', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Along', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('with', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('section_viii_statement', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('generic', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('manufacturer', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('must', 'MD', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('submit', 'VB', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('a', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('proposed', 'VBN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('label', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('to', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented_method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Labs. Ltd. 1361 Along with the section_viii_statement the generic manufacturer must submit a proposed label to the FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('III', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section_viii_statement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('delay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_NDA', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('safety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('effectiveness_data', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 355 2
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_NDA', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('safety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('effectiveness_data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_NDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('submit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
