('932_F.2d_939', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ACOUSTICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DESIGN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('CONTROL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('ELECTRONICS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Insul-Art_Acoustics_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jack_Leonard', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harold_Goldstein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ACOUSTICAL DESIGN INC. Plaintiff-Appellee v. CONTROL ELECTRONICS COMPANY
__NEW_SENT__
('No._90-1296', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('May_1,_1991', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
May_1,_1991
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reena', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Raggi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Reena Raggi J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('notwithstanding', 'IN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prejudicial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('barring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('testifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('drafted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('warranting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assignor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 1 Court of Appeals 2 3 4
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*940', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mentlik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lerner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Littenberg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Krumholz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mentlik', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Westfield', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('N.J.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
William L. Mentlik Littenberg Krumholz & Mentlik N.J.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nelson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Roy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wepner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John R. Nelson Roy H. Wepner
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eichelburg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scully', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murphy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Presser', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Garden', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('N.Y.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert J. Eichelburg Scully Scott Murphy & Presser Garden City N.Y.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Roch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murphy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
William C. Roch Stephen D. Murphy
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Insul-Art_Acoustics_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jack_Leonard', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harold_Goldstein', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('March_30,_1990', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Control Electronics Company Inc. Control Jack_Leonard Harold_Goldstein March_30,_1990 United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('No._86-1692', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enjoining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
No._86-1692
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_17,_1977', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4,024,535', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('Harold_Goldstein', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('generator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('masking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O')
4,024,535
__NEW_SENT__
('Goldstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('assigned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Acoustical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Design', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Goldstein Acoustical Design Inc. ADI
__NEW_SENT__
('U.S._Patent', 'DT', '', 'O') ('4,185,167', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cunningham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sulewsky', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('masking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('package', 'NN', '', 'O')
4,185,167 January 22 1980 Donald R. Cunningham James E. Sulewsky
__NEW_SENT__
('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
ADI
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('masking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('disturbing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('background', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('permitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('alternation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('spectra', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1976', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Noise-Mask', 'JJ', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('product_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product_line', 'NN', '', 'O')
ADI Control 1976 Control Noise-Mask two ADI
__NEW_SENT__
('Control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
ADI
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contracted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('serve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('non-exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('masking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ceiling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('acoustical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('panels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('acoustical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('banners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('baffles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1982 ADI Control ADI Control
__NEW_SENT__
('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Control', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('commissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1976_and_1982', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('agreements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('terminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
ADI Control late 1985 Control ADI ADI 1982 1976_and_1982 ADI
__NEW_SENT__
('Control', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('continued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('masking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('notwithstanding', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('termination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('agreements', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_20,_1986', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
May_20,_1986 ADI United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('incorrect', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventorship', 'NN', '', 'O')
ADI
__NEW_SENT__
('ADI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*941', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'535_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignor_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('theory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Goldstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('principal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corporate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('privity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
ADI Goldstein Leonard
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('triable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seven', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1990 seven days
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('attempted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('invalidate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('items', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4,059,726', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Watters', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Radio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Speakers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Canada', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('RSC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Appellants two 4,059,726 Watters Radio Speakers of RSC
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('close', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('object', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('answers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interrogatories', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('notwithstanding', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JNOV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Appellants JNOV
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('10th', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('renewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignor_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attacking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'535_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
March 10th
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
