('345_F.3d_1318', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ARLINGTON', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('INDUSTRIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BRIDGEPORT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('FITTINGS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
ARLINGTON INDUSTRIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._02-1517', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('02-1518', 'CD', '', 'O')
Nos._02-1517
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Sept._25,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Middle', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Caputo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Middle District Pennsylvania
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flanges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flexing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('possess', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generalized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cantilever', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('general_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('base', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('general_area', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('lay', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('beneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('flexing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('corners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('contain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cut', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('score', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('physical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('indicating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('removability', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('concurred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dissented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1319', 'NFP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Noona', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kaufman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Canoles', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Norfolk', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
*1319 Stephen E. Noona Kaufman & Canoles P.C. Norfolk Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kristan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Burch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Kristan B. Burch
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hogge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kathryn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Clune', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dorsey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Whitney', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mark L. Hogge Kathryn L. Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fulbright', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jaworski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.L.P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Alan M. Anderson Fulbright & Jaworski L.L.P. Minneapolis Minnesota
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ungerman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Strauss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marcy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hogan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Greer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Mark E. Ungerman Michael J. Strauss Washington DC Marcy Hogan Greer Austin Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('concurs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bridgeport_Fittings', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Bridgeport', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington_Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._5736,674', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬674_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Bridgeport_Fittings Inc. Bridgeport Arlington_Industries Inc. Arlington Arlington United States Patent No._5736,674 ¡¬674_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Arlington_Indus.', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bridgeport_Fittings', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._3', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('99_CV_1857_(M.D._Pa._June_25,_2002)', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Arlington_Indus. Inc. Bridgeport_Fittings Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Bridgeport', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bridgeport
__NEW_SENT__
('Arlington_Indus.', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bridgeport_Fittings', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._3', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':99-CV-1857', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('M.D.Pa', 'CD', '', 'O')
Arlington_Indus. Inc. Bridgeport_Fittings Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('July_24,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bridgeport', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erroneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('errors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('jury_instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('prejudicially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Bridgeport three
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('advances', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bridgeport', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('import', 'VB', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('fails', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('persuade', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('prejudicial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bridgeport
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Initial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Activities', 'NNPS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Bridgeport', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('competitively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('make', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('supply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extenders', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Bridgeport Arlington
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1995_or_1996', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gretz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Gretz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('employee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('officials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('McShane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('McShane', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('McShane_Industries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomas J. Gretz Gretz Arlington Arlington William McShane McShane third
__NEW_SENT__
('McShane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patents', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._5042,673', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬673_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5,117,996', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬996_patent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extensions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
McShane two United States 5,117,996
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('McShane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extenders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('McShane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('tubular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('body..', 'UH', '', 'O') ('sized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device..', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
McShane McShane
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('673', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._28-33', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('¡¬996_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._2,_ll._28-33', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬ 673
__NEW_SENT__
('Embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extensions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬673', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬996_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1320.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('McShane_Industries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬673_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('designation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DADJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬673_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DADJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O')
DADJ
__NEW_SENT__
