('287_F.3d_1097', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ABBOTT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi-Tokyo_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('formerly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Tokyo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tanabe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DEY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('L.P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
ABBOTT LABORATORIES Mitsubishi-Tokyo_Pharmaceuticals Inc. Tokyo Tanabe Co. Ltd. DEY L.P. Dey Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._01-1374', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('April_23,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('June_14,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lung_surfactant_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('respiratory_distress_syndrome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('premature_babies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kennelly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2001_WL_558142', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois Matthew F. Kennelly J. 2001_WL_558142
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('earlier-filed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('later-filed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('hypothetical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('effectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('negate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('phospholipid_content', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('recitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('numeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('assertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Prost Circuit_Judge 1 2 3 4
__NEW_SENT__
('Vacated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1099', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Durkin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Brown', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Platt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Thomas M. Durkin Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Stephen A. Miller
__NEW_SENT__
('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McCubbrey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Coudert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Brothers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
J. Bruce McCubbrey Coudert Brothers of San_Francisco CA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Becker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Darrell', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Prescott', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert D. Becker San_Francisco CA New York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN GAJARSA
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PROST', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mitsubishi-Tokyo_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Dey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4397,839', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('``', '``', 'PRODUCT', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Plaintiffs Mitsubishi-Tokyo_Pharmaceuticals Inc. United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois Dey L.P. Dey Inc. the ÁÂ839_patent ``
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tokyo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tanabe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mitsubishi-Tokyo_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('licensee', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Dey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Dey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4338,301', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
I. Tokyo Tanabe Company Ltd. Mitsubishi-Tokyo_Pharmaceuticals Inc. United States Abbott Dey L.P. Dey Inc. ÁÂ839_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lung_surfactant_composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('respiratory_distress_syndrome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('premature_babies', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_21,_1980', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Drs', 'NNP', '', 'O')
May_21,_1980
__NEW_SENT__
('Fujiwara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Tanaka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Takei', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('desirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('spreading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lungs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ultra-alveolar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O')
Fujiwara Tanaka Takei
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('301', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('phospholipid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('neutral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lipid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('total_cholesterol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('carbohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('protein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lung_tissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mammal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('phospholipid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phospholipid_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('75.0-95.5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('neutral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lipid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1.8-14.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total_cholesterol_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.0-3.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbohydrate_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.1-1.5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protein_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.5-5.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('water_content', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1.7-6.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('minimum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('maximum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estimated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilhelmy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dropwise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('physiological_saline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.3-0.8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('£gg', 'UH', '', 'O') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('square_centimeter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('surface_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('2.1-8.6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('dynes/cm', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('48.2-58.0', 'CD', 'NORP', 'B') ('dynes/cm', 'CD', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('surface_areas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('21.BIG_TOKEN__0_cm_2__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('45.BIG_TOKEN__6_cm_2__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O')
Claim 1 75.0-95.5 % 1.8-14.0 % 0.0-3.0 % 0.1-1.5 % 0.5-5.0 % 1.7-6.0 % Wilhelmy 0.3-0.8 2.1-8.6 48.2-58.0
__NEW_SENT__
('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col._17,_l._59', 'CD', '', 'O') ('col._18,_l._6', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('labeled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('TA-546', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tanaka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('continued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('confirmatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('studies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TA-546', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('discover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ed', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tension-reducing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spreadability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adsorbability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gas-liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interface', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TA-546', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('free_fatty_acids', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1.0-27.7', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TA-546', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Tanaka three 1.0-27.7 %
__NEW_SENT__
('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ll.36-44', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('TA-546', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('1.0', 'CD', '', 'O') ('%', 'NN', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fatty', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O')
less than ÁÂ301_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('col._1,_ll._37-38', 'XX', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Table', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tanaka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('*1100', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benefits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('free_fatty_acids', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_4,_1982', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('four', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('months', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_6,_1982', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Id.at 5 Tanaka March_4,_1982 four months ÁÂ301_patent July_6,_1982
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
ÁÂ839_patent August 9 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('phospholipid', 'IN', '', 'O') ('neutral_fat', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total_cholesterol', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('free_fatty_acids', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('carbohydrate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('protein', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lung_tissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mammal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('optionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phosphatidylcholine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('neutral_fat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fatty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('phospholipid_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('68.6', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('90.7', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('neutral_fat', 'DT', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.3-13.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('total_cholesterol_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.0-8.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overall', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('free', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fatty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1.0-27.7', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carbohydrate_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.1-2.0', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('protein_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('0.0-3.5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water_content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('2.1-5.2', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dry', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('measured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('15¢X-25¢XC', 'CD', '', 'O')
Claim 1 ÁÂ839_patent 1 2 at least one 68.6 90.7 % 0.3-13.0 % 0.0-8.0 % 1.0-27.7 % 0.1-2.0 % 0.0-3.5 % 2.1-5.2 %
__NEW_SENT__
('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilhelmy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dropwise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('physiological_saline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.3-0.8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('£gg', 'UH', '', 'O') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('square_centimeter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('30.1-47.5', 'CD', 'NORP', 'B') ('dynes/cm', 'LS', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('54.BIG_TOKEN__0_cm_2__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O')
Wilhelmy 0.3-0.8 30.1-47.5
__NEW_SENT__
('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._17,_ll._13-31', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application-not', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('divisional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('301', 'CD', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('839', 'CD', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('shared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ839_patent ÁÂ301_application
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('examined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ÁÂ839
__NEW_SENT__
('He', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('things', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('March_17,_1981', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Examiner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('p.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('studied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suggestions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface-active_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Table', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('page', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Composition', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Material', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('property', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('spreading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ultra-alveolar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Table 4 Composition of the Material ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface-active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('isolated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ailment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('HMD', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('isolating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface-active_material', 'NN', '', 'O')
HMD
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('believed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('define', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('July_1,_1981', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Amendment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pp', 'XX', '', 'O')
July_1,_1981
__NEW_SENT__
('8-9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
8-9
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issuing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('112', 'CD', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')
35
__NEW_SENT__
('1_and_2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Amendment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Final', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rejection', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('allowance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1981.1', 'CD', '', 'O')
1_and_2 September 3 1981 December 17
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_4,_1982', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approximately', 'RB', 'DATE', 'B') ('three', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('months', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('301', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1101', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ839_application March_4,_1982 approximately three months ÁÂ301_application ÁÂ 301
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('anticipates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
ÁÂ839_application
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ839', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ839
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Forest', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('239_F.3d_1305', 'CD', '', 'O') ('57_USPQ2d_1794_(Fed.Cir.2001)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erroneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Forest', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Forest Laboratories Inc. 57_USPQ2d_1794_(Fed.Cir.2001) Forest
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('present', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('1312-13', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('57', 'CD', '', 'O') ('USPQ2d', 'NNS', 'GPE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1799-1800', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at USPQ2d
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('above', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('quoted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ301', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unmistakable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('assertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability..', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('percentage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('active_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('irrelevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Abbott
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1314', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('57', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('USPQ2d', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1800', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1314 57 1800
__NEW_SENT__
