('583_F.3d_766', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ASTRAZENECA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Astrazeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('UK', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TEVA', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
ASTRAZENECA PHARMACEUTICALS LP Astrazeneca UK TEVA PHARMACEUTICALS USA INC. Teva_Pharmaceutical_Industries Ltd. Defendants-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Sandoz Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2008-1480', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2008-1481', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._25,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antipsychotic_drug_quetiapine', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Joel', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Pisano', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('567_F.Supp.2d_683', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey Joel A.
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('provision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('implied', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('atypical', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('withholding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('atypical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*768', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Renk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Henry J. Renk
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lipsey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farabow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stevens', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('AstraZeneca_Pharmaceuticals_LP', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Bruce C. Haas Charles E. Lipsey Finnegan Henderson Farabow Garrett & Dunner LLP Reston VA Thomas A. Stevens Wilmington DE
__NEW_SENT__
('Ira', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Levy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Goodwin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Proctor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et', 'NN', '', 'O') ('al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Levy Goodwin New_York NY Teva Pharmaceuticals USA Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dinger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daryl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wiesen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bennett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Henry C. Dinger Daryl L. Wiesen John T. Bennett Boston
__NEW_SENT__
('Douglass', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hochstetler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schiff', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hardin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*769', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harp', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Beth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jacob', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Douglass C. Hochstetler Chicago IL Sandoz Inc. Jason G. Harp Beth D. Jacob
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Teva', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Teva_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_Pharmaceuticals_LP', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('UK', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct.1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('misrepresentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material_fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material_fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mislead', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva Pharmaceuticals USA Inc. Teva_Pharmaceutical_Industries Ltd. Sandoz Inc. United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey AstraZeneca_Pharmaceuticals_LP AstraZeneca Limited Appellants the Patent and Trademark Office AstraZeneca
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4879,288', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('288', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antipsychotic_drug_quetiapine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca United States Patent No._4879,288
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('markets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('quetiapine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('SEROQUELTHE_R', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
AstraZeneca SEROQUELTHE_R
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('288', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('atypical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('antipsychotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('typical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('antipsychotics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('involuntary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('movements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('torsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spasms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spasms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dystonia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('neck', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('back', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('protrusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tongue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tonic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spasms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limbs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('dyskinesias', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
¡¬
__NEW_SENT__
('Such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('undesirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unusual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antipsychotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('atypical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antipsychotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clozapine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('become', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1970s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('withdrawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('potentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('deadly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('white', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('agranulocytosis', 'NN', '', 'O')
the 1970s
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('quetiapine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
AstraZeneca FDA 1997
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬288_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('expires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
September 26 2011
__NEW_SENT__
('Teva', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('quetiapine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('certifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬288_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Sandoz 21 355 IV
__NEW_SENT__
('Paragraph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('certifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('technical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('permit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('federal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('regulatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 271 2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procedures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*770', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
AstraZeneca Teva Sandoz the District Court the District of New_Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iii', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬288_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
