('880_F.3d_1356', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('CORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WIRELESS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LICENSING', 'NN', '', 'O') ('S.A.R.L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I')
S.A.R.L. Plaintiff-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ELECTRONICS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mobilecomm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
LG Electronics Mobilecomm U.S.A. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2016-2684', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'RB', '', 'O') ('2017-1922', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2018', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
January 25 2018
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small_screens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mobile_telephones', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Nos._2', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-00911-JRG-RSP', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:14-cv-00912-JRG-SP', 'CD', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rodney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gilstrap', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2016_WL_1106438', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_ineligible_subject_matter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('2016_WL_4440255', 'CD', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas J. Rodney Gilstrap J. 2016_WL_1106438
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Moore Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('index', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('reasonable_jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computing_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('displayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unmistakably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('unlaunched_state', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Wallach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurring-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissenting-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Posture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judgment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Matter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('/Directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Verdict', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Motion', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Summary', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judgment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Motion for Judgment JMOL Motion for Summary Judgment
__NEW_SENT__
('*1357', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nos._2', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (':14-cv-00911-JRG-RSP', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:14-cv-00912-JRG-SP', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rodney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gilstrap', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court Texas Nos._2 J. Rodney Gilstrap
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Benjamin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Russ', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kabat', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Benjamin T. Wang Russ August Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Aaron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fenster', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hoffman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reza', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mirzaie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Kayvan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Noroozi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Noroozi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('PC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Santa', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Monica', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Marc Aaron Fenster Adam S. Hoffman Reza Mirzaie Kayvan B. Noroozi Noroozi Santa Monica
__NEW_SENT__
('Carter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Glasgow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Phillips', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Carter Glasgow Sidley Austin Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ryan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mayergoyz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weinberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Suh', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Seoul', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Korea', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Daniel Hay Ryan C. Morris Anna Mayergoyz Weinberg Peter H. Kang Palo Alto CA James Suh LG Electronics Inc. Seoul Korea
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("O'Malley", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wallach', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Moore O'Malley
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I')
Circuit_Judge Moore
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('concurring-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dissenting-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wallach', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Moore', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1359', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('8_and_9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._8713,476', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'476_patent", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('11_and_13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._8434,020', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ("'020_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_ineligible_subject_matter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6415,164', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Blanchard', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('anticipates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
LG Electronics Inc. LG Texas 1 11_and_13 35 2 U.S. Blanchard 35 102 3
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'476", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'020_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small_screens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mobile_telephones', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'020_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1_at_1', 'CD', '', 'O') (':14-24', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('access', 'NN', '', 'O') ('desired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('functions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electronic_devices', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2:20-44', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window_displays', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited_list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('functions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('commonly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accessed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_menu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('listing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2:55-59', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('launch', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('launch', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
two first
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('2:61-64', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('explain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window', '.', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('far', 'RB', '', 'O') ('faster', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('easier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('navigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approaches', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small_screens', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('2:64-65', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B')
Id.at 2:64-65
__NEW_SENT__
('Core_Wireless', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Licensing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('S.A.R.L', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Core_Wireless', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('8_and_9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'476_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('11_and_13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'020_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
LG LG 11_and_13
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('8_and_9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'476_patent", 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('depend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computing_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('display_screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computing_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('display', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('menu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('listing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('additionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('display', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('menu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('displays', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited_list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('launch', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respective_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enable', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('seen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respective_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('displayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more_applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('*1360', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('11_and_13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'020_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('depend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
11_and_13 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computing_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('display_screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('computing_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('display', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_menu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('listing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('additionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('configured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('display', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_menu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window_displays', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited_list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('offered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('launch', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('initiate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('displayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O')
LG 35 101
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'476_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('representative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evaluating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('eligibility', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('crediting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('characterization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('displaying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concepts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('window', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('unlaunched_state', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('computers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('phones', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LG
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('9561', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LG', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('identifie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('analog', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concepts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('context', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
LG
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('eligible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine-or-transformation', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1 machine-or-transformation
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('9562', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('O2', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Micro', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('situation', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('afforded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opportunity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('argue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O')
O2 Micro
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('10277-78', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('O2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Micro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Int', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", "''", 'TIME', 'B') ('l', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Beyond', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Innovation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('521_F.3d_1351', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1362', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Micro Int ' Beyond Innovation Tech Co. Fed
__NEW_SENT__
('Cir', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2008', 'LS', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('present', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fundamental', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('duty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('resolve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2008
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('displayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('un-launched', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('running', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
LG
__NEW_SENT__
('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_menu', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O')
LG
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('revisit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preserve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
LG Rule 50
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application_summary_window', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('main_menu', 'NN', '', 'O')
LG
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Blanchard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
LG Blanchard
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Core_Wireless', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('elected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('call', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('testify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rebuttal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('credit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LG', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accorded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'476", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'020_Patent", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('s', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
LG LG LG
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
18
__NEW_SENT__
('*1361', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('LG', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LG
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')2', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
