('804_F.2d_135', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('CARELLA', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('STARLIGHT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ARCHERY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('AND', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PRO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LINE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Richard F. CARELLA
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._86-728', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Oct._22,_1986', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Modified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Dec._12,_1986', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Harvey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('595_F.Supp._613', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('archery_bow_sight_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Michigan James Harvey J. 595_F.Supp._613
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Archer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'VBP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Office', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('settlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Archer Circuit_Judge 1 2 3 4
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*136', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ernie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brooks', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brooks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kushman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Southfield', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mich.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ernie L. Brooks Brooks & Kushman Mich.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lewry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brooks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kushman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Southfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mich.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McKinley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Price', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Heneveld', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Huizenga', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cooper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Grand_Rapids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Mich.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Thomas A. Lewry Brooks & Southfield Mich. Thomas M. McKinley Price Heneveld Huizenga & Cooper Mich.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Randall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Litton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Price', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Heneveld', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Huizenga', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cooper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Grand_Rapids', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Mich.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BISSELL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('COWEN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
Randall G. Litton Price Heneveld Huizenga & ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('DECISION', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*137', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Starlight', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Archery', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Starlight', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'XX', 'ORG', 'B') ('Company', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('595_F.Supp._613', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('224_USPQ_879_(1984)', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3365,800', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'800", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Appellants Starlight Archery Starlight Pro_Line Company United_States_District_Court Michigan 595_F.Supp._613 224_USPQ_879_(1984) U.S._Patent_No._3365,800 Richard F. Carella Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further_acts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('archery_bow_sight_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('30', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1968', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('7', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1967', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Carella January 30 1968 the United States Patent Trademark Office August 7 1967
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('archery_bow_sight_assembly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('support_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('adapted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attachment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('archery_bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('longitudinally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('support_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('longitudinal_distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('longitudinal_distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('archery_bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('support_means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('view', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('apparent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vertical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('height', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('longitudinal_distance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O')
ten 1 one one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('bow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('calibrated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sizes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('permits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rings', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('bow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('simultaneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('aiming', 'NN', '', 'O')
Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('archery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Starlight', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Starlight Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('approached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1978', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('bow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('refused', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Carella 1973 1978 Carella Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('advice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1978_and_1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
1978_and_1980 Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('Thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Model', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('M-525RF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('range', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('finder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hunting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('M-5096RF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('range', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('finder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Model M-525RF
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('bow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bracket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('slot', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('threaded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_6,_1981', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Starlight', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Starlight', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O')
May_6,_1981 Carella Starlight Starlight
__NEW_SENT__
('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('intervened', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('injunctive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relief', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Answer', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Counterclaims', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._3056,206', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'206", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Schneider', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rite-Flite', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('procured', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('settlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Perkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Civil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1581', 'CD', '', 'O') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Answer Counterclaims 1 Moore 2 3 Carella Perkins Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1968', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O')
August 5 1968
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('treble_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('warranted', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'XX', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('60,466.00', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('1,663.06', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prejudgment_interest', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further_acts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Pro_Line', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
60,466.00 1,663.06
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('award', 'VB', '', 'O') ('treble_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorneys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*BIG_TOKEN__138_Issues._1__BIG_TOKEN', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'206_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Schneider', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Flite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('sight', 'NN', '', 'O')
Moore the Schneider Rite Flite
__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('Whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3
__NEW_SENT__
('Whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'800_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('Whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('62,129.06', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('prejudgment_interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Carella', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
62,129.06 Carella
__NEW_SENT__
('II', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Validity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('imposes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('persuasion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('attacks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('282', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
35 282
__NEW_SENT__
('Facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('establishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Applied', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Digital', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Data', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('730_F.2d_1440', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1444', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('221_USPQ_385', 'CD', '', 'O') ('388', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1984', 'ADD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
RCA Corp. Applied Digital Data Systems Inc. 1444 388 Fed.Cir.1984
__NEW_SENT__
