('101_F.3d_100', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
101_F.3d_100
__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Walter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DURLING', 'VBG', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SPECTRUM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('FURNITURE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Walter E. DURLING SPECTRUM FURNITURE COMPANY INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._96-1119', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Nov._18,_1996', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contiguous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('three-piece', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sectional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sofa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Middle_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Erwin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Richard C. Erwin J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patented_design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Clevenger Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*101', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Clifton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ted', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hunt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Charlotte', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Clifton Ted Hunt Charlotte NC
__NEW_SENT__
('Blas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Arroyo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Seltzer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Park', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gibson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whittle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Charlotte', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Blas P. Arroyo Bell Seltzer Park & Gibson Jeffrey S. Whittle Charlotte NC
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SKELTON', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Walter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Middle_District', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('North_Carolina', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sole_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('States', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No', 'NN', '', 'O')
Walter E. Durling United_States_District_Court the Middle_District of North_Carolina
__NEW_SENT__
('Des', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('339,243', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'243_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
339,243 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('served', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('freelance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('furniture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Tupelo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Mississippi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
1989 Durling Tupelo Mississippi
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('spring', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('president', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('prepare', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low-cost', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sectional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sofa', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('table', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('integral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tables', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the spring of 1991 Global Furniture Company Durling
__NEW_SENT__
('Durling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('conceived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'243_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('went', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('business', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('spring', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Global the spring of 1992
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('customers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('asked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('furniture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('embodying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O')
Global Spectrum Furniture Co. Inc. Spectrum
__NEW_SENT__
('Spectrum', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contacted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('president', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('received', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('supply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('former', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('customer', 'NN', '', 'O')
Global Global
__NEW_SENT__
('*102.', 'UH', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('furniture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Global', 'NNP', '', 'O')
August 1992 Durling
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('matured', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'243_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
September 1993
__NEW_SENT__
('Shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Durling sued Spectrum
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Spectrum', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sole_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'243_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O')
Spectrum
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emphasized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sectional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Schweiger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Furniture', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Schweiger_model', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('below.1', 'NN', '', 'O')
Schweiger Furniture Industries Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heavily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('concession', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Schweiger_model', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('closest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ("'s", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('differences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'243_patent", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('insignificant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Durling
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Durling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented_design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sole_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'243_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Durling 35 103 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('Durling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('review', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1 1994
__NEW_SENT__
