('533_F.3d_1353', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('EISAI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DR.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('REDDY', 'RB', 'ORG', 'B') ("'S", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
EISAI CO. LTD. Eisai Inc. REDDY 'S LABORATORIES LTD. Laboratories Inc. Defendants-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2007-1397', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('2007-1398', 'CD', '', 'O')
Nos._2007-1397
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('July_21,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sept._16,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('lead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('duodenal_ulcers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('heartburn', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Gerard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lynch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('472_F.Supp.2d_493', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2006_WL_2872615', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Gerard E. Lynch J. 472_F.Supp.2d_493 2006_WL_2872615
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('commit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecuting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1355', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Malley", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paul', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hastings', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Janofsky', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Walker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Joseph M. O'Malley Jr. New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wexler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conca', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ji', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Clancy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Bruce M. Wexler David M. Conca Gary G. Ji Quinn E. Clancy
__NEW_SENT__
('Maurice', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ross', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Budd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Larner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Short', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Hills', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Miller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weinstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ellen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lowenthal', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dmitry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sheluho', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Maurice N. Ross Budd Larner P.C. Short Hills New Jersey Dr._Reddy 's Laboratories Ltd. Dr._Reddy 's Andrew J. Miller Louis H. Weinstein Ellen T. Lowenthal Dmitry V. Sheluho
__NEW_SENT__
('Henry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dinger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Goodwin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Procter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Elaine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blais', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hashmall', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Frederick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Emily', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rapalino', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
Henry C. Dinger Goodwin Boston Massachusetts Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc. Elaine H. Blais David M. Frederick H. Rein Emily L. Rapalino New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Eisai_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5045,552', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
New_York Eisai_Co. Ltd. Eisai Inc. Eisai U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Eisai_Co.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Pharms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('472_F.Supp.2d_493', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y.2006', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('SJ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Validity', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Eisai_Co.', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._03_Civ', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
USA Inc. S.D.N.Y.2006 Eisai_Co. Labs.
__NEW_SENT__
('9053', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y', 'NN', '', 'O')
9053
__NEW_SENT__
('Oct._5,_2006', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('SJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Enforceability', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Order', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Oct._5,_2006 SJ Enforceability Order
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Dr._Reddy 's Laboratories Ltd. Dr._Reddy 's Laboratories Inc. Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc. Teva Eisai Teva Eisai
__NEW_SENT__
('Eisai_Co.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._03_Civ', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Labs.
__NEW_SENT__
('9053', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2007_WL_1406565_(S.D.N.Y._May_11,_2007)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Trial_Order', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
9053
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('non-obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proffered', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('acts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('level', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Eisai
__NEW_SENT__
('*1356', 'UH', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rabeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬552_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Rabeprazole', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proton', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pump', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inhibitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('suppress', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inhibiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('H', 'NN', '', 'O') ('+K+ATPase', '.', '', 'O')
Rabeprazole
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distinctions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rabeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('refers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rabeprazole', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('rabeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rabeprazole', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Aciphex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('duodenal_ulcers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('heartburn', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Rabeprazole 1991 FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Aciphex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('garnering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', 'MONEY', 'B') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'I') ('1', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('billion', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('worldwide', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('yearly', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Aciphex over $ 1 billion yearly
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Applications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNPS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('21', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('355_and_35', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('271', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Aciphex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Teva Abbreviated New Drug Applications the Hatch-Waxman Act 21 U.S.C.¡± 355_and_35 U.S.C.¡± 271 Aciphex
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('artificial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('legally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cognizable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('see', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('Glaxo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('376_F.3d_1339', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1344', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Glaxo Group Ltd. Apotex Inc. 1344 2004 Eisai
__NEW_SENT__
('Eisai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proceeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outcome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Eisai Mylan Laboratories Inc. Mylan Pharmaceuticals Inc. Mylan ANDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Mylan', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bound', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mylan
__NEW_SENT__
('Eisai_Co.', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._04', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Civ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Eisai_Co. Ltd. Mylan Labs. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('656', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y', 'NN', '', 'O')
656
__NEW_SENT__
('Nov._3,_2004', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Nov._3,_2004
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva 1-6
__NEW_SENT__
('Trial_Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('6-7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6-7
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('maintains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬552_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Dr._Reddy six ¡¬552_patent 6 Teva
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva
__NEW_SENT__
('Neither', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
