('221_F.3d_1318', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('FISKARS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fiskars_Oy_AB', 'NNP', 'MONEY', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', 'MONEY', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HUNT', 'NN', '', 'O') ('MANUFACTURING', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CO.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
FISKARS INC. Fiskars_Oy_AB Plaintiffs-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('Joseph_F._Posillico', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sanctioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Party-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._98-1560', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('98-1566', 'CD', '', 'O')
Nos._98-1560
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_24,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Oct._10,_2000', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('circular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blades', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Barbara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crabb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury_verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Wisconsin Barbara B. Crabb J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('sanctioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pursuing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('baseless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1319', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lardner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David J. Harth Foley & Lardner Madison Wisconsin
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Joan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eads', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anat', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hakim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Nancy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Y.T', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Joan L. Eads Anat Hakim Nancy
__NEW_SENT__
('Hanewicz', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B')
Hanewicz
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jefferson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Perkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jefferson Perkins
__NEW_SENT__
('Joseph_F._Posillico', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Synnestvedt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lechner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sanctioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('party-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Joseph_F._Posillico Synnestvedt & Lechner LLP Philadelphia Pennsylvania
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Simpson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hecht', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark D. Simpson Gary A. Hecht
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Hunt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Hunt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin,1', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5322,001', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'001", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fiskars', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Paper', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Cutter', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('with', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Circular', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Blades', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fiskars_Oy_AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fiskars', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Fiskars', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Hunt Manufacturing Co. Hunt United_States_District_Court Wisconsin,1 United States Fiskars `` Paper Cutter with Circular Blades '' Fiskars_Oy_AB and Fiskars Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Hunt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Office', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Hunt the United States Patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Hunt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Joseph_F._Posillico', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Posillico', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('vexatiously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unreasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('multiplied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('incurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('liability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fiskars', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Hunt Joseph_F._Posillico Posillico Fiskars
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'001_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circular-blade', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('*1320.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('FIG._1', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('guillotine-type', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cutters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('employ', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('pivots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cutter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('18', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('enclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carriage_assembly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('rides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
one 18 16 14
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('secured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('board', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ends', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pivots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('27', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('insertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O')
27
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('biased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('springs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('48', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drawings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('carriage_assembly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('5_and_6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (':', ':', '', 'O')
48 5_and_6
__NEW_SENT__
