('110_F.3d_1573', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('GAMBRO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LUNDIA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BAXTER', 'VB', 'ORG', 'B') ('HEALTHCARE', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Defendant/Cross-Appellant', '.', '', 'O')
GAMBRO LUNDIA AB BAXTER HEALTHCARE
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._95-1530', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('96-1004', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I')
Nos._95-1530 96-1004
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_8,_1997', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('recalibrating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sensors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('kidney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('accurately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('measure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('impurities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Jim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carrigan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Colorado Jim R. Carrigan J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('derivation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1574', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Willem', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schuurman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Durkee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Willem G. Schuurman Arnold White & Durkee Austin
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Metteauer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael S. Metteauer Mark B. Wilson
__NEW_SENT__
('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Held', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant/cross-appellant', 'CD', '', 'O')
Timothy J. Malloy Held & Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ryan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vogler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Artz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert C. Ryan Gregory J. Vogler John S. Artz
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mattenson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('McGaw', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Park', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Charles R. Mattenson Baxter International Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ARCHER LOURIE
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lundia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Healthcare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Gambro Lundia AB Gambro Baxter Healthcare Corporation Baxter United_States_District_Court the District of Colorado
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4585,552', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('measurement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('fluid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ducts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
U.S. Patent No._4585,552 two
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recalibrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sensors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hemodialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('accurately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('measure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('impurities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('error', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('analyses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reverses', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Hemodialysis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('commonly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('removes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('contaminants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('excess', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('kidneys', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('function', 'VB', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Hemodialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('works', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('passing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyzer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('functions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1575', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('artificial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('kidney', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyzer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('porous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diffusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('membrane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('differential', 'NN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('membrane', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contaminants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('excess', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fluid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('diffuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('membrane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('impurities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('diffused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hemodialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('volume', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('volumes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('calculate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('removed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('calculation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('critical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hemodialysis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Removal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('much', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('too', 'RB', '', 'O') ('little', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('lead', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('severe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('death', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('British', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('bioengineering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('calculation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Repgreen Limited Repgreen British
__NEW_SENT__
('Keith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wittingham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('chief', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('designer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('monitoring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('UFM', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('1000', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('1977', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Keith Wittingham Repgreen the UFM 1000 late 1977
__NEW_SENT__
('Wittingham', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Professor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Sanderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Wittingham Michael Sanderson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('UFM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('electromagnetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('measure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyzer', 'NN', '', 'O')
1000 two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('quantity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('calibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accurate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('measurement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('direct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('clean_dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sensors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('calibration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('account', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clogging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outflow_sensor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('build', 'VB', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('behind', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outflow_sensor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disrupt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accuracy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('measurements', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Experts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inaccuracy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('drift', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1970s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('monitoring', 'NN', '', 'O')
the late 1970s Gambro
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1979', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Wittingham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gambro_engineers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('occasions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('discuss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('monitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
1979 Wittingham two Repgreen Gambro
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1979', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('went', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bankrupt', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('purchased', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('hemodialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('UFM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('1000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('monitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
July 1979 Repgreen Gambro Repgreen UFM 1000
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('acquiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('team', 'NN', '', 'O') ('worked', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ultrafiltration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('monitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Repgreen Gambro three years
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Gambro_engineers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Bengt-Ake', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gummesson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('refined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('monitoring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O')
June 1982 four Bengt-Ake Gummesson
__NEW_SENT__
('Their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sweden', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('28', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Gambro Sweden September 28 1982
__NEW_SENT__
('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S._application', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Gambro U.S._application September 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('Gunnar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Boberg', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('in-house', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Krumholz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Repgreen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prosecuted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S._application', 'NN', '', 'O')
Arnold Krumholz U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('German', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('German', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ("'756", 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1 German German
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('German-language', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('copy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('German', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ("'756", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('prepared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('fluent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('German', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Gambro German Boberg German
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('withdrew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_29,_1986', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
April_29,_1986
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('valves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('direct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('clean_dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyzer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('recalibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sensors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gambro
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('valve', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('direct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('clean_dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyzer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensor', 'NN', '', 'O')
first second
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('recalibrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('momentarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('blocks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('passage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contaminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outflow_sensor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clean_dialysate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outflow_sensor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recalibrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detectors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clean_dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('intake', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('outflow_sensors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recalibration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hemodialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('continues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contaminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dialysate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('sensor', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('reads', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equipment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyser', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('measuring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_fluid_streams', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('clean', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyser', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('spent', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyser', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1 1 first
__NEW_SENT__
('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('duct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('therethrough', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_duct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('therethrough', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('measuring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('measuring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1576', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_fluid_streams', ',', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_ducts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('transferring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preventing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('second_duct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_ducts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('passing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialyser', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('altering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_ducts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_ducts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('measured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first_fluid_stream', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('flowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second_ducts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('adaptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O')
2 first 3 4 first first 5 first first first 6 first
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enumeration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1984', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('acquired', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dialysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equipment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('division', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Extracorporeal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
1984 Baxter Extracorporeal Inc
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissatisfied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accuracy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Extracorporeal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Baxter_SPS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('550', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Extracorporeal Baxter December 1987
__NEW_SENT__
('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Colorado', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Baxter_SPS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('550', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Gambro Baxter the District Court the District of Colorado March 1992 550
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Baxter
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ten-day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Gambro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('derivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 Gambro
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Baxter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'552_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Baxter
__NEW_SENT__
('Further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('award', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
