('925_F.2d_1435', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('HALLIBURTON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SCHLUMBERGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TECHNOLOGY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._90-1191', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Feb._13,_1991', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('March_15,_1991', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentholder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Sim', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lake', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('III', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('722_F.Supp._324', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cumulative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1436', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Henderson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Farabow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Garrett', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dunner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Donald R. Dunner D.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Allen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sokal', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stroup', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Allen M. Sokal Richard L. Stroup
__NEW_SENT__
('Ronald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Botts', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dallas', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tex.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ronald L. Palmer Baker & Botts Dallas Tex.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mitchell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lukin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sylvia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('M.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Egner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Baker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Botts', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tex', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mitchell D. Lukin
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dana', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Raymond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berkley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brumbaugh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Graves', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Donohue', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Raymond', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dana M. Raymond Richard G. Berkley New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SKELTON', 'VBD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Senior', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
NEWMAN SKELTON Senior Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1437', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Schlumberger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Technology', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Schlumberger', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._4388,529', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'529_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('4,409,481', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'481_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,424,444', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'444_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Halliburton Company Halliburton Schlumberger Technology Corporation Schlumberger U.S. Nos._4388,529 4,409,481 4,424,444
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('embrace', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('tools', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('neutron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('logging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wells', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_energy_neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('measure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('underground', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('geological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formations', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas Halliburton the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Hence', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Halliburton
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('refused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enforce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Schlumberger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('3,375,000.00', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expenses', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Halliburton 3,375,000.00
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Schlumberger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Technology', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('722_F.Supp._324', 'CD', '', 'O') ('12_USPQ2d_1765_(S.D.Tex.1989)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Halliburton Co. Schlumberger Technology Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Halliburton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O')
Halliburton
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reverses', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('producers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('use', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('logging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('detect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('geological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formations', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lowering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complex', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('instrument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('well', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('borehole', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('down', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('borehole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('measures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('logs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('geological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('neutron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('logging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instrument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('high_energy_neutrons', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('million', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('electron_volts', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('descends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('borehole', 'NN', '', 'O')
14 million
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('collide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('borehole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('earth', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('collisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('high-energy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inelastic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gamma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rays', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('collisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('drain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('slow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('down', 'RP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('moderate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('become', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('thermal_neutrons', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('0.025', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('electron_volts', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
0.025
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nuclei', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('capture', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thermal_neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('capture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('neutron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('occurs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('capturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('emit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capture_gamma_rays', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') ('detects', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('capture_gamma_rays', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('capture_gamma_rays', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('reveals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('neutron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('population', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('neutron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decay', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('capture', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rates', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('measuring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thermal_neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('tells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('much', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('formations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('borehole', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('captures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('thermal_neutrons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('saltwater', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'481_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('depicts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tool', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
