('323_F.3d_1354', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('HOFFMANN-LA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ROCHE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Roche_Molecular_Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PROMEGA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
ROCHE INC. Roche_Molecular_Systems Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._00-1372', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DECIDED', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('March_31,_2003', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_11,_2003', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Northern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Vaughn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('R.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Walker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Northern District
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fact_issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('particular_experiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clear_error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('particular_experiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('purification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('experiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thermus_aquaticus', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Taq', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('bacterium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrophobicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Taq_bacterium', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sizing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('experiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('accurate', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fact_issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('memorandum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('employee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('molecular_weights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('purified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('thermostable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('6', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('erroneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('stating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('purification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('protocol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('deemed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge 1 2 3 Thermus_aquaticus 4 5 6
__NEW_SENT__
('Vacated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pauline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Pauline Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1357', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jennifer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Gordon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pennie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Jennifer Gordon Pennie & Edmonds LLP New York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('her', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wagner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Todd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Krause', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Todd A. Wagner Todd L. Krause
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Barbara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Caulfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Orrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Herrington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sutcliffe_LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Barbara A. Caulfield Herrington & Sutcliffe_LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Leslie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Misrock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pennie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Heidi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Keefe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Myra', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pasek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Orrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Herrington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sutcliffe_LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O')
S. Leslie Misrock Pennie & Edmonds Heidi Keefe Myra J. Pasek
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Troupis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Best', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Friedrich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('WI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
James R. Troupis Michael Best & Friedrich Madison WI
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Husmann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Donald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Best', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scheller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Karla', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael E. Husmann J. Donald Best John C. Scheller Karla M. Davis
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carroll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kamrin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MacKnight', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Medlen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carroll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Russell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Skjerven', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Morrill', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MacPherson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Franklin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Friel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Jose', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Peter G. Carroll Kamrin T. MacKnight Medlen & Carroll LLP San_Francisco CA Russell L. Johnson San Jose
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
Circuit_Judge PAULINE NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PCR', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('scientists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('beginning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deoxyribonucleic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('generate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('copies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1358', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('short', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PCR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('synthesize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('significant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('advances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molecular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('biology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pathology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('identification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trace', 'NN', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hair', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PCR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('segment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('strands', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first two
__NEW_SENT__
('Then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pieces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('synthetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('primers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('annealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('locations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('strands', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Enzymes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DNA_polymerases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('extend', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complementary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nucleotide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nucleotide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('strand', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('creates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('double-stranded', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('helices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('strands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('helix', 'NN', '', 'O')
two two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('strand_separation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('primer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('annealment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('extension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('repeatedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('DNA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('strands', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('PCR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_temperatures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('strand_separation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('destroyed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('drive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction', 'NN', '', 'O')
PCR first
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beginning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cycle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cumbersome', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DNA_polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Thermus_aquaticus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Taq', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('bacterium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('geysers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('springs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_temperatures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('withstand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PCR', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Taq
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Taq', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PCR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('much', 'RB', '', 'O') ('faster', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('efficient', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_17,_1987', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Cetus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predecessor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Hoffmann-La', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Roche_Molecular_Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._07', 'NN', '', 'O') ('/063,509', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬509_application', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purified', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('thermostable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O')
June_17,_1987 Cetus Corporation Hoffmann-La Roche Inc. Roche_Molecular_Systems Inc. Roche U.S. Patent Application ¡¬509_application
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬509_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('named', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gelfand', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Cetus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('scientist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('knowledgeable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Taq_enzyme', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ms.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Susanne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Stoffel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gelfand', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('technician', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬509_application David Gelfand Cetus Taq_enzyme Susanne Stoffel Gelfand
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broadest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Taq_enzyme', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('office', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('variety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
November 1 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticipation/obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('journal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('et_al.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kaledin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('et_al.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('DNA_polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Taq_bacterium', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Chien et_al. Kaledin
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('differed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('estimates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Taq', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kaledin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Taq Chien Kaledin
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suggested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proteins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('behave', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('anomalously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('subjected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SDS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('page', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('estimate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O')
SDS
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'LS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NN', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('experimental', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parameters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('literature', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_17,_1989', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('canceling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broadest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
three 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Purified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('thermostable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Thermus_aquaticus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('DNA_polymerase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('migrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denaturing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('polyacrylamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('faster', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('phosphorylase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('B', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('slowly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('bovine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('serum', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('albumin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('estimated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('86,000-90,000', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('daltons', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phosphorylase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('B', 'NN', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1359', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('92,500', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('daltons', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I')
86,000-90,000 daltons 92,500 daltons
__NEW_SENT__
('U.S._Patent_No._4889,818', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('col._44,_ll._46-52', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remarks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('accompanying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-part', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('differences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('specific_activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fidelity', 'NN', '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('belief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prior_art_enzymes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('far', 'RB', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('pure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Chien', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kaledin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('preparations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Second Chien Kaledin
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific_activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_enzyme', 'ADD', '', 'O')
ten
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬509_application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4889,818', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('¡¬818_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
¡¬509_application `` the ¡¬818_patent `` December 26 1989
__NEW_SENT__
('Cetus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('licensed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('¡¬818_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('to', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Promega', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Cetus the ¡¬818_patent to Promega Corporation June 1990
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cetus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬818_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Promega', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('breached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Cetus Roche Promega
__NEW_SENT__
('Roche', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contract', 'NN', '', 'O')
Roche
__NEW_SENT__
('Promega', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬818_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('soon', 'RB', '', 'O') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('focus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬818_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
August 1996 four
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬818_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('addressed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O')
eight three
__NEW_SENT__
('Roche', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Roche
__NEW_SENT__
('II', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heavy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('misrepresentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('deceive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Manville', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sales', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paramount', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sys.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('917_F.2d_544', 'CD', '', 'O') ('552', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('16_USPQ2d_1587', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('1593', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1990', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Kingsdown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Med', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Consultants', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hollister', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('863_F.2d_867', 'CD', '', 'O') ('872', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('9_USPQ2d_1384', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1389', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1988', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Manville Sales Corp. Paramount Sys. Inc. 552 16_USPQ2d_1587 Fed.Cir.1990 Kingsdown Med Consultants Ltd. Hollister Inc. 872 1389
__NEW_SENT__
('Once', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requisite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('levels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('warrant', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Molins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Textron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('48_F.3d_1172', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1178', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('33_USPQ2d_1823', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1827', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1995', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Molins PLC Textron Inc. 1178
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('difficult', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reviewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('deferentially', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('reviewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear_error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('overturned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('definite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('firm', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conviction', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mistake', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Molins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('48', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('F.3d', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1178', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('33', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('USPQ2d', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1827', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Molins 48 F.3d 1178 33 1827
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('assessment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reviewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('omissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('grouped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('representations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('molecular_weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Taq_enzymes', 'NNPS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('representations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Example', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('procedures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('achieved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('representations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('comparative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fidelity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('template', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dependence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1360', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_enzymes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
three 1 2 Example VI one 3
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('analyze', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('upholding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('overturning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B')
three as to two three third
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dissent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('overturn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('criticizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assessing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O')
three
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('recognize', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('applies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('note', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('task', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reviewing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determinations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('instance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('infected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mind', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('turn', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
