('991_F.2d_768', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('INTERNATIONAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VISUAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CROWN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('METAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MANUFACTURING', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
INTERNATIONAL VISUAL CROWN METAL MANUFACTURING CO. INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._92-1262', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('April_15,_1993', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('magnetically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('secured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Holderman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Northern_District Illinois James F. Holderman Jr. J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('apart', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('magnet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('decide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('concurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lourie Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*769', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dudine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Darby', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Darby', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
William F. Dudine Jr. New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Myron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cass', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Silverman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cass', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Singer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert C. Sullivan Jr. Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Herbert J
__NEW_SENT__
('Singer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Albert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brunett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Albert J. Brunett
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
NIES LOURIE CLEVENGER Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*770', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CURIAM', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Visual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IVC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('March_9,_1992', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Metal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
International Visual Corporation IVC March_9,_1992 United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois Crown Metal Manufacturing
__NEW_SENT__
('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Visual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Metal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mfg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('22_USPQ2d_1778', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1992_WL_38376_(N.D.Ill.1992)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
International Visual Corp. Crown Metal Mfg Co. 1992_WL_38376_(N.D.Ill.1992)
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('incorrectly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('interpreted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IVC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4,677,780', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VBP', '', 'O')
IVC U.S. 4,677,780
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'780_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Magnetically', 'RB', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Secured', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Display', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Apparatus', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
`` Magnetically Secured Display Apparatus ''
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('IVC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('GRIPPER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-BIG_TOKEN__3_and_6__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-10', ':', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 10 1989 IVC Crown
__NEW_SENT__
('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O')
Crown
__NEW_SENT__
('IVC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('move', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
IVC Crown Crown
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('IVC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Crown', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('entirety', 'NN', '', 'O')
IVC Crown
__NEW_SENT__
