('822_F.3d_1355', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('INTENDIS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('GMBH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Intraserv_GmbH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Co._KG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bayer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Healthcare', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GLENMARK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
GLENMARK PHARMACEUTICALS INC. USA Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2015-1902', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('May_16,_2016', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('licensees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_drug_manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Food', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Drug_Administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('topical_treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inflammatory_papules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pustules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mild', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('moderate_rosacea', 'VB', '', 'O')
FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Markman_hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Sue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('117_F.Supp.3d_549', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('licensees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('proved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the District of Delaware Sue L. Robinson J. 117_F.Supp.3d_549
__NEW_SENT__
('Manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Moore Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear_error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('isopropyl_myristate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_drug_manufacturer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('triglyceride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lecithin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reversible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ensnare', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history_estoppel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear_error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('objective_indicia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1358', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bradford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Badke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sidley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Bradford J. Badke Sidley Austin LLP New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sona', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('De', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Sona De
__NEW_SENT__
('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jay', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Goodwin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Procter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
William M. Jay Goodwin Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Burgess', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Elizabeth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Holland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Linnea', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cipriano', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Huiya', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Zimmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Brian Timothy Burgess Elizabeth Linnea P. Cipriano Wu New_York NY David Zimmer San Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MOORE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('TARANTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
PROST MOORE
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Act,1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd. Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Inc. USA 's Glenmark 2 FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'GPE', 'I') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Intendis_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Intraserv_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co._KG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HealthCare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Glenmark United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware 's Intendis_GmbH Intraserv_GmbH & Co._KG Bayer HealthCare Pharmaceuticals Inc. Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1359', 'LS', '', 'O') ('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('HealthCare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('No._21470', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('azelaic_acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('therapeutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concentration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topical_treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inflammatory_papules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pustules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mild', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('moderate_rosacea', 'VB', '', 'O')
Appellee Bayer HealthCare Pharmaceuticals Inc. New Drug Application NDA FinaceaTHE_R_Gel 15 %
__NEW_SENT__
('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inactive_ingredients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('triglycerides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lecithin', 'NN', '', 'O')
FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hydrogel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semisolid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gelling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('dispersed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('insoluble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('liquids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('Intendis_GmbH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('117_F.Supp.3d_549', 'CD', '', 'O') ('567-68', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2015', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Glenmark Pharm Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Food', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Drug_Administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Approved', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Therapeutic', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('Equivalence', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('Evaluation', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('commonly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'EVENT', 'B') ('Orange', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Book', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('lists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._6534,070', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
FDA Approved Drug Products Therapeutic Equivalence Evaluation the Orange Book U.S. FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Composition', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('with', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Azelaic', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Acid', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Intraserv_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exclusively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Intendis_GmbH', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Composition with Azelaic Acid '' Appellee Intraserv_GmbH & Co. Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('provisional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('12', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
March 2003 February 12 1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Sole', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('070', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('azelaic_acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('therapeutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concentration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('5_to_20', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('triacylglyceride3', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concentration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.BIG_TOKEN__5_to_5__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O')
5_to_20 % at least one 0.BIG_TOKEN__5_to_5__BIG_TOKEN %
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iv', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('propylene', 'NN', '', 'O') ('glycol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('v', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('polysorbate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('phase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('polyacrylic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vi', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('lecithin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrogel', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('28-39', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
FDA FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
IV 21 355 2 IV ¡¬070_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('generic_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('isopropyl_myristate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('triglyceride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lecithin', 'NN', '', 'O')
FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('USA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('informed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
21 355 2 Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('070', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Appellees Glenmark the District of Delaware Glenmark 35 271 2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Markman_hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('five-day', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('5-11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 21 2015 February 5-11 2015
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_27,_2015', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-12', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1-12 ¡¬070_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('isopropyl_myristate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1360', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('generic_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('triglyceride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lecithin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('function-way-result', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('encompass', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution_history_estoppel', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('every', 'DT', '', 'O') ('element', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Glenmark 1 Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('marketed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('topical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('20', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('azelaic_acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cream', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SkinorenTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
FinaceaTHE_R_Gel Bayer 20 %
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('pursue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrogel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('azelaic_acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('SkinorenTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('undesirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('qualities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('phase', 'NN', '', 'O') ('separation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emulsion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whitening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('spreadability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art_references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Glenmark 1
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expectation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O')
Glenmark Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objective_indicia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FinaceaTHE_R_Gel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('weighed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O')
FinaceaTHE_R_Gel
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('approve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('18', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2018', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬070_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
August 14 2015 Appellees FDA Glenmark November 18 2018
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
