('536_F.3d_1361', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'IN', '', 'O') ('OMEPRAZOLE', '``', '', 'O') ('PATENT', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LITIGATION', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Astrazeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Aktiebolaget_Hassle', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('KBI-E', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('KBI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Astrazeneca_LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Torpharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Astrazeneca AB Aktiebolaget_Hassle KBI-E Inc. KBI Inc. Astrazeneca_LP Apotex Inc. Torpharm Inc. Defendants-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Impax_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2007-1414', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2007-1416', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2007-1458', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2007-1459', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._20,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Oct._9,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pioneer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal_disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Barbara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('490_F.Supp.2d_381', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Barbara S. Jones J. 490_F.Supp.2d_381
__NEW_SENT__
('Applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bryson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Bryson Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('post-expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('remedy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pediatric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exclusivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stabilized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('desiccant', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compound', 'RP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('created', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('micro-pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('preparation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('intended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inert_subcoating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compounds', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ARC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('micro-pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')
ARC
__NEW_SENT__
('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('inert_subcoating', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('identifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('ready', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clinical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('studies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('real-time', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tablets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('European', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')
European
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1364', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Errol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taylor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Milbank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tweed', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hadley', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('McCloy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Errol B. Taylor New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Fredrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zullow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Griem', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kass', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Claire', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gilmartin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Emily', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kunz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Fredrick M. Zullow John M. Griem Lawrence T. Kass David C. Haber Claire A. Gilmartin Emily J. Kunz
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Breisblatt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Katten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Muchin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rosenmann', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'UH', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('et', 'FW', '', 'O') ('al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Robert B. Breisblatt Katten Chicago IL Apotex_Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Silver', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bruce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chasan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Allan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fried', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Youngblood', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bassler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Caesar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rivise', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bernstein', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cohen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pokotilow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('PA.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Toney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sutherland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Asbill', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Brennan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Impax_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('North', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('N.E.B', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert S. Silver Bruce J. Chasan Allan H. Fried William C. Youngblood Marc B. Bassler Philadelphia Jeffrey J. Toney Atlanta GA John L. North
__NEW_SENT__
('Minnear', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jackie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Toney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kristin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Timm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Blair', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jacobs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Minnear Jackie L. Toney Kristin M. Timm Atlanta Blair M. Jacobs Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Leslie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomasson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Leslie S. Thomasson
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BRYSON', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Apotex_Corp.', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Torpharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax_Laboratories', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'XX', '', 'O')
Apotex Inc. Torpharm Inc. Apotex Impax_Laboratories Inc. United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('Apotex', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multidistrict', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initiated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Astrazeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Aktiebolaget_Hassle', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('KBI-E', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('KBI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Astrazeneca_LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Astra', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Astra', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Prilosec', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('acid-related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gastrointestinal_disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Impax Astrazeneca AB Aktiebolaget_Hassle KBI-E Inc. KBI Inc. Astrazeneca_LP Astra Astra Prilosec
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('divided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('waves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wave', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('wave', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Omeprazole', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('*1365', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Litigation', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('84_Fed.Appx._76_(Fed.Cir.2003)', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Omeprazole_Patent_Litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('483_F.3d_1364_(Fed.Cir.2007)', 'CD', '', 'O')
first Omeprazole Patent *1365 Litigation
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arise', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('wave', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('wave', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
second Mylan Laboratories Inc. Apotex Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('Astra', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('recently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Omeprazole_Patent_Litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2008_WL_2369864_(Fed.Cir._June_10,_2008)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Astra Mylan
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O')
Apotex Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4786,505', 'JJ', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('505', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4853,230', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬230_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
U.S._Patent_No._4786,505 505
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('preparations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Prilosec', 'NNS', 'GPE', 'B')
two Prilosec
__NEW_SENT__
('Omeprazole', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('potent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inhibitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('susceptible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('degradation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('acid-reacting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('neutral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('media', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Omeprazole
__NEW_SENT__
('Its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('organic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solvents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('protect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Enteric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coatings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('acidic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('decompose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discoloration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('decreasing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('increase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('storage_stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compounds', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ARCs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ARC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('compromise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating', 'NN', '', 'O')
ARC
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('diffusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('juices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('dissolve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ARCs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dissolve', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬505_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('33', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('col.', 'VB', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 33 2 4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬505', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬230_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('solved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inert_subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disintegrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬505
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('increases', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('storage_stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resistance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('degrading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Once', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intestine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solubility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('release', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_core', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬505_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._5,_ll._19-68', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬505_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('preparation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬505_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('preparation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('core_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('omeprazole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('plus', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_omeprazole_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('plus', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_omeprazole_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alone', 'RB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inert_subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('soluble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disintegrating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('core_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more_layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('among', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tablet_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('polymeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('film-forming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬230_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('broadly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preparation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('acid-labile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'PERSON', 'I') ('¡¬230_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('preparation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('acid-labile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1366', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('active_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('acid_labile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('active_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('acid_labile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('active_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline_reacting_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('active_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inert_subcoating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dissolves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disintegrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('core_region', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subcoating', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more_layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tablet_excipients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('film-forming', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alkaline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Claim 1 of the one
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating_layer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subcoating_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subcoating_layer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('isolates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alkaline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('core', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enteric_coating_layer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preparation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
