('774_F.2d_1132', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('INTERCONNECT', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('PLANNING', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('FEIL', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('O.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carpenter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('V_Band', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Turret', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Equipment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Thomas E. FEIL Robert O. Carpenter V_Band Systems Inc. Turret Equipment Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._84-1467', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('85-565', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Oct._9,_1985', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Oct._9,_1985
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('587_F.Supp._1495', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Duffy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('counterclaim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent_no._31144', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multistation_telephone_switching_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_York Kevin Thomas Duffy J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent_no._31144', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multistation_telephone_switching_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Vacated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1133', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Alfred', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ewert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morgan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Foley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alfred P. Ewert Morgan Finnegan Pine Foley & Lee
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jerome', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Molan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McGrath', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jerome G. Lee Robert A. Molan Richard J. McGrath
__NEW_SENT__
('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Karasik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sherman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Citron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('New_York_City', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Howard Karasik Sherman & P.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kurland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stiefel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gross', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kurland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('New_York_City', 'NN', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Feil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('et', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('al', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Lawrence G. Kurland Stiefel Gross Kurland & Pavane P.C. Feil et al
__NEW_SENT__
(';', ':', '', 'O') ('Lance', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lieberman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dolgin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Towne', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dolgin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sawyer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Horton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stern', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Theodore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steingut', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steingut', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Weiner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fox', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Stern', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lance J. Lieberman Daniel L. Dolgin Sawyer & Horton Peter R. Stern Theodore S. Steingut Berger Weiner Fox & Stern
__NEW_SENT__
('*1134', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DAVIS', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('SMITH', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
DAVIS SMITH NEWMAN Circuit_Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Interconnect', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Planning', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Interconnect_Planning_Corp.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Feil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('587_F.Supp._1495', 'CD', '', 'O') ('223_USPQ_961_(S.D.N.Y.1984)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Reissue_Patent_No._31144', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Multi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Station', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Telephone', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Switching', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('System', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Feil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conditions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Interconnect Planning Corporation IPC United_States_District_Court Feil IPC Thomas E. Feil 35 103 IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')
103
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reissue_Patent_No._31144', 'NNS', 'NORP', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('trader_turrets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('multi-line', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consoles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('financial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('community', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('networks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('securities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('commodities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('currency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('like', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Reissue_Patent_No._31144
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('facilitate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('concurrent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('telephone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('traders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sources', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('price', 'NN', '', 'O') ('information', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('transactions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('meeting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('demands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('busy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('often', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hectic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('financial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enterprises', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Trading', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rooms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('house', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('hundred', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('trader_turrets', 'NNS', '', 'O')
a hundred
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('connections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('needs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('communication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('networks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('complex', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reliability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('momentary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('failures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('extremely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('costly', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Feil_trader_turrets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('achieved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('displacing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('attributes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Feil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('architecture', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('enabled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ease', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('capacity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reliability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O')
IPC Feil
__NEW_SENT__
('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Feil_trader_turrets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('grew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('320', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('000_for_20', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1974', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('27,900', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('000_for_3500', 'CD', '', 'O') ('units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
IPC 320 1974 first year 27,900 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('Thomas_Feil', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('formerly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('officer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1977', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Mr._Feil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('V_Band', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Mr._Feil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('left', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('V_Band', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('president', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('chief', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('executive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('officer', 'NN', '', 'O')
1977 V_Band Systems Inc. 1980 IPC V_Band
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('make', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trader_turrets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3991,282', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'282_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thomas_Feil', 'NN', '', 'O')
November 21 1980 IPC U.S. No._3991,282
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Feil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('V_Band', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unfair', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('competition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O')
IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('Various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('counterclaims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('apparently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'282_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
May of 1981 IPC the U.S. Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('cited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('M.E', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
IPC M.E
__NEW_SENT__
('Ozenberger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('W.H', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Ozenberger
__NEW_SENT__
('Keith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Telephone', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Bell Telephone Laboratories
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('refused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('completion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('rules', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_1,_1982', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'282_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
June_1,_1982 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Interconnect_Planning_Corp.', 'LS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Feil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('543_F.Supp._610', 'CD', '', 'O') ('614-19', 'CD', '', 'O') ('215_USPQ_734', 'CD', '', 'O') ('736-41', 'CD', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y.1982', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
736-41
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('resumed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('examination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_application', 'NN', '', 'O')
IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1135', 'LS', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('supplemental', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_application', 'NN', '', 'O')
IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'282_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surrendered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('RE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('31,144', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('IPC', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('restricted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ways', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O')
February 8 1983 31,144 IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('Defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('collateral', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'282_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('resisted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('memoranda', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affidavits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('depositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('documents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O')
IPC
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_20,_1984', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B')
1982 June_20,_1984
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('54', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('IPC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('attempt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal..', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('heard', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Jersey.1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
54 IPC appeal.. United_States_District_Court the District of New
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('day', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I')
this day
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('argument', 'VB', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infra', 'NN', '', 'O')
New_York
__NEW_SENT__
