('893_F.3d_1372', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('IMPAX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_AB', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_UK_Limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LANNETT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HOLDINGS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LANNETT HOLDINGS INC. Lannett Company Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2017-2020', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('June_28,_2018', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assignor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exclusive_licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nasal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('migraines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('challenged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('standing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('bring', 'VB', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (':14-cv-00984-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:14-cv-00999-RGA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Andrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2015_WL_7737309', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('246_F.Supp.3d_1024', 'CD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Nos._1 Richard G. Andrews J. 2015_WL_7737309
__NEW_SENT__
('Infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skilled_artisan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('looked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('triptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('looking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('develop', 'VB', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('take', 'VB', '', 'O') ('advantage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('pass', 'NN', '', 'O') ('metabolism', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('licensing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attributable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('mentioned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nasal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sprays', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Posture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1374', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (':14-cv-00984-RGA', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:14-cv-00999-RGA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Andrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Nos._1 Richard G. Andrews
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hurst', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
James F. Hurst Kirkland & Ellis Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marcus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sernel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Marcus Edward Sernel
__NEW_SENT__
('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Posillico', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fox', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rothschild', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Joseph F. Posillico Fox Rothschild LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carroll', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Glynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Frank T. Carroll Michael W. Glynn New York
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Taranto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Lourie Dyk
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lourie', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1375', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Lannett_Holdings_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('14', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6,750,237', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237_patent", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('6_and_14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-16', ':', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7,220,767', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('see', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Impax_Labs.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett_Holdings_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('246_F.Supp.3d_1024', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D._Del', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lannett_Holdings_Inc. Lannett Co. Inc. Lannett the District of Delaware 4 11 12 and 14 6,750,237 7,220,767 Lannett_Holdings_Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2017', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_AB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca_UK_Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Impax_Labs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett_Holdings_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-00984-RGA', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D._Del', 'NNP', '', 'O')
2017 Opinion Impax Laboratories Inc. AstraZeneca_AB AstraZeneca_UK_Limited AstraZeneca Lannett 35 271 4 Impax_Labs Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Apr._17,_2017', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ECF_No._1', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('74', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ECF_No._1 74
__NEW_SENT__
('1-4', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1-4
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('follow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Triptans', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('selective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('serotonin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('receptor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agonists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
the early 1980s
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('triptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('marketed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ImitrexTHE_R', 'IN', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
first ImitrexTHE_R first U.S. 1993
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('sumatriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oral_tablet_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intranasal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ImitrexTHE_R', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Nasal_Spray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NS', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1995 1997 ImitrexTHE_R Nasal_Spray NS
__NEW_SENT__
('Zolmitriptan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('triptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oral_tablet_form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1999', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ZomigTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Zolmitriptan first U.S. 1999
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('triptans', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive_licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s,1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intranasal_administration', 'NN', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('intranasal_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solutions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'237_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('5_l._4', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('-col.', 'SYM', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('6_l._22', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5_l._8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-col.', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('6_l._25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
5_l._4 -col. 6_l._22 6_l._25
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Claim 4 2 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237_patent", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('read', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 2 and 4 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intranasal_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4.BIG_TOKEN__5_to_5__BIG_TOKEN5', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 5
__NEW_SENT__
('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
4
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('buffered', 'VBN', '', 'O')
2
__NEW_SENT__
("'237_patent", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('5_ll._4', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-9', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12-13', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('6_and_15', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('read', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intranasal_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acceptable_carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3.BIG_TOKEN__5_to_5__BIG_TOKEN5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('buffered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('citric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disodium_phosphate', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
15
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
less than 6.0
__NEW_SENT__
("'767_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('5_ll._23', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-27', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('6_ll._21', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-22', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ranges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('buffering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('additional_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sterility', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1376', 'ADD', '', 'O') ("'237_patent", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('col.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('5_l._4', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('-col.', 'SYM', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('6_l._22', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5_l._8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-col.', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('6_l._25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
5_l._4 -col. 6_l._22 6_l._25
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('additional_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ZomigTHE_R', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Nasal_Spray', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('2.5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mg/spray', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg/spray', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('migraine', 'NN', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca the New Drug Application NDA ZomigTHE_R 5 the U.S. Food and Drug Administration FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('connection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ZomigTHE_R_Nasal_Spray', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Approved', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Therapeutic', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Equivalence', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Evaluations', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('commonly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'EVENT', 'B') ('``', '``', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Orange', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Book', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ("''", "''", 'EVENT', 'I')
ZomigTHE_R_Nasal_Spray FDA Approved Drug Products the `` Orange Book ''
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('supply', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ZomigTHE_R_products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
2012 AstraZeneca Impax
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ZomigTHE_R_products', 'NNS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('return', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('payment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'B') ('130', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('payments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('varying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('royalty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('40', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nasal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spray', 'NN', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca ZomigTHE_R_products $ 130 million 40 %
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('246', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.3d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1039', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
1039 J.A
__NEW_SENT__
('2204-05', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2014', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('notified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ZomigTHE_R_Nasal_Spray', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('IV', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'NNS', '', 'O')
June 2014 Lannett AstraZeneca ZomigTHE_R_Nasal_Spray 21 355 2 IV Paragraph IV
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2014', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
July 2014 Appellees Lannett the District of Delaware 35 2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 2015
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preamble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical_formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intranasal_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O')
Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('Impax_Labs', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Holdings', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('2015_WL_7737309', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*2-3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D._Del', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Impax_Labs Inc. Lannett Holdings Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2017', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Claim_Construction_Opinion', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Impax_Labs', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett_Holdings_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-00984-RGA', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D._Del', 'NNP', '', 'O')
2017 Impax_Labs Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Dec._8,_2017', 'UH', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ECF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._64', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Claim', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Construction', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('9-10', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('declining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('adopt', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ionic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('covalently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('bonded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preserve', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Appellees Lannett
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim_Construction_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2015_WL_7737309', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*3-4', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('word', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('buffer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('adopting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('functional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('definition', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*4-7', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lannett Lannett
__NEW_SENT__
('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('agreed-upon', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('disodium_phosphate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
9
__NEW_SENT__
('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
10
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2016', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four-day', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
September 2016 four-day
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('target', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pH', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Impax_Labs', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett_Holdings_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':14-cv-00984-RGA', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D._Del', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lannett 5 FDA Impax_Labs Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sept._29,_2016', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ECF_No._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('37', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
37
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2017', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
March 2017 Lannett
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('246', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.3d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1030', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1030
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('teachings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('NS', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('Publication', 'NNP', 'EVENT', 'I') ('No', 'NN', 'EVENT', 'I')
first NS International Publication No
__NEW_SENT__
('WO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('99/64044', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Marquess', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('6,326,401', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('counterpart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('French', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marquess 6,326,401
__NEW_SENT__
('FR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2773489', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('together', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Chauveau', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')2', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stewart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tepper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rapoport', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Triptans', 'NNPS', 'NORP', 'B') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Summary', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('CNS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drugs', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('*1377', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('403-417', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Nov.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1999', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'ORG', 'B') ('Tepper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rapoport', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2773489 Chauveau Stewart Tepper & Alan Triptans 5 CNS Drugs 403-417 Nov. 1999 `` Tepper & Rapoport ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1032-34', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1032-34
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'237_patent", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'767_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marquess', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Chauveau', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('neither', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Lannett 4 15 Marquess Chauveau
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1034-35', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lannett
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('1035-44', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Chauveau', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('formulating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intranasal_administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('potent_metabolite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('183C91', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrasted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('metabolite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skilled_artisan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expectation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nasal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zolmitriptan', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 Chauveau 183C91 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1036-39', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1032', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('n.3', 'NN', '', 'O')
1032
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('metabolite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('o', 'XX', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('nly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('triptans', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('eletriptan', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('almotriptan', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('metabolites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('metabolites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'do", 'VBP', '', 'O') ("n't", 'RB', '', 'O') ('really', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contribute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('efficacy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Zolmitriptan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('stands', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('alone', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('triptans', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('potent_metabolite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Zolmitriptan
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1033', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('quoting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rapoport', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1033 Appellees Alan Rapoport
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('objective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indicia', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1039-43', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('agreement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Impax', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inconclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O')
2012 Impax AstraZeneca
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('question', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('close', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('meet', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Lannett
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1043-44', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('1-4', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1-4
__NEW_SENT__
('Lannett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Lannett
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
