('703_F.3d_511', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United_States', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United_States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ROSUVASTATIN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CALCIUM', 'NN', '', 'O') ('PATENT', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LITIGATION', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('UK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('IPR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Shionogi_Seiyaku_Kabushiki_Kaisha', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Aurobindo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pharma', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca UK Limited IPR Pharmaceuticals Inc. Shionogi_Seiyaku_Kabushiki_Kaisha Plaintiffs-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Apotex_Corp.', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cobalt_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cobalt_Laboratories_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Cobalt_Laboratories_Inc. Defendants-Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc. Defendant-Appellant
__NEW_SENT__
('Par', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Par Pharmaceutical Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sandoz Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2010-1460', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2010-1461', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1462', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1463', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1464', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2010-1465', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1466', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1467', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1468', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1469', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2010-1470', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2010-1471', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2010-1472', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2010-1473', 'CD', '', 'O')
2010-1464 2010-1469 2010-1470 2010-1471
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Dec._14,_2012', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Holders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti-cholesterol', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_producers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('initiated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('accompanied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farnan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('719_F.Supp.2d_388', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Joseph J. Farnan Jr. J. 719_F.Supp.2d_388
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficiently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('warrant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('citation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('deceptive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('unintentional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Information', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Disclosure', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Statement', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('IDS', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('species', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('warrant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Information Disclosure Statement ( IDS
__NEW_SENT__
('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsidiary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('submitter', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plager', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Mayer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*514', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lipsey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Finnegan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Henderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farabow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Charles E. Lipsey Finnegan Henderson Farabow Garrett & Reston VA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frankel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('York', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Faulkner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Kenneth M. Frankel York M. Faulkner
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Farabow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Levine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ferguson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Cambridge', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Livingstone', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bourke', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Connolly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bove', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lodge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hutz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DE', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Henry', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Renk', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Stevens', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Judy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Yun', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Ford F. Farabow Jr. Howard W. Levine Washington Mary K. Ferguson Cambridge John D. Livingstone Atlanta Mary W. Bourke Connolly Wilmington DE Henry New York Thomas Stevens Judy Yun AstraZeneca Pharmaceuticals LP Wilmington DE
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Breisblatt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Katten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Muchin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rosenman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Robert B. Breisblatt Katten Muchin Rosenman LLP Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jeremy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Daniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Paradis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jeremy C. Daniel Charles B. Paradis
__NEW_SENT__
('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merchant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gould', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('WI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Jeffrey S. Ward P.C. Madison WI
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heneghan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas P. Heneghan Edward J
__NEW_SENT__
('Pardon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Shane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brunner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Pardon Shane A. Brunner
__NEW_SENT__
('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Maddox', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knobbe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martens', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Olson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bear', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Steven A. Maddox Knobbe Martens Olson & Bear LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Payson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lemeilleur', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jared', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Bunker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knobbe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martens', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Olson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bear', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Irvine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Payson Lemeilleur Jared Bunker Knobbe Martens Olson & Bear LLP Irvine CA
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN MAYER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('21', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('producers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('authorized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('status', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('federally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('registered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_producer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('counterpart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Hatch-Waxman Act 21 U.S.C.¡± 355
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('succeeds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eliminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('180-day', 'CD', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exclusivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('providers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iv', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 355 5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('statin', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('CrestorTHE_R', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('federally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cholesterol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('atherosclerosis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Reissue', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('No._37314', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*515', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5260,440', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬440_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Reissue Patent No._37314 No._5260,440
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Shionogi_Seiyaku_Kabushiki_Kaisha', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Shionogi', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('licensee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('AstraZeneca', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('UK', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('subsidiary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IPR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
AstraZeneca UK United_States IPR Pharmaceuticals Inc. Plaintiffs
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CrestorTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('calcium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whose', 'WP$', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rosuvastatin', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('cholesterol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inhibiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('HMG-CoA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reductase', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rosuvastatin one
__NEW_SENT__
('Scientists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('working', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shionogi', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('laboratory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conducting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('search', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reduced_side_effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Shionogi Japan
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('course', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('beneficial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1991
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('countries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Japan ¡¬314_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Federal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('12', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', 'DATE', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('decades', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 12 2003 over two decades
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('highly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('successful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('superior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('efficacy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lowering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('low-density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('LDL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cholesterol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('elevating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('high-density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('HDL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('cholesterol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('reduced_side_effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statins', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LDL HDL
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Peter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('et', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('al.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Comparison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ('Efficacy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Safety', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rosuvastatin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Versus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Atorvastatin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Simvastatin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pravastatin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Across', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Doses', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('STELLAR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('92', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Am', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Peter H. Jones Comparison of the Efficacy and Safety of Rosuvastatin Versus Atorvastatin Simvastatin Pravastatin Across Doses 92
__NEW_SENT__
('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Cardiology', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('152', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
J. Cardiology 2003
__NEW_SENT__
('Several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('generic_producers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('initiated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('accompanied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
¡¬314_patent 21 2 IV
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('permits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_producer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('federal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('registrant', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('constitutes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('shall', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('submit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('355', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('title', 'NN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (']..', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Act', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('veterinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('biological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('biological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
271 2 the Patent Act section 355 21 Act
__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 271 2
__NEW_SENT__
('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fails', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 271 4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('challengers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Aurobindo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pharma', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cobalt_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Cobalt_Laboratories_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Par', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Defendants are Cobalt_Laboratories_Inc. Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries Ltd. Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc. Par Pharmaceuticals Inc. Sandoz Inc
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('*516', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('314', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('improper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Defendants ¡¬ 314 the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬314_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed.1', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('admitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'CD', '', 'O') ('All', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬314_patent Defendants All of the Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('VALIDITY', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('challenge', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('Obviousness', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('basic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inquiries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Deere', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('383_U.S._1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('17-18', 'CD', '', 'O') ('86_S.Ct._684', 'CD', '', 'O') ('15_L.Ed.2d_545_(1966)', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('elaborated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('International', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teleflex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('550_U.S._398', 'CD', '', 'O') ('406-07', 'CD', '', 'O') ('127_S.Ct._1727', 'CD', '', 'O') ('167_L.Ed.2d_705_(2007)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('viz.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('content', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('level', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('differences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('objective_indicia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('long-felt', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O')
four Graham John Deere Co. 15_L.Ed.2d_545_(1966) KSR International Co. Teleflex Inc. 1 2 3 4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('identified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('European', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Publication', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._0_367_895', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Sandoz', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('May_16,_1990', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pyrimidine-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O')
Defendants European Patent Office Publication No._0_367_895 Sandoz Sandoz May_16,_1990
__NEW_SENT__
('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-CH3', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amino', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-CH3', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-SO2CH3', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O')
two one one
__NEW_SENT__
('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sandoz_European_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('especially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sandoz', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*9', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suggests', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('selection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('change', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('-CH3', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('-SO2CH3', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('hydrophilic', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*517', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('publications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liver-selective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fewer', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('undesirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrophilic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('liver-selective', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('persons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Sandoz_Compound', 'RB', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('hydrophilic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('C2_position', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('marked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supra', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('logical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('modify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('essential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substitutions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sulfonyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('spacer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('-SO2-at', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('C2_position', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('increase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('hydrophilicity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('predicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('change', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fewer', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rendering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('pointed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sandoz_Compound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toxicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('encouraging', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Plaintiffs
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sandoz_European_application', 'NN', 'EVENT', 'B') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('better', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vitro', 'FW', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plaintiffs Sandoz_European_application Compound 11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scientist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1b', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('hydrophilic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pointing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('publications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('lipophilic_substituents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('C2_position', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('converse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrophilic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('increase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('statin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plaintiffs 1991 Compound 1b
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suggestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('unexpectedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('superior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reasonable_expectation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pfizer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('480_F.3d_1348', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1361', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2007', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('T', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('falls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skilled_artisan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('teachings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('achieve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skilled_artisan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_expectation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O')
Pfizer Inc. Apotex Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('highlighted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unpredictability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyrrole-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspects', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyrimidine-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('displayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('toxic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('pointed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('abandoned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pyrimidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prevailing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('belief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pyrimidine-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('promising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('leads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Plaintiffs at least five
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('pointed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('suggested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unknown', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('advantageous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Plaintiffs
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('550', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('421', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('127_S.Ct._1727', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factfinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('aware..', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distortion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hindsight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bias', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cautious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reliant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ex', 'FW', '', 'O') ('post', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoning', 'NN', '', 'O')
U.S. 421 127_S.Ct._1727
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmacal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('231_F.3d_1339', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1345', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2000', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medicinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemist', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('expected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('desirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmacological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('quotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('omitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi Pharm Co. Danbury Pharmacal Inc. 1345
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('pointed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('objective_indicia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('long', 'RB', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unfilled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('need', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Graham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('383', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('17-18', 'CD', '', 'O') ('86_S.Ct._684', 'CD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O')
Plaintiffs Graham 383 U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('*518', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pfizer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('480', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('F.3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1359-60', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('presume', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('challenger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bears', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing_evidence', 'JJ', '', 'O')
480 1359-60
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('never', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shifts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('insertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sulfonyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('finite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('predicable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solutions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('KSR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('550', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('421', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('127_S.Ct._1727', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('test', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Defendants one U.S. 421 127_S.Ct._1727
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('situation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'RP', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'IN', '', 'O') ("O'Farrell", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('853_F.2d_894_(Fed.Cir.1988)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ("'obvious", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('try', 'VB', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('explore', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('approach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('seemed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('promising', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('field', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('gave', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('guidance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('achieve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('903', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
903
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('demonstrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('required', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Sandoz_Compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1b', 'CD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sulfonyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('change', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Compound', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('1b', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O')
Defendants Compound 1b
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Eli', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lilly', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Goldline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pharms.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('471_F.3d_1369', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1379', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2006', 'ADD', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('considering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('chosen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Eli Lilly & Co. Zenith Goldline Pharms. 471_F.3d_1369 1379 Fed.Cir.2006
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('try', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('negated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skepticism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pyrimidine-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('statins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('abandoned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hydrophilic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substituents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lipophilic_substituents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('C2_position', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chem', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Indus.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pty.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('492_F.3d_1350', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1357', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2007', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('n', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('remains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('identify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('modify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O')
Takeda Chem Indus. Ltd. Alphapharm Pty. 492_F.3d_1350 1357
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rosuvastatin', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
