('32_F.3d_1541', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
32_F.3d_1541
__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('KEARNS', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff/Cross-Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CHRYSLER', 'VB', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant/Appellant', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Robert W. KEARNS
__NEW_SENT__
('American', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motors', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
American Motors Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._93-1450', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('93-1470', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Aug._11,_1994', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Sept._28,_1994', 'NNP', '', 'O')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intermittent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('windshield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wipers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Cohn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross-appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Michigan Cohn J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bound', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('royalty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1542', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Robert_W._Kearns', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pro', 'FW', '', 'O') ('se', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taylor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pillsbury', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sutro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant/appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert P. Taylor Pillsbury Madison & Sutro Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scinto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Lawrence F. Scinto New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Deanne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Siemer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Deanne C. Siemer Michael A. Conley
__NEW_SENT__
('*1543', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Durkee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Durkee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Houston', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus_curiae', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Arnold', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('White', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Durkee', 'NNP', '', 'O')
William D. Durkee Arnold White & Durkee
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Allison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Munisteri', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sewell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Riggs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Houston', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O')
William B. Allison James G. Munisteri Sewell & Riggs
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aitken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aitken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aitken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McCann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus_curiae', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inventors', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ass', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'", "''", 'ORG', 'I') ('n', 'RB', '', 'O')
Richard L. Aitken Andrew C. Aitken Lane Aitken & McCann Washington DC Houston Inventors Ass '
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Robert_W._Kearns', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cross-appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('18,740,465.43', 'CD', '', 'O')
Chrysler Corporation Robert_W._Kearns United_States_District_Court Michigan Kearns
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
three Kearns Chrysler
__NEW_SENT__
('Kearns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civil_No._82-70748', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kearns Civil_No._82-70748
__NEW_SENT__
('Oct._30,_1992', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Chrysler
__NEW_SENT__
('Kearns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civil_No._82-70748', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kearns Civil_No._82-70748
__NEW_SENT__
('June_3,_1993', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respects', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Kearns', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
1982 Kearns Chrysler U.S
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3,351,836', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('3,564,374', 'CD', '', 'O') ('3,602,790', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3,581,178', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intermittent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('windshield', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wipers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IWWs', 'NNPS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automotive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vehicles', 'NNS', '', 'O')
3,351,836 3,581,178
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distributors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Civil_Action_No._78-70740', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kearns three Kearns Ford Motor Co.
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wood_Motors', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civil_Action_No._78-70642', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kearns
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('SWF-Spezialfabrik', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('fur', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Autozubehor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gustav', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rav', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('GmbH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Civil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Action', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._79-74451', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Autozubehor Gustav Rav Kearns Civil Action No._79-74451 (
__NEW_SENT__
(')1', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O')
October 22 1982 Chrysler
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('instituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bound', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._3351,836', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3,564,374', 'CD', '', 'O') ('3,581,178', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3,602,790', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Wood_Motors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SWF', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('whichever', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adjudicated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Chrysler U.S. 3,602,790 Ford SWF
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bound', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consent_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Chrysler
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1989', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Ford_case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('went', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('renewed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O')
1989 Chrysler
__NEW_SENT__
('Subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court-ordered', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('Chrysler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bound', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('excluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consent_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Kearns', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ford_case', 'CD', '', 'O') ('C.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Chrysler Kearns
__NEW_SENT__
('78-70740', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')
78-70740
__NEW_SENT__
('Those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nos._3351,836', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3,564,374', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('3,581,178', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3,602,790', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
United States Patent 3,564,374 3,581,178 3,602,790
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('15', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
February 15 1990
__NEW_SENT__
