('952_F.2d_1357', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('LAITRAM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC_Information_Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sears', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Roebuck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I')
NEC CORPORATION NEC_Information_Systems Inc. Sears Roebuck and Company Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._91-1108', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
No._91-1108
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Dec._31,_1991', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Suggestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jan._30,_1992', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Eastern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Louisiana', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('A.J', 'NNP', '', 'O')
the United States District Court the Eastern District Louisiana
__NEW_SENT__
('McNamara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('partial_summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('immediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
McNamara J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('patent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('se', 'FW', '', 'O') ('substantive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('premises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('patent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1358', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Held', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Timothy J. Malloy McAndrews Held & Malloy Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jarvis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vogler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Dudek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kuelper', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Lawrence M. Jarvis Gregory J. Vogler Jean Dudek Kuelper
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Phillip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wittmann', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Usdin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stone', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pigman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Walther', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wittmann', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hutchinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_Orleans', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('La.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Barry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LaCour', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Drapanas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Harahan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('La', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Phillip A. Wittmann Steven Usdin Stone Pigman Walther Wittmann & Hutchinson New_Orleans La. Barry L. LaCour Mark T. Drapanas Laitram Corp. Harahan La
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hopgood', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kalil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Blaustein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judlowe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John M. Calimafde Hopgood Calimafde Kalil Blaustein & Judlowe New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marvin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gordon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kagan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Marvin N. Gordon Charles Quinn David H. Kagan
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McMichael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Liskow', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lewis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_Orleans', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('La', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
James D. McMichael Liskow & Lewis New_Orleans La
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ARCHER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN ARCHER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laitram_Corporation', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('against', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC_Information_Systems', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sears', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Roebuck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('partial_summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('immediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal.1', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Laitram_Corporation against NEC Corporation NEC_Information_Systems Inc. Sears Roebuck and Company NEC NEC
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('patent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('substantive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('se', 'FW', '', 'O') ('rule', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('substantively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('changed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('partial_summary_judgment', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
partial_summary_judgment
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._3952,311', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'311_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Electro-Optical', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Printing', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('System', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lapeyre', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_20,_1976', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Laitram_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O')
United States Patent `` Electro-Optical Printing System '' James M. Lapeyre April_20,_1976
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('electro-optical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('printing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereby', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('printed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sheet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('radiation_sensitive_material', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('arrayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_sensitive_material', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('past', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitter_array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation_sensitive_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('moves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('past', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('activated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
third
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("'311_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ensuing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1_and_2 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Claim 2 35 one
__NEW_SENT__
('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3_through_27', 'CD', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Laitram 1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('follow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('*1359', 'FW', '', 'O') ('italicized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('deleted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brackets', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1_and_2 1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electro-optical_printing_apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('photosensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recording_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation_emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wavelengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('radiation_emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('activating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('activated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('recorded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alpha-numeric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('positioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('irradiate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_areas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('irradiated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('arranged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('overlapping', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('print', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electro-optically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('type_quality_alpha-numeric_characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('photosensitive_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('arranging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rapidly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reacting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation_emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wave-', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lengths', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('photosensitive_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sensitive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('energizing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('transmitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different_area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('relative_movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coordinate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('array', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('energized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relative_movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alpha-numeric_character_images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('recorded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('exposure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ares', 'NNS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('areas', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('recording', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radiation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('synchronously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('generating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('programs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('determines', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('duration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('employing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('signals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('effect', 'VB', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('record', 'VB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alpha-numeric_character_images', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('high_speed', 'NN', '', 'O')
first second first second
__NEW_SENT__
('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_through_27', 'CD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pointing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('teachings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('differed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'311", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Laitram
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Laitram', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('newly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Baylis', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitter_array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'311", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coordinate', 'NN', '', 'O')
Laitram Baylis more than one
__NEW_SENT__
('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('perceived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('deficiencies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Laitram
__NEW_SENT__
('*1360', 'VB', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3_through_27', 'CD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('giving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('fails', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('teach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electro-optical_printing_apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('printing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('straight_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recording', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('constant_speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('direction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('perpendicular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitter_array', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('coordinating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('activation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('emitters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('predetermined_periods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('elements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('Laitram', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('done', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('define', 'VB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('inherent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('details', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('change', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Laitram 1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('decide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('changes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('discuss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O')
1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substantive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
