('266_F.3d_1358', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('LORAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('FAIRCHILD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MATSUSHITA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ELECTRICAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INDUSTRIAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LTD.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Matsushita', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Canon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Canon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fairchild', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Semiconductor', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fuji', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Photo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Film', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fuji', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Photo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Film', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gold', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Star', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Electronic', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('International', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Goldstar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hitachi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Home', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronics', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('America', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hitachi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kokos', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Color', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mitsubishi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sales', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('National', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Semiconductor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nippon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electric', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Samsung', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Electronics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
LORAL FAIRCHILD CORPORATION Matsushita Electric Corporation of Canon Inc. Fuji Photo Film U.S.A. Inc. Hitachi Home Electronics Hitachi Ltd. Kokos Color TV Inc. Mitsubishi Electric Corp. Mitsubishi Electric Sales America Inc. National Semiconductor Corporation Nippon Electric Company Ltd. Samsung Electronics America Inc. Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('Toshiba_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Consumer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Components', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Information', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
Toshiba America Inc. Toshiba America Consumer Products Inc. Toshiba America Electronic Components Inc. Toshiba America Information Systems Inc. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Technologies', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
NEC Corporation NEC America Inc. NEC Technologies Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._00-1487', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sept._21,_2001', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B')
Sept._21,_2001
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Oct._17,_2001', "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Eastern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Randall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('sitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('designation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Eastern District Randall R. Rader J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Michel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('precluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('corroborating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('efforts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Michel Circuit_Judge 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pauline', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
Pauline Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1360', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wallace', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Fielding', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
James H. Wallace Jr. Wiley Rein & Fielding Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wyss', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lyons', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John B. Wyss Gregory R. Lyons
__NEW_SENT__
('Arthur', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Oblon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Spivak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McClelland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Maier', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Toshiba_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Arthur I. Neustadt Oblon Maier & Neustadt P.C. Arlington VA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kelly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Carl', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schlier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard D. Kelly Carl E. Schlier
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hopgood', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judlowe', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mondolino', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
John M. Calimafde Hopgood New_York NY NEC Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MAYER NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MICHEL', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('preclude', 'VB', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July_12,_2001', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine_issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('preceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Japanese', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('electronics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('distributors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._3931,674', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬674_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('charge-coupled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CCD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1991 Loral Japanese U.S. 1 United States Patent No._3931,674 CCD
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CCD', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('component', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cameras', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('produces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('representing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('image', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('focused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O')
CCD
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('signal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('processed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('displayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('video', 'NN', '', 'O') ('monitor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('severed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-manufacturing_defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('manufacturing_defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sanyo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hitachi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('OKI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
August 1995 Loral six Sony Sanyo Toshiba Hitachi NEC OKI
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('go', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sony first
__NEW_SENT__
('Over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('course', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('weeks', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('tried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')
five weeks 1996 Loral and Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
February 14 1996 Sony Loral
__NEW_SENT__
('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alternatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Sony JMOL Sony
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Loral_Fairchild_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Victor_Co.', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('931_F.Supp._1014_(E.D.N.Y.1996)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Loral_II', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Victor_Co. Japan Loral_II
__NEW_SENT__
('One', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('journal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('authored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Darrel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Erb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Erb_reference', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1973', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1974', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('filing_date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1361', 'NN', '', 'O') ('¡¬674_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
One Sony Darrel Erb December 3 1973 February 8 1974
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1030', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sporting', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Goods', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Geoffrey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Assoc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('904_F.2d_677', 'CD', '', 'O') ('683-85', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('14_USPQ2d_1942', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1948-49', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1990', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assert', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1030 Wilson Sporting Goods Co. David Geoffrey & 683-85 1948-49
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Erb_reference', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('qualify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬674_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable_jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('done', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Loral_II', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('931', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('F.Supp.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1031', 'CD', '', 'O')
931
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('solely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('address', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Erb_reference', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬674_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
JMOL Loral
__NEW_SENT__
('Loral_Fairchild_Corp.', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('181_F.3d_1313', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1316_n._3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('50_USPQ2d_1865', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1876_n._3_(Fed.Cir.1999)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Loral_III', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Sony Corp. 1876_n._3_(Fed.Cir.1999)
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('manufacturing_defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('believed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬674_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-Toshiba', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Loral NEC
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_10,_2000', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Erb_reference', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
April_10,_2000 Toshiba NEC 1 102
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-day', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unpublished', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine_issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('status', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Erb_reference', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Loral_Fairchild_Corp.', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Victor_Co.', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Japan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Nos._92-0128', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('91-5056', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.N.Y', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Victor_Co. Japan Nos._92-0128 & 91-5056
__NEW_SENT__
('June_21,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Toshiba', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Toshiba
__NEW_SENT__
('Loral', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('timely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Loral 28 1
__NEW_SENT__
