('449_F.3d_1209', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('LIQUID', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DYNAMICS', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VAUGHAN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._05-1105', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('05-1325', 'CD', '', 'O') ('05-1366', 'CD', '', 'O') ('05-1399', 'CD', '', 'O')
Nos._05-1105
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_1,_2006', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
June_1,_2006
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_11,_2006', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('handling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('waste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('slurries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('storage_tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Northern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('2002_WL_1769979', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Suzanne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conlon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Northern District Illinois Suzanne B. Conlon J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('355_F.3d_1361', 'CD', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('2005_WL_711993', 'CD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
District Court
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gajarsa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Gajarsa Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('47', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('storage_tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')
47
__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('helical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('storage_tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('foreign', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('purchasers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('best', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('mode', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('practicing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('storage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('installations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1212', 'LS', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schroer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Tabin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Flannery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argue', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Steven C. Schroer Fitch Tabin & Flannery Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hetzler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Birmingham', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark W. Hetzler Jon A. Birmingham
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carlson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Christensen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Connor", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kindness', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Seattle', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Robert J. Carlson Christensen O'Connor Johnson Kindness Seattle Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Walters', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark P. Walters
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Ward Brown
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
GAJARSA DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('GAJARSA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('previous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Liquid', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Dynamics', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('contested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O')
Liquid Dynamics LD
__NEW_SENT__
('Liquid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dynamics', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('355_F.3d_1361', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2004', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Liquid Dynamics Corp. Vaughan Co. LD
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('revised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim_construction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six-day', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._5458,414', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'414_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'414_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Vaughan Company Inc. Vaughan 1_and_8 U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('*1213', 'NFP', 'DATE', 'I') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'414_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'414_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
October 25 *1213 2004 Vaughan Vaughan
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('1,183,722', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B')
LD 1,183,722
__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('LD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('close', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O')
Vaughan LD
__NEW_SENT__
('Final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('15', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment-as-a-matter-of-law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('new-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willfulness', 'NN', '', 'O')
November 15 2004 Vaughan JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LD
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trebled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('damage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('willfulness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('behavior', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Vaughan
__NEW_SENT__
('Separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('amounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('1,501,239', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B')
1,501,239
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
February 25 2005
__NEW_SENT__
('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('willful_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
Vaughan JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('Further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Vaughan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('orders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Vaughan
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'414_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pumps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('stir', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('mixtures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('liquids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1,000,000-gallon', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1,000,000-gallon
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('wastewater', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manure', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('already', 'RB', '', 'O') ('detailed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('background', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LD', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reproduce', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('slurry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LD
__NEW_SENT__
('Slurry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('store', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chemicals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('organic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('waste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manure', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('retain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fertilizer', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('storage_tanks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('house', 'NN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('waste_compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('semisolid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('waste_compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('tend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('separate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crust', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('falling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Productive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('remixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('suspend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heavy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('particles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liquid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('ensure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('suspension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('uniform', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('One', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('standard', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('approach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stir', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mix', 'NN', '', 'O') ('continuously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('settling', 'VBG', '', 'O')
One
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('expensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ways', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('store', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixtures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('allow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('settling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('remix', 'VB', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'414_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('addressed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concerns', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LD', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1363', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1363
__NEW_SENT__
