('848_F.3d_1358', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('METALCRAFT', 'VB', '', 'O') ('OF', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYVILLE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('dba', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Scag_Power_Equipment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B')
MAYVILLE INC. Plaintiff-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('THE', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('TORO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Exmark_Manufacturing_Co.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
THE TORO COMPANY Exmark_Manufacturing_Co. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2016-2433', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'RB', '', 'O') ('2016-2514', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2017', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
February 16 2017
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ride-on', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lawnmower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('riding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('light_utility_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement_action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lawnmower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rudolph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('T.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Randa', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2016_WL_4076894', 'CD', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Adelman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2016_WL_4402021', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Lynn Adelman J. 2016_WL_4402021
__NEW_SENT__
('Manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Moore Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('phrase', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supports..', 'XX', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire_body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('steering_controls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('suffer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('irreparable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('harm', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('outweighed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('overly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1362', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('No._2', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (':16-cv-00544-WED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rudolph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Randa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Adelman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court No._2 Rudolph T. Randa Lynn Adelman
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Griggs', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Boyle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fredrickson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Milwaukee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('WI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Michael T. Griggs S.C. Milwaukee WI
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Brookman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sarah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wong', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Adam Brookman Sarah M. Wong
__NEW_SENT__
('Rachel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hughey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merchant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gould', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Rachel C. Hughey P.C. Minneapolis MN
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Anthony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zeuli', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Anthony Richard Zeuli
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hughes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stoll', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Moore Hughes Stoll
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Moore', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Metalcraft', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mayville', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precluding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Toro_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Exmark_Manufacturing_Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('offering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('equipped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('platform_suspension_systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._8186,475', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'475_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Wisconsin Mayville Inc. 's Exmark_Manufacturing_Co. Inc. U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Metalcraft', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mayville', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('d/b/a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Scag_Power_Equipment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Scag', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('manufactures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('riding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mayville Inc. Scag
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('improve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('mowers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Scag', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'475_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Scag
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'475_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ride-on', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lawnmower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('riding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('light_utility_vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigid_chassis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suspension_system', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("'475_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abstract', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2:33-34', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire_body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2:51-52', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suspension_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suspends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chassis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1363', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('isolates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vibrations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('shock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mower', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('driven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('uneven', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('terrain', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4:1-6', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('suspend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('isolate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('controls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rigid_chassis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2:37-39', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_controls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('platform', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('2:39-41', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('Scag', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('commercialized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'475_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Cheetah_line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Toro_Company', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('wholly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('subsidiary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Exmark_Manufacturing_Co.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('riding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suspended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('operator_platforms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compete', 'VB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Scag', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Cheetah_line', 'NN', '', 'O')
2015 Exmark_Manufacturing_Co. Inc. Toro
__NEW_SENT__
('Toro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('MyRIDE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('tm', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('suspension_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Exmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('platform', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upgrade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Lazer', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('Z', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('Series', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
MyRIDE Exmark Lazer Z Series
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_controls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Exmark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('riding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chassis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('operator_platform', 'NN', '', 'O')
Toro Exmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Br', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('24', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Br', 'NN', '', 'O')
24 Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
13
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_5,_2016', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Scag', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement_action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('simultaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enjoin', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('offering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('lawnmowers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('platform_suspension_systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ("'475_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
May_5,_2016 Scag Toro Wisconsin Toro
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Scag', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 1 Scag
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 4 Toro
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Toro', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Scag', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('set', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bond', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O')
Toro Scag
__NEW_SENT__
('Toro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1292 1 1
__NEW_SENT__
