('837_F.3d_1299', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MCRO', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('DBA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Planet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Blue', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
MCRO
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BANDAI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NAMCO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('GAMES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('AMERICA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Naughty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Konami', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Digital', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Entertainment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sega', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Arts', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Obsidian', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Entertainment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Disney_Interactive_Studios', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Square_Enix', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Neversoft_Entertainment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Treyarch_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Capcom_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sony_Computer_Entertainment_America_LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Atlus_U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sucker_Punch_Productions', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Infinity_Ward', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lucasarts', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I') ('A', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Division', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('LucasFilm_Entertainment_Company_Ltd._LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Warner_Bros._Interactive_Entertainment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('A', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Division', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Warner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bros.', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Home', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Entertainment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Activision_Publishing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Blizzard_Entertainment', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Valve', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Codemasters_USA_Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Codemasters_Software_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Codemasters', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Codemasters_Software_Company_Limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
BANDAI NAMCO GAMES AMERICA Naughty Dog Inc. Digital Entertainment Inc. America Inc. Electronic Arts Inc. Obsidian Entertainment Inc. Disney_Interactive_Studios Inc. Square_Enix Capcom_USA Inc. Sony_Computer_Entertainment_America_LLC Atlus_U.S.A. Inc. LLC Infinity_Ward Inc. Lucasarts A Division of Warner Bros. Home Entertainment Inc. Activision_Publishing Inc. Blizzard_Entertainment Inc. Valve Corporation Codemasters_USA_Group Inc. Codemasters Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('2015-1080', 'LS', '', 'O') ('-1081', ':', '', 'O') ('-1082', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('-1083', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-1084', '.', '', 'O') ('-1085', ',', '', 'O') ('-1086', 'DT', '', 'O') ('-1087', ':', '', 'O') ('-1088', ':', '', 'O') ('-1089', 'LS', '', 'O') ('-1090', '.', '', 'O') ('-1092', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('-1093', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('-1094', ':', '', 'O') ('-1095', ':', '', 'O') ('-1096', 'LS', '', 'O') ('-1097', ':', '', 'O') ('-1098', 'FW', '', 'O') ('-1099', ':', '', 'O') ('-1100', '.', '', 'O') ('-1101', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('13', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2016', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
September 13 2016
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('animating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lip', 'NN', '', 'O') ('synchronization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('facial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('expressions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three-dimensional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('animated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('characters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('55_F.Supp.3d_1214', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pleadings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unpatentability', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California George H. Wu J. 55_F.Supp.3d_1214
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Reyna Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('evaluating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sub-sequences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('multiple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sequential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('phonemes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rules', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('merely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invoke', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('machinery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('favoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1302', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nos._2', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (':12-cv-10322-GW-FFM', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:12-cv-10323-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2:12-cv-10327-GW-FFM', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:12-cv-10329-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2:12-cv-10331-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:12-cv-10333-GW-FFM', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:12-cv-10335-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2:12-cv-10337-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:12-cv-10338-GW-FFM', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:12-cv-10341-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2:12-cv-10342-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('8:13-cv-01870-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:14-cv-00332-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:14-cv-00336-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:14-cv-00358-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2:14-cv-00383-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:14-cv-00352-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2:14-cv-00417-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('8:13-cv-01874-GW-FFM', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('2:14-cv-00389-GW-FFM', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2:14-cv-00439-GW-FFM', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court California Nos._2 2:12-cv-10323-GW-FFM 2:12-cv-10329-GW-FFM 2:12-cv-10331-GW-FFM 2:12-cv-10335-GW-FFM 2:12-cv-10337-GW-FFM 2:12-cv-10341-GW-FFM 2:12-cv-10342-GW-FFM 8:13-cv-01870-GW-FFM 2:14-cv-00332-GW-FFM 2:14-cv-00336-GW-FFM 2:14-cv-00358-GW-FFM 2:14-cv-00383-GW-FFM 2:14-cv-00352-GW-FFM 2:14-cv-00417-GW-FFM 8:13-cv-01874-GW-FFM George H. Wu
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lamken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('MoloLamken', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jeffrey A. Lamken MoloLamken LLP Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pattillo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Francis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Petrsoric', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Stewart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Raskin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whitman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mishcon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('de', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Reya', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Whealan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chevy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chase', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MD', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Michael Gregory Pattillo Jr. John Francis Mark Stewart Robert Alan New York LLP New York NY John M. Whealan Chevy
__NEW_SENT__
('Sonal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Naresh', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mehta', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Durie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Tangri', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('representing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Electronic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Arts', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Capcom_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Activision_Publishing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Blizzard_Entertainment', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Durie Tangri LLP San_Francisco Electronic Arts Inc. Capcom_USA Inc. Activision_Publishing Inc. Blizzard_Entertainment Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reines', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gotshal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Manges', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Redwood', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Shores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Bandai', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Namco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Games', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sega', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Disney_Interactive_Studios', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Neversoft_Entertainment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Treyarch_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Atlus_U.S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Infinity_Ward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LucasArts', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Division', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LucasFilm_Entertainment_Company_Ltd._LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Warner_Bros._Interactive_Entertainment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Division', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Warner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bros.', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Home', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Entertainment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Edward R. Reines Bandai Namco Games America Inc. Sega of Division of Warner Bros. Home Entertainment Inc
__NEW_SENT__
('Basil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Trent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Webb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shook', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hardy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bacon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kansas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('MO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Naughty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dog', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sony_Computer_Entertainment_America_LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Sucker_Punch_Productions', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Basil Trent Webb Kansas City Naughty Dog Inc. Sony_Computer_Entertainment_America_LLC Sucker_Punch_Productions
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Garretson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Beth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Larigan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
John D. Garretson Beth A. Larigan
__NEW_SENT__
('Wendy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morrison', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Foerster', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Konami', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Digital', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Entertainment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Square_Enix', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Benjamin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Wendy J. Ray Morrison & Foerster LLP Los Angeles Konami Digital Entertainment Inc. Square_Enix Inc. Benjamin J
__NEW_SENT__
('Fox', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Fox
__NEW_SENT__
('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Tsu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Spach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Capaldi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Waggaman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newport', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Beach', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Obsidian', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Entertainment', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Walling', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Andrew David Tsu Spach Capaldi & Waggaman Obsidian Entertainment Inc. Thomas Walling
__NEW_SENT__
('Jan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Patrick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weir', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michelman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robinson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Irvine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Valve', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Jan Patrick Weir Michelman & Robinson LLP Irvine Valve Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mellema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Theodore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Angelis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McDonald', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('K', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('L', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gates', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Seattle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Joseph James Mellema Theodore J. Angelis David T. McDonald K & L Gates
__NEW_SENT__
('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirsch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hostetler', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cincinnati', 'NNS', 'GPE', 'B') ('OH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Codemasters', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Codemasters_USA_Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Codemasters_Software_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Codemasters_Software_Company_Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kevin W. Kirsch Baker Cincinnati Codemasters Inc. Codemasters_USA_Group Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Jared', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brandyberry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Barry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Eastburn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bretschneider', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Jared A. Brandyberry Barry Eastburn Bretschneider Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Duan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Public_Knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amici', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Public_Knowledge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Electronic_Frontier_Foundation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Charles Duan
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Vera', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ranieri', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Electronic_Frontier_Foundation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Vera Ranieri
__NEW_SENT__
('Andrew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pincus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brown', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('BSA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('I', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Software', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Alliance', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Andrew John Pincus Mayer Brown BSA
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Whitfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hughes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Paul Whitfield Hughes
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Taranto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stoll', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Reyna Taranto
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reyna', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pleadings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Fed
__NEW_SENT__
('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Civ', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
R. Civ
__NEW_SENT__
('P.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos._6307,576', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'576_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('6,611,278', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'278_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
U.S. 6,611,278
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent-ineligible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California 35
__NEW_SENT__
('McRO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sony', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Computer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("Entm't", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Am.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('55_F.Supp.3d_1214', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C.D', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
McRO Inc. Sony Computer C.D
__NEW_SENT__
('Cal', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2014', 'LS', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Patentability', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Op', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2014 Patentability Op
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1303', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('unconventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('sub-sequences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('phonemes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('timings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('morph', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abstract_idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('patent-eligible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
101
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Background', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'576_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'278_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Maury', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rosenfeld', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('titled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Method', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Automatically', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Animating', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lip', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Synchronization', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Facial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Expression', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Animated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Characters', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Maury Rosenfeld
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'278_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'576_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('shares', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
