('672_F.3d_1350', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('MARINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('POLYMER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TECHNOLOGIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HEMCON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
MARINE POLYMER TECHNOLOGIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2010-1548', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('March_15,_2012', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('promoted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('hemostasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stopping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bleeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hemorrhage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Hampshire', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DiClerico', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2008_WL_1995454', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patentee_summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jury_verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('2010_WL_3070197', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('patentee_summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('29,410,246', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('royalties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('past', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('permanently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('future', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2010_WL_3120051', 'CD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Hampshire Joseph A. DiClerico Jr. J. 2008_WL_1995454 29,410,246
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('659_F.3d_1084', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('damages_award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('acquired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('parallel_reexamination_proceeding', 'VBG', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('2012_WL_255331', 'CD', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appellate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('divided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('divided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substantial_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('damages_award', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acquire', 'VB', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whom', 'WP', '', 'O') ('Gajarsa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Reyna', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wallach', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('joined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('joined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dyk Circuit_Judge Gajarsa Reyna Wallach Circuit_Judges Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1353', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Poissant', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jones', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Day', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Brian M. Poissant Jones Day New York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Julie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lynda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Q.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nguyen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ognian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shentov', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Julie M. Baher Lynda Q. Nguyen Ognian V. Shentov
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Castanias', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Gregory A. Castanias Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Raymond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kurz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hogan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Lovells', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Raymond A. Kurz Hogan U.S. Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Celine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jimenez', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crowson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Keith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Doherty", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Celine Jimenez Crowson Keith B. O'Doherty
__NEW_SENT__
('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gollin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Venable', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Biotechnology', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Industry', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Organization', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Michael A. Gollin Venable LLP Washington DC Biotechnology Industry Organization
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Coston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Saad', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Meaghan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fabian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Koenigbauer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
William D. Coston Martin L. Saad Meaghan H. Kent Fabian M. Koenigbauer
__NEW_SENT__
('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reines', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gotshal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Manges', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Redwood', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Shores', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amici', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('HewlettPackard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Edward R. Reines Redwood Shores HewlettPackard Company
__NEW_SENT__
('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nathan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Greenblatt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Nathan Greenblatt
__NEW_SENT__
('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Phillips', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stoel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rives', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Portland', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('OR', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Intellectual', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ventures', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Management', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Matthew C. Phillips Portland Intellectual Ventures Management
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nathan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Brunette', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rainey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Intellectual', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ventures', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Management', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bellevue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Nathan C. Brunette Matthew C. Rainey Bellevue Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Mitchell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stockwell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kilpatrick', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Townsend', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Stockton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Atlanta', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('GA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Jan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Voda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mitchell G. Stockwell Kilpatrick Townsend & Stockton LLP Atlanta Jan K. Voda M.D.
__NEW_SENT__
('*1354', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sterne', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sterne', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kessler', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Goldstein', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Fox', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('P.L.L.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amici', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Soverain', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('Software', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('et_al.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O')
Robert G. Sterne Washington Soverain Software
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wright', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Jon E. Wright
__NEW_SENT__
('Matthew', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Latham', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Watkins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amici', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Geico', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Matthew J. Moore Latham & Watkins Washington DC Geico Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Julie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Holloway', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Greenfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Julie M. Holloway Adam M. Greenfield
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA,1LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('REYNA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges.2', 'ADD', '', 'O')
NEWMAN LOURIE DYK PROST REYNA
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('LOURIE', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('join', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge_LINN', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('joins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge LOURIE NEWMAN BRYSON PROST Circuit_Judge_LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('REYNA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('join', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge_LINN', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('joins', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('parts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('I-II', 'ADD', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge DYK Circuit_Judge_LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Defendant-Appellant', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Hampshire', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6,864,245', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Technologies', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Defendant-Appellant HemCon Inc. HemCon the District of New_Hampshire HemCon U.S. 6,864,245 Marine_Polymer
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('acquired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parallel_reexamination_proceeding', 'NN', '', 'O')
September 26 2011 HemCon ¡¬245_patent Marine_Polymer
__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer_Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('659_F.3d_1084', 'IN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2011', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Panel_Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('475_Fed.Appx._315', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2012_WL_255331', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir', 'RB', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer_Techs. Inc. HemCon Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Jan.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jan. 20 2012
__NEW_SENT__
('Upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('equally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('divided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('decide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('consider', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('majority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concludes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('affirmance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O')
HemCon
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('preparations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('poly-£]-1¡÷4-N-acetylglucosamine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'UH', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('naturally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('occurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('polysaccharide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('polymer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('organisms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arthropods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('fungi', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('microalgae', 'JJ', '', 'O')
¡¬245_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Purified', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('utility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('industrial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bio-medical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('promotes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hemostasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('stoppage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bleeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hemorrhage', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trauma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('serious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('wounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('context', 'NN', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('biological_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tendency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('elicit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('deleterious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reactions-e.g.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('necrosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erythema', 'NN', '', 'O') ('edema', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cellular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('degeneration-upon', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('exposure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('living', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tissues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('E.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.42', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ll.36-38', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.44', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ll.15-16', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('tests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('assess', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substance', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implantation_test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intracutaneous_injection_test', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('systemic_injection_test', 'NN', '', 'O')
four
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.42', 'LS', '', 'O') ('ll.1-3', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1355', 'UH', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('exposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cultured', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('observing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('signs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cytotoxicity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.42', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('ll.6-62', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implantation_test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('implanting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sample', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('animal', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('muscle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('scoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('severity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('local', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reactions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.42', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('l.64-col.43', 'NN', '', 'O') ('l.64', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intracutaneous_injection_test', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('calls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('injecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('volumes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extract', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('animal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('monitoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.43', 'CD', '', 'O') ('l.65-col.44', 'RB', '', 'O') ('l.56', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('systemic_injection_test', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('animals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('monitored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('changes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('overt', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('signs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('toxicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('intravenous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('intraperitoneal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extract', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.44', 'CD', '', 'O') ('l.57-col.45', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('l.42', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('describing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility_tests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('test_substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mild', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('slight_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('scores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('zero', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('scale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('biological_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('zero', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('slight_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('represents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('mild_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('represent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moderate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('severe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('satisfy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cultures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('show', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mild_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
zero to four zero one two three or four
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.42', 'LS', '', 'O') ('ll.41-62', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('But', 'CC', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('states', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detectable_biological_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('elution_tests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('intramuscular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('implantation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rabbits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('intracutaneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rabbits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('systemic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mice', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.41', 'CD', '', 'O') ('l.66-col.42', 'NN', '', 'O') ('l.3', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('col.45', 'CD', '', 'O') ('l.44-col.49', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('l.66', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('reporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'RB', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('zero', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
zero
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('22', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'NN', '', 'O')
22
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('majority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generically', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biocompatible_poly-£]-1¡÷4-N-acetylglucosamine', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('150,000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('N-acetylglucosamine', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('monosaccharides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covalently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('£]-1¡÷4', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conformation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('weight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('up', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('30', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('daltons', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('N-acetylglucosamine', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('monosaccharide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('deacetylated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
6 about 150,000 about 30 million daltons at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.72', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ll.5-10', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬245_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('biocompatible_poly-£]-1¡÷4-N-acetylglucosamine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6-11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('score', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
12 one 6-11 0
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.72', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ll.33-35', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('3_and_20', 'CD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('specify', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('zero', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('scores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('elution_test', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('analogous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('22', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('elution_test_scores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
zero 4 5 13 22 one two
__NEW_SENT__
('E.g.', 'RB', '', 'O') ('id', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.72', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('ll.33-41', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('245', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer HemCon March 2006 HemCon
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biomedically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'UH', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reproducibly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('acceptably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('levels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bioreactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility_tests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Markman Marine_Polymer
__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer_Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._06-', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CV-100', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2008_WL_1995454', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.N.H', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer_Techs. Inc. HemCon Inc. 2008_WL_1995454
__NEW_SENT__
('May_6,_2008', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('HemCon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('countered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('harvested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('microalgae', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('interpreted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('broadly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('suited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('biomedical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('applications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('*1-2', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1356', 'UH', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('constructions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reviewing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('language', 'NN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬245_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('means', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('p-GlcNAc', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('low_variability', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('high_purity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detectable_biological_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility_tests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
¡¬245_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*10', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('10-12', 'CD', '', 'O') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
HemCon 6 17 and 20
__NEW_SENT__
('Applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer HemCon seven
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('factual_findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬245_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('royalty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('29,410,246', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B')
Marine_Polymer 29,410,246
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_verdict', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('factual_findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('challenging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damages_award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantial_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O')
HemCon JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('16', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('barring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
September 16 2010 HemCon September 22 2010
__NEW_SENT__
('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')
HemCon
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ex', 'FW', '', 'O') ('parte', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('245', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
August 2009 HemCon ¡¬ the United States Patent Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reexamination_request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior_art_references-all', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('raised', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')
HemCon ten HemCon ¡¬245_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('40740-41', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('reexamination_request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initiated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('office', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_1,_20103', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('office', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('broadest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('low_variability', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('high_purity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('little', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
HemCon April_1,_20103 first
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('39503', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('emphasis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
39503
__NEW_SENT__
('Noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('22', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('elution_test_scores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('slight', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('mild_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('detectable_biological_reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('conflicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('avoided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inconsistency', 'NN', '', 'O')
4 5 22 ¡¬245_patent one two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('22', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('broader', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
22
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior_art_references-a', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('scientific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('article', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Sandford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Peniston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Malette', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-finding', ':', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explicitly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('every', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Sandford two Peniston Malette
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('difference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('biocompatibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sandford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Peniston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Malette', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('minor', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1357', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Sandford Peniston Malette
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('39507', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('39517', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('39522', 'CD', '', 'O')
39507 39517
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('addressed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dependency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Examiner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cancelling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('six', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('elution_test_scores', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('expressly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reactivity', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6-12', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('15-20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('unaltered', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer Examiner six one two 1-3 6-12 15-20
__NEW_SENT__
('Having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('deleted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inconsistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'biocompatible", 'JJ', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('adopted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('teachings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('37688-90', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conflicting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cancelled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('agree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('d', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('biocompatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('39481', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
39481
__NEW_SENT__
('Furthermore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('withdrew', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rejections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('narrower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('confirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentable', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certificate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('until', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')
November 3 2010 Marine_Polymer
__NEW_SENT__
('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('18', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damages_award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('permanent_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
HemCon November 18 2010
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_29,_2011', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certificate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_Reexam', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cert', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('cancelled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dependent_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('13', 'CD', '', 'O') ('14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('22', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('confirmed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('6-12', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('15-20', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O')
4 22 1-3 6-12 15-20
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬245_Reexam', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Cert', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.2', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ll.1-6', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('heard', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_7,_2011', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('majority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damages_award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('acquired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('intervening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('rights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬245_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
HemCon June_7,_2011 September 26 2011 HemCon
__NEW_SENT__
('Panel_Opinion', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('659', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('F.3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1090-95', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Panel_Opinion 659 1090-95
__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('petitioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Marine_Polymer', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('panel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer January 20 2012 Marine_Polymer
__NEW_SENT__
('Marine_Polymer_Techs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HemCon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No.2010-1548', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-Fed.Appx', '.', '', 'O')
Marine_Polymer_Techs. Inc. HemCon Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('2012_WL_255331', 'LS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Jan.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('20', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2012', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jan. 20 2012
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
