('558_F.3d_1352', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('NARTRON', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('SCHUKRA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INCORPORATED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Borg_Indak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1363', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('March_5,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('En', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Banc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') ('April_10,_2009', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
| Rehearing En Banc Denied April_10,_2009
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('automobile_seats', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('massage_functionality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zatkoff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2008_WL_896060', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Michigan Lawrence P. Zatkoff
__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('suggesting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1353', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Angileri', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brooks', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kushman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Southfield', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Frank A. Angileri Brooks Kushman P.C. Michigan
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert C.J
__NEW_SENT__
('Tuttle', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lewry', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lorelli', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas A. Lewry Marc Lorelli
__NEW_SENT__
('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sadowski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Howard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Attorneys', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bloomfield', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Hills', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Jeffrey A. Sadowski Howard & Howard Attorneys Bloomfield Hills Michigan
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Melanie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frazier', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Melanie T. Frazier
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sheehan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Michael J. Sheehan
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nartron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Michigan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('join', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6,049,748', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nartron Corporation Nartron United_States_District_Court Michigan Nartron U.S. 6,049,748
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._06-10683', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('2008_WL_896060', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Mich', 'NNP', '', 'O')
No._06-10683
__NEW_SENT__
('Mar', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('31', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('2008', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
31 2008
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('insignificant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contributing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Incorporated', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consistent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Joseph Benson 11
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Schukra', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Incorporated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Schukra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('supplies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1354', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('systems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automobile_seats', 'NN', '', 'O')
Schukra U.S.A. Incorporated Schukra
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Schukra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('contracted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('design', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('automobile_seats', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('massage_functionality', 'NN', '', 'O')
1996 Schukra Nartron for Nartron
__NEW_SENT__
('Nartron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seat_control_system', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('massage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capability', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('matured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Borg_Indak', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('supplies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('electronic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Schukra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Schukra
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
2006 Nartron
__NEW_SENT__
('Borg_Indak', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Schukra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('employee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Benson Schukra 11
__NEW_SENT__
('Neither', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Schukra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Schukra Benson
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'VB', 'PERSON', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 11 Benson
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6 5 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('read', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 5 6 and 11 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seat_control_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('introducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('massage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seat_control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adjustable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('control_actuators', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('modular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in-line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connectors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('coupling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seat_control', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('harness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('connector', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intercept', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('interface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inputs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('control_actuators', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('driver', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('repeatedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adjusting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('range', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('control_actuators', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transparency_simulator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('maintaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('full', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('seat_control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('indications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('repeatedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('adjusting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_position', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('...', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
5
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('transparency_simulator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('time-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('control_actuators', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('transparency_simulator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('control_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('predetermined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('generating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('control_actuator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('predetermined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O')
5 first first second first
__NEW_SENT__
('...', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('6', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O')
6
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬748_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('19', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('l.13-col.20', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('l.31', 'NNS', '', 'O')
19
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('contributed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O')
11 Benson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('motor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('controls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('governs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('degree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('outwardly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('spinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('curvature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('occupant', 'NN', '', 'O')
second 28 30
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanisms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('26_and_30', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('affect', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('32', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
26_and_30 32 16
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.4', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.28-33', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represent', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('box', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('diagram', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_system', 'NN', '', 'O')
30
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Figs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('numeral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1 30
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('employees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('presumptively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1355', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_system', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nartron
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('admit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inventive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consisted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('operated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('existing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('automobile_seats', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('already', 'RB', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('extenders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
11 Nartron
__NEW_SENT__
('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('admits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('idea', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Benson Nartron
__NEW_SENT__
('Oral', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Argument', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('11:38-12:30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('http', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('//oral', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('arguments.cafc.uscourts.gov/mp3/2008-1363.mp3', 'XX', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('If', 'IN', '', 'O') ('you', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('isolate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('extends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lumbar_supports', 'NNS', '', 'O')
11:38-12:30
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2008', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O')
March 2008
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('748', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conceived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('element', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('co-inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('joined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Benson ¡¬ 748 11
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contrary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬748_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('exclusively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('control_module', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('software', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('insignificant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conceived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('massager', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prototype', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nartron ¡¬748_patent Benson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conceded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('working', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frame', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('basket', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('operated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('massage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O')
Benson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('contradict', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('conceived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('practice', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extender', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lumbar_support_adjustor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nartron Benson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('join', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('necessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lawsuit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Benson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('employer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Schukra', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contractual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Benson Schukra
__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('effectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prevented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nartron', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enjoining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obtaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Borg_Indak', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Nartron
__NEW_SENT__
('Nartron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
