('701_F.3d_698', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('OSRAM_SYLVANIA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AMERICAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INDUCTION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TECHNOLOGIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Cross', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Appellant', 'NNP', '', 'O')
AMERICAN INDUCTION TECHNOLOGIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2012-1091', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2012-1135', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Dec._13,_2012', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Assignee', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('toward', 'IN', '', 'O') ('low_pressure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intensity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O')
Assignee
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Central', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Manuel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Real', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the Central District California Manuel L. Real J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("O'Malley", 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals O'Malley Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('factual_issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('face', 'VB', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('establishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('factual_issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('existed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('consider', 'VB', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('irrelevant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*700', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Gregg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Locascio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kirkland', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ellis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gregg F. Locascio Kirkland & Ellis LLP Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Nathan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mammen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Leslie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schmidt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Nathan S. Mammen Leslie M. Schmidt
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Coyle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cantor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Colburn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hartford', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('CT.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Glenn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Trost', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Connolly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bove', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lodge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hutz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-cross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Steven M. Coyle Cantor Colburn LLP Hartford Glenn W. Trost Connolly Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ("O'MALLEY", 'NN', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('REYNA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("O'MALLEY", 'LS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('OSRAM_SYLVANIA', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('OSRAM', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('25', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('27', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('32', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5834,905', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valery', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Godyak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('et', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('al.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('OSRAM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
OSRAM_SYLVANIA Inc. OSRAM 1 17 25 27 32 U.S. ¡¬905_patent Valery A. Godyak OSRAM
__NEW_SENT__
('*701', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('preclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('consider', 'VB', '', 'O') ('objective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indicia', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Technology', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Issue', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('OSRAM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed-loop', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tubular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('electrodeless', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('parameters', 'NNS', '', 'O')
OSRAM ¡¬905_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assembly', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrodeless', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed-loop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tubular_lamp_envelope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mercury_vapor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('torr', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transformer_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('surround', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('closed-loop', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('envelope', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('input_winding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('transformer_core', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
less than 0.5
__NEW_SENT__
('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radio_frequency_power_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('input_winding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supplying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mercury_vapor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('envelope', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('amperes', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬905_patent_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('8_ll._7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-19', 'NFP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('low_pressure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intensity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('light', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('considerably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('per', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('electroded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Electrodeless', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('articles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('authored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('G.E', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
first John Anderson G.E
__NEW_SENT__
('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1960s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'DATE', 'I') ('1970s', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the 1960s and
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Background', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Invention', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._3987,334', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Anderson_¡¬334_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('torodial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('forms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('closed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('path', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('passes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('torodial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ferrite_core', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬905_patent `` Background of the Invention '' Anderson U.S. No._3987,334
__NEW_SENT__
('Applying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wrapped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ferrite_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('creates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('magnetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('flux', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('induces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('voltage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wire', 'NN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ferrite_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transformer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transformer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('inner', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('coated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phosphor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('emits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('visible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('irradiated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('photons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('emitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('excited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mercury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬905_patent_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2_ll._14', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-16', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Anderson_¡¬334_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('operated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas_pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('torr', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('905', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inefficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('impractical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O')
¡¬ 905 Anderson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed-loop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tubular_lamp_envelope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mercury_vapor..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transformer_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('envelope', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('input_winding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transformer_core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radio_frequency_power_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('coupled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('input_winding', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('specifies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas_pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('0.5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('torr', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬905_patent_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2_ll._31', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('-37', 'NFP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('radio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supplies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('radio', 'NN', '', 'O') ('frequency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mercury_vapor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('envelope', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('amperes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('2_ll._36', 'NN', '', 'O') ('-41', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parameters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('-namely', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas_pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('torr', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('amperes-allegedly', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('output', 'NN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('efficiency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('operating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('life', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('conventional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*702', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('electroded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('fluorescent_lamps', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬905_patent less than 0.5 greater than 2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('operates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas_pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('torr', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('current', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('greater', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', '', 'O') ('5.0', 'CD', '', 'O') ('amperes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬905_patent less than about 0.2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬905_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('makes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('relationship-high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discharge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('current', 'NN', '', 'O') ('combined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('buffer_gas_pressure-that', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increased', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('efficiency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ferrite_core', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬905_patent
__NEW_SENT__
