('566_F.3d_989', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('PROCTER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('GAMBLE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('TEVA', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'I') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
The PROCTER & GAMBLE COMPANY Plaintiff-Appellee v. TEVA PHARMACEUTICALS USA INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2008-1404', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2008-1405', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2008-1406', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('May_13,_2009', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('compound_risedronate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Farnan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('536_F.Supp.2d_476', 'CD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Joseph J. Farnan Jr.
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Huff', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('District_Judge', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('sitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('designation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Huff District_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('commit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('secondary_considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intermittent_dosing_method', 'XX', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('qualified', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'VBG', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cutler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pickering', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hale', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dorr', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
William F. Lee Wilmer Cutler Boston MA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Vinita', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ferrera', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Allen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nunnally', 'RB', 'PERSON', 'I')
Vinita Ferrera Allen C. Nunnally
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bassett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Meade', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'DT', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
David B. Bassett Christopher J. Meade
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Galbraith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
James Galbraith Kenyon & Kenyon LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Maria', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Luisa', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palmese', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Antony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pfeffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Maria Luisa Palmese A. Antony Pfeffer
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HUFF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('District_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
MAYER DYK Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('HUFF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('District_Judge', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Procter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gamble', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('P', 'NN', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('G', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('upholding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('P', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('5,583,122', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('``', '``', 'PRODUCT', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc. United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware The Procter & Gamble Company three P & G 's 5,583,122 ÁÂ122_patent ``
__NEW_SENT__
('Procter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gamble', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('536_F.Supp.2d_476', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Del.2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Procter & Gamble Co. Teva_Pharmaceuticals_USA Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('cases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defenses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Teva
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound_risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('P', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('osteoporosis', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ActonelTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ122_patent P & G 's
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2004', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('notified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('P', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('G', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('planned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('equivalent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ActonelTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 2004 P & G Teva ÁÂ122_patent Teva
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('P', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('G', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound_risedronate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('16', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('diseases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva 4 16 23
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('*993', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('122', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('P', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('expired', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4,761,406', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ406_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_6,_1985', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Teva ÁÂ 122 P & G 's U.S._Patent 4,761,406 June_6,_1985 August 2 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('Alternately', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Teva', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'NN', '', 'O')
Teva ÁÂ122_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Risedronate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('member', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inhibiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resorption', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('promising', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('studied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metabolic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('diseases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('etidronate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('EHDP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('clodronate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('clinical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('prevented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('commercialization', 'NN', '', 'O')
first two EHDP
__NEW_SENT__
('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('conducted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('significant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('experimentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('hundreds', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('predict', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('efficacy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('toxicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
P & G hundreds
__NEW_SENT__
('Eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('researchers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('promising', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('candidate', 'NN', '', 'O')
P & G
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inventors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 6 1985
__NEW_SENT__
('P', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('G', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Compositions', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Containing', 'VBG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Geminal', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Diphosphonates', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
P & G ÁÂ122_patent `` Pharmaceutical Compositions Containing Geminal Diphosphonates '' December 10 1996
__NEW_SENT__
('Risedronate', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('neither', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ406_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Risedronate
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ406_patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Regimen', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Treating', 'VBG', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Osteoporosis', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intermittent_dosing_method', 'XX', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('osteoporosis', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ406_patent `` Regimen for Treating Osteoporosis ''
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ406_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('addresses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('central', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('problem', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seen', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('inhibited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mineralization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('teaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cyclic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administrative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('regimen', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('achieve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('benign', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti-resorption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unwanted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti-mineralization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gamble', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('536', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('492', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Procter & Gamble 536 F.Supp.2d 492
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('406', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thirty-six', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('polyphosphonate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('molecules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('candidates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('intermittent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('2-pyr', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('EHDP', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ÁÂ 406 eight 2-pyr
__NEW_SENT__
('Teva', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('contends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('similarities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('2-pyr', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('EHDP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('render', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
2-pyr EHDP ÁÂ122_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('From', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('406', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('identify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('2-pyr', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('EHDP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lead', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ 406 2-pyr EHDP
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extremely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unpredictable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bisphosphonates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('molecular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('modifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('risedronate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('toxicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rebut', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('secondary_considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Similarly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ122_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ122_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
