('789_F.2d_1556', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('POLAROID', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('EASTMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('KODAK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
POLAROID EASTMAN KODAK COMPANY
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._86-604', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B')
No._86-604
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('April_25,_1986', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
April_25,_1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('photographic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Rya', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Zobel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Massachusetts W. Zobel J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Markey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cameras', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O') ('units', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('photographic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('processes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Markey Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1556', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Francis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Francis T. Carr Kenyon & Kenyon
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Madsen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Galbraith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Walter', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hanley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schwartz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fish', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neave', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Kenneth E. Madsen James Galbraith Walter E. Hanley Jr. Herbert F. Schwartz Fish & Neave
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Herman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mullowney', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patricia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martone', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barnes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Goldman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Culligan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Kenneth B. Herman Edward F. Mullowney Patricia A. Martone Richard M. Barnes Robert J. Goldman Kevin J. Culligan
__NEW_SENT__
('*1557', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MARKEY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SMITH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I')
NEWMAN Circuit Judges
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MARKEY', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Eastman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kodak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Kodak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Massachusetts', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zobel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Eastman Kodak Company Kodak United_States_District_Court the District of Massachusetts
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Polaroid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Polaroid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
seven Polaroid Corporation Polaroid
__NEW_SENT__
('228_USPQ_305', 'CD', '', 'O') ('344', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.Mass.1985', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
344
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('respects', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Polaroid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kodak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_26,_1976', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('actively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Polaroid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Polaroid Kodak April_26,_1976 35 35 ten Polaroid
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issuance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('temporary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunctions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('treble', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('next', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('five', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('participated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pretrial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conferences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('numerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('thousand', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('entries', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('docket.1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Between', 'IN', 'DATE', 'B') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('5', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('26', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1982', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conducted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('seventy-five', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
the next five years more than one thousand Between October 5 1981 February 26 1982 seventy-five days
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kodak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('carry', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('certain_claims', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('become', 'VB', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('9', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986.3', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1985', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Kodak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.App.P', 'NNP', '', 'O')
October 11 1985 1 Kodak seven 2 2 3 five 4 January 9 1986.3 November 4 Kodak
__NEW_SENT__
('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('stay', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('completion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
8
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('briefing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1986', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 6 1986
__NEW_SENT__
('Kodak', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('carry', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seven', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('certain_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3753,392', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Kodak seven 4 5
__NEW_SENT__
('Polaroid', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('cross-appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('five', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Polaroid five
__NEW_SENT__
