('696_F.3d_1151', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('POZEN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PAR', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICAL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
POZEN PAR
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm_Pty_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Nos._2011-1584', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2011-1585', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2011-1586', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Sept._28,_2012', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Sept._28,_2012
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_19,_2013', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('migraines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_tablet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('offering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('importing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('accused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('719_F.Supp.2d_718', 'CD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Davis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('800_F.Supp.2d_789', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas Leonard Davis J. 800_F.Supp.2d_789
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wallach', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Wallach Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('render', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('satisfied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Clevenger', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O')
Clevenger Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1156', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hash', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vinson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Elkins', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Austin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Stephen M. Hash Vinson & Elkins LLP Austin
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Tracey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Davies', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Willem', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Schuurman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jennifer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Librach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephanie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lollo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Donahue', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rebecca', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cantor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Tracey B. Davies G. Schuurman Jennifer Librach Nall Stephanie Lollo Donahue Rebecca J. Cantor
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Berman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fox', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Par_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pty.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Parker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bird', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Richard J. Berman Arent Fox LLP Washington Par_Pharmaceutical Inc. Alphapharm Pty. Ltd. Thomas J. Parker Alston & Bird LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Par_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Taniel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ermano', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bucknell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aziz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Burgy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Janine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carlan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Joshua', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Morris', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ligler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schoenhard', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Par_Pharmaceutical Inc. Taniel Ermano Anderson Timothy Bucknell Aziz Burgy Janine A. Carlan Joshua T. Morris Amy E. Ligler Schoenhard
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pty.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Natalie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bird', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Alphapharm Pty. Ltd. Natalie C. Clayton Alston & Bird LLP
__NEW_SENT__
('Paul', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kochanski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lerner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Littenberg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Krumholz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mentlik', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Westfield', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NJ', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Teschner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Roy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wepner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Paul H. Kochanski David Littenberg Krumholz & Mentlik LLP Westfield NJ Dr._Reddy 's Michael H. Teschner Roy H. Wepner
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting-in-part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('INTRODUCTION', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Par_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Par', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm_Pty_Ltd.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dr._Reddy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('DRL', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Par_Pharmaceutical Inc. Par Alphapharm_Pty_Ltd. Alphapharm DRL Appellants United_States_District_Court Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6060,499', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Sept._11,_1998', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬499_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._6586,458', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Apr._27,_2000', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬458_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._7332,183', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Dec._22,_2003', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬183_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
U.S._Patent_No._6060,499 Sept._11,_1998 ¡¬499_patent Apr._27,_2000 U.S. No._7332,183 Dec._22,_2003 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Par', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DRL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filings', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Par DRL
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Par', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DRL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enjoined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('importing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('selling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('offering', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('generic_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States.1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Par DRL the United patents-in-suit
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('migraines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('naproxen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_tablet', 'NN', '', 'O')
Pozen two
__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Par', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharm.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('800_F.Supp.2d_789', 'CD', '', 'O') ('796', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.Tex.2011', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Pozen Inc. Par Pharm. Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Sumatriptan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('5-HT', 'CD', '', 'O') ('receptor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('agonist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'I') ('1980s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('widely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accepted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('medicine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('migraines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reoccurrence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('migraine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('symptoms', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the late 1980s
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('797', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
797
__NEW_SENT__
('Naproxen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('nonsteroidal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1157', 'FW', '', 'O') ('anti-inflammatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NSAID', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
NSAID
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('798', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('partnership', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GlaxoSmithKline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('GSK', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('markets', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('naproxen', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('TreximetTHE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
TreximetTHE_R three
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬499_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('migraines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('co-timely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('administration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('5-HT', 'CD', '', 'O') ('agonists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('long-acting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('NSAIDs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬499_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬499_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.13-17', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬499_patent', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('combining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('5-HT', 'CD', '', 'O') ('agonists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('long-acting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('NSAIDs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
¡¬499_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬458_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.18-20', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬183_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('multilayer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tablet', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('triptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sumatriptan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('NSAID', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('layers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('dissolve', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O')
NSAID
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('183', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.54-57', '.', '', 'O')
183
__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('TreximetTHE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_15,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')
New Drug Application NDA TreximetTHE_R the United States Food and Drug Administration FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('800', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('798', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
798
__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents-in-suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('TreximetTHE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
NDA TreximetTHE_R
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Approved', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('with', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Therapeutic', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Equivalence', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Evaluations', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Orange_Book', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('see', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('indicating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unlicensed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TreximetTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
FDA Approved Drug Products with 21 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Pozen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('800', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('798', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
798
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('forms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TreximetTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Pozen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
FDA Pozen
__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
(';', ':', '', 'O') ('see', 'VB', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 2 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Orange_Book', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Appellants Orange_Book
__NEW_SENT__
('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Pozen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('800', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('798-99', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('constitutes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('artificial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
21 355 2 IV Pozen 800 F.Supp.2d
__NEW_SENT__
('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Warner-Lambert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('316_F.3d_1348', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1365', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2003', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 271 2 Warner-Lambert Co. Apotex Corp. 1365
__NEW_SENT__
('Thereafter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pozen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('complaints', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬499_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('12', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('24', 'CD', '', 'O') ('26', 'CD', '', 'O') ('27', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('29', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬183_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Act.2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Pozen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('800', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('799', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Pozen Appellants 15 11 12 27 29 and 30 2 35 2 Pozen 800 F.Supp.2d 799
__NEW_SENT__
