('946_F.2d_870', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('QUAD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ENVIRONMENTAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('TECHNOLOGIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('UNION', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SANITARY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DISTRICT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('A.P.T.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('d/b/a', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Calvert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Environmental', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
QUAD ENVIRONMENTAL TECHNOLOGIES CORPORATION UNION SANITARY DISTRICT A.P.T. Inc. California Corp. Calvert Environmental Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._91-1027', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B')
No._91-1027
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Oct._8,_1991', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Suggestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Dec._13,_1991', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contributory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reexamined', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('describing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('removing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('odors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dry', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('waste', 'NN', '', 'O') ('gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('streams', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fern', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('M.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Smith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court
__NEW_SENT__
('Inventor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Inventor
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pauline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Newman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('terminal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disclaimer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obviate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('double', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('admission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('subsequent_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('previous_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('subsequent_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unobvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('embodied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('previous_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('reexamination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('admission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*871', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Alan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.J', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Alan E.J
__NEW_SENT__
('Branigan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Griffin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Branigan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Butler', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Arlington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Branigan Griffin Branigan & Butler Arlington Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kurtossy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arlington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Va.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Neil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Smith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Medlen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Limbach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Limbach', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sutton', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cal.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
George C. Kurtossy Va. Neil A. Smith Virginia S. Medlen Limbach Limbach &
__NEW_SENT__
('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laff', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laff', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Whitesel', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Conte', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Saret', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Charles A. Laff Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.I', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert F.I
__NEW_SENT__
('Conte', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Waters', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Judith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grubner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gabrielides', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('O.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Doyle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Flehr', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hohbach', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Test', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Albritton', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Herbert', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('San_Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cal.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Conte William P. Waters Judith L. Grubner John T. Gabrielides Chicago Ill. Thomas O. Herbert Richard P. Doyle Albritton & Herbert San_Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MILLER', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Senior', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
NEWMAN PLAGER Circuit_Judges MILLER Senior Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PAULINE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
PAULINE NEWMAN Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Quad', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Environmental', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technologies', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*872', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness.1', 'WP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('deeming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('mooted', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Quad Environmental Technologies Corporation United_States_District_Court Northern_District California
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improvidently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('errors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('require', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Summary', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('salutary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('avoiding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unnecessary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('56', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Liberty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lobby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('477_U.S._242', 'CD', '', 'O') ('247', 'CD', '', 'O') ('106_S.Ct._2505', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2509-10', 'CD', '', 'O') ('91_L.Ed.2d_202_(1986)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Celotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Catrett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('477_U.S._317', 'CD', '', 'O') ('322-23', 'CD', '', 'O') ('106_S.Ct._2548', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2552', 'CD', '', 'O') ('91_L.Ed.2d_265_(1986)', 'CD', '', 'O')
56 Anderson Liberty Lobby Inc. 91_L.Ed.2d_202_(1986) Celotex Corp. Catrett
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('burden', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('establishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('entitlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presumptions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('burdens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('characterize', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Anderson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('477', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('254', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('106', 'CD', '', 'O') ('S.Ct.at', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2513', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('H.H', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
U.S. 254 2513 H.H
__NEW_SENT__
('Robertson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Steel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Deck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('820_F.2d_384', 'CD', '', 'O') ('388', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2_USPQ2d_1926', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1928', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1987', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Robertson Co. United Steel Deck Inc. 388 1928
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reviewing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('met', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('When', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('movant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('presumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('282', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
35 103 35 282
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inferences', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('drawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opponent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Anderson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('477', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('255', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('106', 'CD', '', 'O') ('S.Ct.at', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2513', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Cooper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ford', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Motor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('748_F.2d_677', 'CD', '', 'O') ('679', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('223_USPQ_1286', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1288', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1984', 'ADD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Anderson 477 U.S. 255 2513 Cooper Ford Motor Co. 679 1288
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('amenable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('disputed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('testimonial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('documentary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('expert', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('resolution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('summary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjudication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('indicated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
