('531_F.3d_1372', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ROCHE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PALO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ALTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('formerly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Syntex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Allergan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('APOTEX', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'WRB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LLC Syntex ( U.S.A. LLC Allergan Inc. APOTEX INC. Apotex_Corp.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2008-1021', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('July_9,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Sept._5,_2008', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti-inflammatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('eye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drops', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jenkins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('526_F.Supp.2d_985', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District California Martin J. Jenkins J. 526_F.Supp.2d_985
__NEW_SENT__
('Proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Prost', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Prost Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('prima-facie', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reverse_doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('barred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1374', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Alexander', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brainerd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ehrman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Alexander L. Brainerd Heller Ehrman LLP San Francisco California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Saunders', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haskett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Samuel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ernst', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Nathan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shafroth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Christine Saunders Haskett Samuel F. Ernst Nathan E. Shafroth
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Keith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Keith R. Weed
__NEW_SENT__
('Manny', 'JJ', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Poktilow', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Caesar', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rivise', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bernstein', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cohen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pokotilow', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LTD.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Philadelphia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pennsylvania', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Manny D. Poktilow Philadelphia Pennsylvania
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Silver', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mona', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gupta', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Castillo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert S. Silver Mona Gupta William J. Castillo
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Shashank', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Upadhye', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Toronto', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ontario', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Canada', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Shashank S. Upadhye Apotex Inc. Toronto Ontario Canada
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chief', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PROST', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HOCHBERG', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
MICHEL PROST Circuit_Judge HOCHBERG District
__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PROST', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'PRP$', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Allergan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
the Hatch-Waxman Act Apotex Inc. Apotex_Corp. Apotex United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of California Roche Palo Alto LLC Allergan Inc. Roche Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('Roche', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('526_F.Supp.2d_985', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Cal.2007', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Roche Palo Alto LLC Apotex Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reverse_doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inapplicable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('preclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prohibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('raising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')
Apotex
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5110,493', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬493_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('eye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inflammation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('glaucoma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conjunctivitis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('eye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surgery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('eye', 'NN', '', 'O') ('injury', 'NN', '', 'O')
A. Roche U.S. No._5110,493
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('493', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col._1,_ll._14-28', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬ 493
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('non-steroidal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anti-inflammatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NSAID', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ketorolac', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tromethamine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('KT', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('quaternary_ammonium_preservative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('benzalkonium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('BAC', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonionic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfactant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('octoxynol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('O40', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
NSAID BAC 40 O40
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('col._3,_ll._13-19', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('col._4,_ll._20-41', '.', '', 'O')
Id.
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('*1375', 'UH', '', 'O') ('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opthalmologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-steroidal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anti-inflammatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opthamologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('non-steroidal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anti-inflammatory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carboxyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group-containing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective_amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ophthalmic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('0.001', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('10.00', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_wt/vol', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('a', 'LS', '', 'O') ('quaternary_ammonium_preservative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antimicrobially', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effective_amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('0.001', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('1.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_wt/vol', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ethoxylated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('phenol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('conforms', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('C8', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('H17C6H4', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('OCH2-CH2', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('n', 'CC', '', 'O') ('OH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('n', 'RB', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('average', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('value', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('O40', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stabilizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('0.001', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('1.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_wt/vol', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aqueous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('vehicle', 'NN', '', 'O') ('q.s', 'ADD', '', 'O')
Claim 1 between 0.001 % 10.00 between 0.001 % 1.0 40 O40 between 0.001 % 1.0
__NEW_SENT__
('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('100', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
100 %
__NEW_SENT__
('Dependent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('sodium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NaCl', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('concentration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('0.79', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('%_wt/vol', 'NN', '', 'O')
7 0.79
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('requiring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('O40', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejection', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1 O40
__NEW_SENT__
('Accompanying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Lidgate', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Declaration', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('O40', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('produced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unexpected_results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nonionic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfactants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('O3', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('O5', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Lidgate Declaration O40 O3
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('O40', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('produced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('others', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O')
O40
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unexpected_results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('O40', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B')
O40
__NEW_SENT__
('Over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬493_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')
the years Apotex two two IV
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA-1', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ACULARTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
2001 Apotex first ANDA-1 Roche
__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2005', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Apotex', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA-2', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Roche', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ACULARTHE_RLS', 'NN', '', 'O')
2005 Apotex second ANDA-2 Roche
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('differ', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('ANDA-1', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ANDA-2', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ACULARTHE_R', 'IN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ACULARTHE_RLS', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('KT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
KT
__NEW_SENT__
('0.5', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.5 %
__NEW_SENT__
('0.4', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.4 %
__NEW_SENT__
('BAC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
BAC
__NEW_SENT__
('0.01', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.01 %
__NEW_SENT__
('0.0063', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.0063 %
__NEW_SENT__
('O40', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('0.01', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.01 %
__NEW_SENT__
('0.004', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.004 %
__NEW_SENT__
('NaCl', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('0.8', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.8 %
__NEW_SENT__
('0.8', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I')
0.8 %
__NEW_SENT__
