('183_F.3d_1342', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('RHINE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('CASIO', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INCORPORATED', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Casio_Computer_Co.', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
Gary E. RHINE CASIO INCORPORATED Casio_Computer_Co. Ltd. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1432', 'JJ', 'GPE', 'B')
No._98-1432
__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('July_6,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('wrist_watch', 'VB', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time_delay_circuit', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Ohio James G. Carr J.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('illuminated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Mayer Chief_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1343', 'FW', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schaffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Emch', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Schaffer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Schaub', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Porcello', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('L.P.A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Toledo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Mark C. Schaffer Schaub & L.P.A. Toledo Ohio
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Porcello', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr..', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Barry', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rein', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pennie', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
James F. Porcello LLP New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Kenneth L. Stein
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MAYER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('SKELTON', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O')
CLEVENGER Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MAYER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rhine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ohio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Case', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._96', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CV7524', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Casio_Computer_Co.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gary E. Rhine United_States_District_Court Northern_District Ohio Case No._96 CV7524 Casio Inc. Casio_Computer_Co. Ltd. Casio
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1344', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rhine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4910,652', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wrist_watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time_delay_circuit', '.', '', 'O')
U.S. Patent No._4910,652
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time_delay_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('turns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('keeping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('displaying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('wrist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mountable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('power_supply', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('supplying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('power', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('power_supply', 'NN', '', 'O') ('electrically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('time_delay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extinguishing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time_delay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('energization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('deenergization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1 at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufactures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wrist_watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whose', 'WP$', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('illuminates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('brightness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('light', 'VB', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beyond', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('Rhine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Casio Rhine 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('settlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Rhine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('file', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('construe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('purporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('follow', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('procedure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suggested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Markman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Westview', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Instruments', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('517_U.S._370', 'CD', '', 'O') ('116_S.Ct._1384', 'CD', '', 'O') ('134_L.Ed.2d_577_(1996)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Rhine Markman Westview Instruments Inc. 134_L.Ed.2d_577_(1996)
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interpretation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Rhine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wrist_watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('illuminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time-delayed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('extinguishment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rhine 1 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Rhine', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Casio
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wrist_watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('light_sources-one', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('illuminates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('one', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('illuminates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beyond', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O')
Casio two
__NEW_SENT__
('Casio', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single_light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whose', 'WP$', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('illuminator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('bright', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enough', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('illuminate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time_delay_circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('illuminators', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Casio 1 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('th', 'XX', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('illuminates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time_delay', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('extinguishes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Japanese_reference', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wristwatch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('illumination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lamp', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lighting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('display', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('illumination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('casing', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Japanese_reference
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('noted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mounting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('search', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('flashlights', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('wrist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enabling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('users', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('check', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('watch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('illumination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
the Patent and Trademark Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Japanese_reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('illumination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('capable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('illuminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('flashlight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('limitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('single_light_source', 'ADD', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
Casio
__NEW_SENT__
('Casio', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('light_source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('illuminating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('watch_face', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('about', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Casio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Casio
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
