('11_F.3d_1036', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
11_F.3d_1036
__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('RAWLPLUG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ILLINOIS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TOOL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('WORKS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
The RAWLPLUG COMPANY INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._92-1356', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Nov._23,_1993', 'ADD', 'PRODUCT', 'B')
Nov._23,_1993
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('anchor', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fixtures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('fastened', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('masonry', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Metzner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringer', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Charles M. Metzner J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plunkett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('District_Judge', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I') ('sitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('designation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reversible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('comparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('installation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('installation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('restrictions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonabrading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Plunkett District_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1037', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Dennis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mondolino', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hopgood', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Calimafde', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Kalil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Blaustein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judlowe', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dennis J. Mondolino Hopgood Calimafde Kalil Blaustein & Judlowe New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Goldberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Lee A. Goldberg
__NEW_SENT__
('Granger', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cook', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Egan', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McFarron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Manzo', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Granger Cook Jr. Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Heller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ted', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ringsred', 'VBN', 'PERSON', 'I')
Stephen B. Heller Ted K. Ringsred
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Buckman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Neal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Illinois_Tool_Works', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenview', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Thomas W. Buckman Neal C. Johnson Illinois_Tool_Works Inc. Glenview IL
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judges', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('PLUNKETT', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('District_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
NEWMAN SCHALL Circuit Judges PLUNKETT District_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('*', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PLUNKETT', 'NN', '', 'O') ('District_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois_Tool_Works', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ITW', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('masonry_anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sold', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('names', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_Striker', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hammer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Loc', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
The Rawlplug Company Rawlplug two Illinois_Tool_Works ITW New_Striker Hammer Loc
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('piece', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pre-shaped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('anchoring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('masonry', 'NN', '', 'O')
ITW
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Defendant', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Complaint', 'NNP', '', 'O')
the Defendant ITW
__NEW_SENT__
('Rawlplug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interpreting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('follow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('secure', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fixtures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('roofing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('masonry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('manufactures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fasteners', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('masonry_anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rawlplug
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('1980', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Vice-President', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Manufacturing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Engineering', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Louis', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Giannuzzi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('conceived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('simple', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('yet', 'CC', '', 'O') ('efficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('masonry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anchor', 'NN', '', 'O')
1980 Rawlplug Louis Giannuzzi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anchor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consisting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('resilient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tempered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('steel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('shaped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('bend', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('longitudinal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('axis', 'NN', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('memory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('forcibly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('deformed-e.g.', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pounded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hole-it', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('recover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('returns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anchor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exerts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('outward', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pressure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('walls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1038', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('driven', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('detail', 'NN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rawlplug
__NEW_SENT__
('Through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Buildex', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ramset/Redhead', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Divisions', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('masonry_anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Buildex ITW
__NEW_SENT__
('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('manufactures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('masonry_anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tradenames', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('New_Striker', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Hammer-Loc', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
ITW two New_Striker Hammer-Loc
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('stipulated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('anchors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('Hence', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('title', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('New_Striker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Rawlplug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('York1', 'UH', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('New_Striker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('anchor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._4828,445', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'445_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,963,062', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'062_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')2', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court ITW ITW two Rawlplug U.S. 4,963,062 Rawlplug
__NEW_SENT__
('ITW', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
ITW
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four-day', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('bench', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('New_Striker', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
four-day Rawlplug
__NEW_SENT__
('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Illinois_Tool_Works', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('23_USPQ2d_1054', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1992_WL_91703_(S.D.N.Y.1992)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Rawlplug Co. Illinois_Tool_Works
__NEW_SENT__
('Rawlplug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
Rawlplug
__NEW_SENT__
