('183_F.3d_1347', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SMITHS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INDUSTRIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MEDICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('SYSTEMS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('successor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Intertech', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Resources', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VITAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('SIGNS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
SMITHS INDUSTRIES MEDICAL SYSTEMS INC. Intertech Resources Inc. VITAL SIGNS INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1106', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('July_14,_1999', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resuscitator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Harry', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Leinenweber', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Northern_District Illinois two
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('resuscitator', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meant', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('resuscitator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('normally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('spontaneously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('breathe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('stored', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('squeezebag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('automatically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('directs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('breathe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ambient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('air', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unobstructed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('exit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('port', 'NN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supply', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('squeezebag', 'NN', '', 'O') ('becomes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('occluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('improper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Court of Appeals 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lourie', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('dissented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1349', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schnurr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Marshall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ("O'Toole", 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gerstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Borun', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Richard A. Schnurr Marshall O'Toole Gerstein Murray & Borun Chicago Illinois
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Allen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gerstein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Owen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murray', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Danielle', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Johnston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Allen H. Gerstein Owen J. Murray Danielle M. Johnston
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DeLucia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Richard L. DeLucia Kenyon & Kenyon New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mayer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Loughnane', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Elizabeth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gardner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hutchins', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Richard L. Mayer Elizabeth A. Gardner John R. Hutchins
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gale', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rhodes', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomason', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Moser', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Red', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Bank', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Charles Lee Thomason R. Gale Rhodes Jr. Thomason & Moser Red Bank New Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ORDER', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereto', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ORDERED', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('purpose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clarifying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
ORDERED
__NEW_SENT__
('IT', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('IS', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('FURTHER', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ORDERED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('previous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('withdrawn', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('accompanies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('CLEVENGER', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I')
CLEVENGER Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Smiths', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Industries', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Medical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Systems', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Smiths', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('Northern_District', 'NN', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Smiths', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('resuscitator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Vital_Signs', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Vital_Signs', 'NNS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Smiths Industries Medical Systems Inc. Smiths United_States_District_Court the Northern_District of Illinois Smiths two Vital_Signs Inc. Vital_Signs
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Smith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Indus', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Med', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sys.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Vital_Signs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('4_F.Supp.2d_746', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('748-52', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('N.D.Ill.1997', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Med Sys. Inc. Vital_Signs Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misinterpreted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Smiths', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Smiths
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('vacate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
