('748_F.3d_1354', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United_States_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('SANOFI-AVENTIS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DEUTSCHLAND', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('GMBH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Aventis_Pharma_S.A.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
SANOFI-AVENTIS DEUTSCHLAND GMBH
__NEW_SENT__
('Abbott', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('GMBH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('KG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('GLENMARK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Generics.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Abbott GMBH & Co. KG GLENMARK PHARMACEUTICALS INC. USA Glenmark Generics. Inc. USA
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2012-1489', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('April_21,_2014', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('July_9,_2014', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('angiotensin-converting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inhibitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ACE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('inhibitor', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('calcium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antagonist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
ACE
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('regard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('standing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('lost', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('double', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holder', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Holder
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Dennis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Cavanaugh', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('821_F.Supp.2d_681', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent_holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the District of New Jersey Dennis M. Cavanaugh
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ripe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('give', 'VB', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('destruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new_drug_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('distributor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('standing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('participate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement_suit', '.', '', 'O')
NDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Affirmed
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1356', 'UH', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Allcock', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DLA', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Piper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('US', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('San', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Diego', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
John Allcock DLA US San Diego
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Stuart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pollack', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Panikowski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abbott_GmbH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kg', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Stuart E. Pollack Stanley J. Panikowski Abbott_GmbH & Kg
__NEW_SENT__
('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Benjamin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hsing', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sapna', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palla', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kaye', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Scholer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'UH', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sanofi-aventis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Deutschland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('GmbH', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('et_al', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Benjamin C. Hsing Sapna W. Palla Kaye Scholer LLP New_York New_York Deutschland GmbH
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Galbraith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kenyon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
James Galbraith Kenyon & Kenyon LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Huiya', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shelton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Huiya Wu Lee B. Shelton Michael S. Chang
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LINN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN LINN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement_suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antihypertension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('TarkaTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('TarkaTHE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingredients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('angiotensin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('converting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('enzyme', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ACE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('inhibitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('trandolapril', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('calcium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('channel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('blocker', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('calcium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antagonist', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('verapamil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O')
TarkaTHE_R two ACE
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5721,244', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exclusively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('licensed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sanofi-Aventis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Deutschland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('GmbH', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Germany', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Aventis_Pharma_S.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('France', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Abbott_GmbH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Germany', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
United States ¡¬244_patent Sanofi-Aventis Deutschland GmbH Germany France Germany Abbott_Laboratories and Abbott_Laboratories Inc. United States
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('NDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('TarkaTHE_R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('acquired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Abbott_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
The New Drug Application NDA TarkaTHE_R the Food and Drug Administration 1996 2001
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2007', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('new_drug_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('counterpart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')
2007 Glenmark Pharmaceuticals Inc. Glenmark_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd. Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('244', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Certification', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('leading', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬ Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Launch', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('generic_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('months', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*BIG_TOKEN__1357_provides._21__BIG_TOKEN', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iii', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Glenmark 30 months 355 5
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O')
2010 Plaintiffs
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2010', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('launched', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('generic_product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('at-risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')
June 2010 Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('admitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬244_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('proved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Glenmark ¡¬244_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('15,200,000', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('803,514', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('price', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erosion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
15,200,000 803,514
__NEW_SENT__
('Post-trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('retained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('authority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('assess', 'VB', '', 'O') ('post-verdict', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sustained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('quantum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('244', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prejudicial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('spoliation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('standing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbott', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Glenmark 1 ¡¬ 2 Glenmark 3 Abbott United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('defend', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lacks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('entertain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('proper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rulings.1', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('JURISDICTION', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B')
JURISDICTION
__NEW_SENT__
('Within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('post-verdict', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
30 days Glenmark Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('state', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('premature', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('document', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('retained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('authority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('award', 'VB', '', 'O') ('post-judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('argue', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appellate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('responds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('30', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2011', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disposed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('every', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('defense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('calculation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Glenmark September 30 2011
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('pre-verdict', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('post-verdict', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('standing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('double', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs', 'NNS', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Glenmark Rule 50 2 Glenmark 3 Plaintiffs
__NEW_SENT__
('ECF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._379', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('renewed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('50', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Glenmark Rule 50
__NEW_SENT__
('ECF', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._410', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('30', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O')
Glenmark 30 days
__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('points', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('recognizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('finality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accounting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('complete', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Glenmark 28 1292 2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assigns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-an', ':', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('civil', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('appealable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United_States_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accounting', 'NN', '', 'O')
1292 2 the United_States_Court of Appeals Federal_Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Bosch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Pylon', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Mfg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('719_F.3d_1305', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1317', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2013', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reiterated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accounting', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert Bosch LLC Pylon Mfg Corp. 1317
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('issuance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', 'NORP', 'B') ('closing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('provision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accounting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('*1358', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('accrue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('negate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('finality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('meets', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('terms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1292', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Order 1292 2
__NEW_SENT__
('No', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('magic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('words', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('confer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Local', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Union', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._1992', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('l', 'XX', '', 'O') ('Bhd', 'XX', '', 'O')
Local Union No._1992
__NEW_SENT__
('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Elec', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Elec
__NEW_SENT__
('Workers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Okonite', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('358_F.3d_278', 'CD', '', 'O') ('285', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Cir.2004', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('denomination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'order", 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'judgment", 'NN', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('mean', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('fails', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('satisfy', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('document', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requirement', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final_judgment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rule', 'NN', '', 'O')
Okonite Co. 285
__NEW_SENT__
(')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Potter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('352_F.3d_1142', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1144', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('7th', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('Cir.2003', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('test', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is..', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('finished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Hill 7th
__NEW_SENT__
('Glenmark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ripe', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('exercising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Glenmark
__NEW_SENT__
