('794_F.2d_1561', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('SHILEY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BENTLEY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
SHILEY BENTLEY LABORATORIES INC.
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._85-2226', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('June_16,_1986', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high_efficiency_heat_exchanger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('blood_oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('601_F.Supp._964', 'CD', '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Wallace', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tashima', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('permanently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('enjoining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California Tashima J.
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stay', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('782_F.2d_992', 'CD', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Baldwin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('patent_owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('misrepresentations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omissions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dealing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('double_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('misrepresentation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('omission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('dealings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Patent', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent_owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attorney', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('agent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('materiality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('intent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('arise', 'VB', '', 'O')
Court of Appeals Baldwin Circuit_Judge 1 Patent and Trademark_Office 2 3 4 Patent and Trademark_Office
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('621_F.Supp._105', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
621_F.Supp._105
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1564', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Roy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hofer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Willian', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Brinks', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Olds', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hofer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gilson', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lione', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Ill.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Roy E. Hofer Olds Hofer Gilson & Chicago Ill.
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ropski', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Buonaiuto', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gary M. Ropski Mark J. Buonaiuto
__NEW_SENT__
('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kidd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pennie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
John E. Kidd Pennie New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Gidon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stern', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harbulak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Gidon D. Stern Stephen J. Harbulak
__NEW_SENT__
('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Colaianni', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pennie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appellee', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Joseph V. Colaianni Pennie & Edmonds Washington D.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BALDWIN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SMITH', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
SMITH NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BALDWIN', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Shiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Shiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bentley_Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Bentley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._4065,264', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'264", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('4,138,288', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'288", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
BALDWIN Circuit_Judge Shiley Inc. Shiley Bentley_Laboratories Inc. Bentley U.S. 4,138,288
__NEW_SENT__
('Bentley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bentley
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('resulted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('special', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('recover', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('17,528,000', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('royalty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('twelve', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('percent', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('12', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('price', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('commit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark_Office', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('PTO', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O')
17,528,000 twelve percent 12 % the United States Patent and Trademark_Office
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('notwithstanding', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JNOV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('treated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('merely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('advisory', 'RB', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('double_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prejudgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('interest', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('permanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
JNOV
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amended', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('$', '$', '', 'O') ('44,248,137', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bentley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_13,_1985', 'NNP', '', 'O')
44,248,137 Bentley
__NEW_SENT__
('Shiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bentley_Laboratories', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('601_F.Supp._964', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('225_USPQ_1013_(C.D.Cal.1985)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Shiley Inc. Bentley_Laboratories Inc. 601_F.Supp._964
__NEW_SENT__
('Bentley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('entry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('charges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('calculating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damage_award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issuance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'264_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('doubling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('damage_award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('willful_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Bentley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('new_trial', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prejudicial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bentley Bentley
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('high_efficiency_heat_exchanger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood_oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('lung', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heart-lung', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('employed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heart', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surgery', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_exchanger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('surgery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('rewarm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('normal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('temperature', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cooled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('induces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('condition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('hypothermia', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('slowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('functioning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vital', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('organs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('overall', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consumption', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Hypothermia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('gives', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('perform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procedure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enhances', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('survival', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_exchanger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('formed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hollow', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('helical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('spiral', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('rib', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('wrapped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('encased', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tight-fitting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('shell', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Heated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cooled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inside', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outside', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1565.', 'LS', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1566', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('combination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rib', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('shell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('confines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('flow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('long', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('paths', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Temperature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('control', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('very', 'RB', '', 'O') ('efficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exchange', 'NN', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contacted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('volume', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('helically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ribbed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('name', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Turbotec', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Turbotec
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specifications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Nos', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Shiley U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('RE24', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('783_and_3015,355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('apparatus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aluminum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stainless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('steel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('mentioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shiley_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Stainless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('steel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('compatible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('expensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('poor', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conductivity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Aluminum', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('toxic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conductivity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('relatively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('inexpensive', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Aluminum
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shiley_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('toxic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('aluminum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('coating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polyurethane', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alternative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ring-like', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ribs', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('refer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('tubing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('19_and_24', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'288_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bellows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O')
7 8 19_and_24
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_exchanger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('chamber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood_oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('incorporated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shiley_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shiley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S-100', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Bentley', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('BOS-10', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_exchanger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chamber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bubble_blood_oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O')
Shiley Bentley
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bubble_blood_oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sparge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tube', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('introduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bubbles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('gases', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('What', 'WP', '', 'O') ('actually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('travels', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heat_exchanger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('foam', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('defoaming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Shiley_patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('satisfaction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('placement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('particular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat_exchanger', 'NN', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('tank', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bubble', 'NN', '', 'O') ('oxygenator', 'NN', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('enhanced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('blood-gas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
