('608_F.3d_1333', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TRIMED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INCORPORATED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('STRYKER', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
STRYKER
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2009-1423', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('June_9,_2010', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
June_9,_2010
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implantable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('set', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bone_fractures', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Manuel_L._Real', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('noninfringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court California J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('514_F.3d_1256', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals 514_F.3d_1256
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Manuel_L._Real', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
California J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('again', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Linn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Linn Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('fact_issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('explain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invocation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commonsense', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('consider', 'VB', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('secondary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('considerations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('fact_issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('reassignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('warranted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('preserve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('appearance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('justice', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1335', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grossman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Niro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Scavone', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Haller', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Niro', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lee F. Grossman Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('*1336', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grossman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grossman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Offices', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Sean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kneafsey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kneafsey', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Tostado', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Associates', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Mark M. Grossman Chicago Sean M. Kneafsey Tostado & Associates LLP Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Vogler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Held', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gregory J. Vogler McAndrews Held & Malloy Ltd. Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Surrette', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stephanie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Samz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Robert A. Surrette Stephanie F. Samz
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LINN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('LINN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('returns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('us', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('construction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('questions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TriMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stryker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('514_F.3d_1256', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2008', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('TriMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
second TriMed Inc. Stryker Corp. 514_F.3d_1256 TriMed
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('TriMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Incorporated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('TriMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._5931,839', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('¡¬839_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('``', '``', 'PRODUCT', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stryker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Stryker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
TriMed Incorporated TriMed California U.S. the ¡¬839_patent `` Stryker Corporation Stryker
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('resolved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stryker', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reassignment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('advisable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('preserve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appearance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('justice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('instruction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reassign', 'VB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judge', 'NN', '', 'O')
Stryker
__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬839_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('TriMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬839_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implantable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('set', 'VB', '', 'O') ('bone_fractures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wrist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colles', 'NNPS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O')
TriMed ¡¬839_patent Colles
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬839_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('setting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Colles', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('merit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discussion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O')
¡¬839_patent four two
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('internal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fixation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cuts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wrist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_bones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('reduces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bone_fractures', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('appl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ies', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('plates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('screws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('needed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬839_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.6-8', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('usually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opening', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('positioning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('metal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('attaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fractured_bone_fragments', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('screws', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('reduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drawbacks', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('First', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('screw_holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('lead', 'VB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fragmentation', 'NN', '', 'O')
First
__NEW_SENT__
('Second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('osteoporotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('threads', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('attach', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O')
Second
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rotation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('screw', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_fragment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('causes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('compression', 'NN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fragment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('shatter', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('percutaneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pinning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Kirschner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('wires', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('K-wires', 'NNPS', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_bone_fragment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable_bone_fragment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('out', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_bone_fragment', 'NN', '', 'O')
second first one Kirschner K-wires
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('weaken', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fragmented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('better', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('suited', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('screws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fixating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('small', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('osteoporotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fragments', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tendency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('bend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('displaced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('doctors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('immobilize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wrist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('elbow', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('heals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('subjecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stiffness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('associated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('casts', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬839_patent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('describes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('implantable_device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('kinds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1337', 'NN', '', 'O') ('components', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('screws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pins', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('screw_holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pin', 'VB', '', 'O') ('holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opposite_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O')
¡¬839_patent three one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('setting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fractures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('permits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('rigid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fixation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fragments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('immediate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('joint', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬839_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.3', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.22-43', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_5', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬839_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('illustrative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('implanting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('opens', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('skin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('slides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_bone_fragment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('embeds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable_bone_fragment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('leaving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_fragment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
one 11 9 11 10 8 9
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('positions', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('extending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fractured_fragment', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('rests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 11 8 9 3
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('observed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TriMed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hole', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('stabilizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('projecting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('movement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('slide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('axially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preventing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('compression', 'NN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fracture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
TriMed 3 8 1 1 11
__NEW_SENT__
('514', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('F.3d', 'CD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1260', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
514 1260
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surgeon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('places', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opposite_end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable_bone_fragment', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fragment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('screws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('screw_holes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stable_bone_fragment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 10 1 7 2 1 10
__NEW_SENT__
