('492_F.3d_1350', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TAKEDA', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('CHEMICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INDUSTRIES', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', ',', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Takeda_Pharmaceuticals_North_America', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ALPHAPHARM', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PTY.', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genpharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TAKEDA CHEMICAL INDUSTRIES LTD. Takeda_Pharmaceuticals_North_America ALPHAPHARM PTY. LTD. Genpharm Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._06-1329', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('June_28,_2007', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diabetes', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Denise', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cote', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('417_F.Supp.2d_341', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court J. 417_F.Supp.2d_341
__NEW_SENT__
('Manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lourie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Lourie Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('closest_prior_art_compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antidiabetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('person', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ordinary_skill', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prompted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('modify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('closest_prior_art_compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('homologation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ring-walking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('synthesize', 'VB', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('harmless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('incorrectly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('implying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('histories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('accessible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dyk', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dyk Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1351', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Conlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Edwards', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Angell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palmer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dodge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('MA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('*1352', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
David G. Conlin Edwards Angell Palmer & Dodge LLP Boston MA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Barbara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kathleen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Samansky', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Anthony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Viola', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Andre', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cizmarik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Barbara L. Moore Kathleen B. Carr Adam P. Samansky Anthony J. Viola Andre K. Cizmarik
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Chao', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Takeda_Pharmaceuticals_North_America', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lincolnshire', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Mark Chao Lincolnshire IL
__NEW_SENT__
('Kevin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Murphy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Frommer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lawrence', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Haug', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Kevin F. Murphy New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Edgar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Haug', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hovden', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Edgar H. Haug Jeffrey A. Hovden
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('DYK', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE BRYSON DYK
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Concurring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('DYK', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('LOURIE', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pty.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Genpharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('4,687,777', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Alphapharm Pty. Ltd. Genpharm Inc. Alphapharm 4,687,777 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chem', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Indus.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mylan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Labs.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('417_F.Supp.2d_341', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y.2006', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Takeda Chem Indus. Ltd. Mylan Labs. S.D.N.Y.2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('determining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hence', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Diabetes', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('disease', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('inability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('regulate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('blood_sugar', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inadequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('levels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('insulin-a', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('hormone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pancreas', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Insulin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('allows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('blood_sugar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('glucose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('derived', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('food', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O')
Insulin
__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('types', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diabetes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Type', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Type', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'I')
two Type 1 and Type 2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Type', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'GPE', 'I') ('diabetes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pancreas', 'NN', '', 'O') ('fails', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('insulin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('individuals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('suffering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diabetes', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('regularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('receive', 'VB', '', 'O') ('insulin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('external', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O')
Type 1
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contrast', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Type', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('diabetic_individuals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('insulin', 'NN', '', 'O')
Type 2
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('bodies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('unable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('effectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('insulin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('insulin_resistance', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('glucose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cells', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('depriving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('main', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('diabetes', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('common', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diabetes-affecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('90', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('diabetic_individuals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
2 90 %
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1990s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('thiazolidinediones', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('TZDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Type', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('diabetes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the 1990s Type 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Chemical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Industries', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Takeda_Pharmaceuticals_North_America', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('TZDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1970s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I')
Takeda Chemical Industries Ltd. Takeda_Pharmaceuticals_North_America Inc. Takeda the 1970s
__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('revealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TZDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('acted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('insulin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sensitizers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('ameliorate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('insulin_resistance', 'NN', '', 'O')
Takeda
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('function', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TZDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('completely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('understood', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('TZDs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appeared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('glucose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('levels', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('binding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nucleus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PPARgamma', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('activates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('insulin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('receptors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stimulates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('glucose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('transporters', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('417', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('348-49', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transporters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('travel', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cellular', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('glucose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('enter', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bloodstream', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ACTOSTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('control', 'VB', '', 'O') ('blood_sugar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patients', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('suffer', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Type', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'ORG', 'I') ('diabetes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Type 2
__NEW_SENT__
('ACTOSTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('enjoyed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('launch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1999', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1999
__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1353', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('2003', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('47', 'CD', 'PERCENT', 'B') ('%', 'NN', 'PERCENT', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('TZD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('gross', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('exceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'B') ('1.7', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('billion', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I')
2003 47 % TZD that year $ 1.7 billion
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('386', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
386
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ACTOSTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('TZD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O')
TZD
__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent', 'JJ', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('4,687,777', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Thiazolidinedione', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Derivatives', 'VBZ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Useful', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('As', 'IN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Antidiabetic', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Agents', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Takeda U.S._Patent 4,687,777 `` Thiazolidinedione Derivatives Useful As Antidiabetic Agents ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('practically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antidiabetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('agents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('safety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('margin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmacological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('toxicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unfavorable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reactions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬777_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col.1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ll.34-37', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('5', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
1 2 and 5
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Claim 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compositions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Claim 5
__NEW_SENT__
('Those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('read', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmacologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
5
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antidiabetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('consists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmacologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable_salt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('association', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmacologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('excipient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('diluent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id. 1
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('critical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('left_moiety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('namely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ethyl-substituted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pyridyl_ring.1', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ethyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('H5', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pictorially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('drawn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('center', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridyl_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('indicates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('viz.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ethyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('available', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('positions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridyl_ring', 'NN', '', 'O')
four four
__NEW_SENT__
('Takeda', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('417', 'CD', '', 'O') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('360', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
360
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('3-ethyl', 'CD', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4-ethyl', 'CD', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('5-ethyl', 'CD', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('6-ethyl', 'CD', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*BIG_TOKEN__1354_Claim_2__BIG_TOKEN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬777_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('reads', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('5-', 'XX', '', 'O') ('{', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4-', 'XX', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2-', 'XX', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5-ethyl-2-pyridyl', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ethoxy', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('benzyl', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('}', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-2,4-thiazolidinedione', '.', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('¡¬777_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2
__NEW_SENT__
('Pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('5-ethyl', 'CD', '', 'O') ('compound_because', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ethyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('5-position', 'CD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridyl_ring', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('depicted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('et', 'FW', '', 'O') ('seq', 'FW', '', 'O')
Abbreviated New Drug Application the Hatch-Waxman Act U.S. Food and Drug Administration FDA 21 355
__NEW_SENT__
('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sell', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Paragraph', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('¡±', 'CD', '', 'O') ('505', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('B', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Paragraph IV 505 2 ¡¬777_patent 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
Takeda Alphapharm three FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2006', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('commenced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('enforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 17 2006
__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('advanced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alphapharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('entirely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TZD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('referenced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Table', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_b', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alphapharm TZD Table 1 of
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('left_moiety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_b', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pyridyl_ring', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CH3', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('6-position', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ring', 'NN', '', 'O')
6-position
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('chemical_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('illustrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('follows', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_b', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Alphapharm 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('select', 'VB', '', 'O') ('compound_b', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lead_compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antidiabetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('away', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prima_facie_case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Alphapharm
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('continued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alphapharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('succeeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('showing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Takeda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prevail', 'VB', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prima_facie_case', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('rebutted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unexpected', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pioglitazone', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('nontoxicity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Alphapharm Takeda
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Takeda', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Takeda
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬777_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('procured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')
¡¬777_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('today', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B')
today
__NEW_SENT__
('Alphapharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('timely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1
__NEW_SENT__
