('336_F.3d_1322', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TORPHARM', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RANBAXY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PHARMACEUTICALS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Schein_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Danbury_Pharmacal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy_Laboratories_Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Schein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('L.L.C.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy_Schein_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('L.L.C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Defendants-Appellees', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Ranbaxy Schein Pharma L.L.C. L.L.C. Defendants-Appellees
__NEW_SENT__
('No._02-1590', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'RB', '', 'O') ('July_23,_2003', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ulcer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lifland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey John C. Lifland
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clevenger', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nonobvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Clevenger Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1323', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Feder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lord', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bissell', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Brook', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Scott B. Feder Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Anthony', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lehr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
L. Anthony Lehr
__NEW_SENT__
('Darrell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Olson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Knobbe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Martens', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Olson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bear', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Irvine', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Darrell L. Olson Knobbe Martens Olson & Bear LLP Irvine CA
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reisman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Zimmerman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Johnfar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Kerlee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Joseph M. Reisman William R. Zimmerman Johnfar Kerlee
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1324', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeals', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schein_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Danbury_Pharmacal', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ranbaxy_Laboratories_Limited', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Schein', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy_Schein_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._5670,671', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
TorPharm Inc. the District of New_Jersey Ranbaxy Pharmaceuticals Inc. Schein_Pharmaceutical Inc. Danbury_Pharmacal Inc. Ranbaxy Schein Pharma LLC Ranbaxy TorPharm ÁÂ671
__NEW_SENT__
('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy_Pharms.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._99-_CV-714', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.N.J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
TorPharm Inc. No._99-_CV-714 D.N.J
__NEW_SENT__
('Aug._6,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecuting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_process_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('negation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unrelated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rebutting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('challenge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_process_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TorPharm 1 1 TorPharm Ranbaxy
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('despite', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('assertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
TorPharm 1
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proceedings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ranitidine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antihistamine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('inhibits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('secretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('treat', 'VB', '', 'O') ('ulcers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Ranitidine
__NEW_SENT__
('Several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('forms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonparty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Glaxo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('extensive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Glaxo Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Glaxo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Group', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('153_F.3d_1366', 'CD', '', 'O') ('47_USPQ2d_1836_(Fed.Cir.1998)', 'CD', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Glaxo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Novopharm_Ltd.', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('110_F.3d_1562', 'CD', '', 'O') ('42_USPQ2d_1257_(Fed.Cir.1997)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Glaxo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Novopharm_Ltd.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('52_F.3d_1043', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('34_USPQ2d_1565_(Fed.Cir.1995)', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
Glaxo Group TorPharm Inc. Glaxo Inc. Novopharm_Ltd. 42_USPQ2d_1257_(Fed.Cir.1997) Glaxo Inc. 52_F.3d_1043 34_USPQ2d_1565_(Fed.Cir.1995)
__NEW_SENT__
('That', 'DT', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('concerned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('overcame', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('undesirable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('filtration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'NN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('relates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
TorPharm 1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('crystallizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('solution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('isopropyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alcohol', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('harder', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denser', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('providing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('larger', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('sized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('gives', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filtration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('ÁÂ671_patent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('col._3,_ll._26-27', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('distinguished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('reflecting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('bulk_density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tap_density', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 two
__NEW_SENT__
('According', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulk_density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('gm/ml', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tap_density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'JJS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('gm/ml.1', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Id.at', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ll', 'RB', '', 'O')
1 at least 0.23 at least 0.28 Id.at
__NEW_SENT__
('31-32', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O')
ÁÂ671_patent 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Representative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('principal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('requirements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('yields', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('densities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three-', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('four-carbon', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('alcohol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
2 two 1 2
__NEW_SENT__
('Process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('sic', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Ranitidine_Hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('filtration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('*1325', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulk_density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('gm/ml', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ii', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tap_density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('less', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('about', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('0.28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('gm/ml', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('adding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Ranitidine_Hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anhydrous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hydroxylic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('solvent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('alkanol', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('3-4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('carbon', 'NN', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('dissolves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Ranitidine_Hydrochloride', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recovering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Ranitidine_Hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O')
about 0.23 about 0.28 at least one 3-4
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('originally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('include', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tap_density_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('simply', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('yielding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Ranitidine_Hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tap_density_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('defining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amendment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rejections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Glaxo', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O')
Glaxo 1
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('divisional', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('yielded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('United_States_Patent_No._5523,423', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423', 'JJ', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
ÁÂ423
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tap_density_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('product-by-process_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('671', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 ÁÂ 671
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('North', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Carolina', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('423', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalidated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meeting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tap_density_limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TorPharm North Carolina 423 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Genpharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nos._5', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':97-CV-686-BO', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-658-BO', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-968-BO', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D.N.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Genpharm Inc. 3 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Mar._8,_1999', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Mar._8,_1999
__NEW_SENT__
('Evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina_litigation', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('revealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('three', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('years', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('423', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Interchem', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('sold', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('290', 'CD', 'QUANTITY', 'B') ('kg', 'NNS', 'QUANTITY', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hydrochloride', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Geneva', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
North_Carolina_litigation 1992 more than three years ÁÂ 423 Interchem Corporation three 290 kg 1 Geneva Pharmaceuticals Inc
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('slip', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('5', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.
__NEW_SENT__
('Neither', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Interchem', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Geneva', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Interchem Geneva TorPharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Quality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tests', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Geneva', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('lots', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('densities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.23', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('gm/ml', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tap', 'NN', '', 'O') ('densities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('0.28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('gm/ml', 'NN', '', 'O')
Geneva two three more than 0.23 more than 0.28
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('North', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Carolina', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('meeting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('limitations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('product_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereby', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalidating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('102', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')2', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Id.', 'NNPS', 'NORP', 'B') ('slip', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('8', 'CD', '', 'O')
North Carolina ÁÂ423 more than one year 35 Id.
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Interchem', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product-by-process_claims', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina_litigation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Interchem 1 ÁÂ423_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('slip', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('op.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', '', 'O')
Id.
__NEW_SENT__
('TorPharm', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Ranbaxy ÁÂ671 United_States_District_Court the District of New_Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('principles', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('collateral_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Ranbaxy
__NEW_SENT__
('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('contended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('representation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('allowance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('allowable', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invalidation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423_patent', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O')
Ranbaxy TorPharm ÁÂ423_patent ÁÂ671_patent ÁÂ423_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ranbaxy
__NEW_SENT__
('TorPharm_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy_Pharms.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._99-_CV-714', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.N.J', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
No._99-_CV-714 D.N.J
__NEW_SENT__
('Aug._17,_2001', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('acknowledging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('*1326', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re-litigating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423_patent', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_process_claims', 'CD', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('legally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('linked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('product_claim', 'NN', '', 'O')
TorPharm ÁÂ423_patent ÁÂ423
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reaching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assumed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('nonobvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('novel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reason', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_sale', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dictate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_process_claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TorPharm 1 ÁÂ671 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('requested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ranbaxy
__NEW_SENT__
('Arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('epitome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Connell', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sears', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Roebuck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('722_F.2d_1542', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1548', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('220_USPQ_193', 'CD', '', 'O') ('198', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.1983', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('noting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('102', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('source', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('suggested', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('notion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be..', 'VB', '', 'O') ('non-obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('embodying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invalidated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'I') ('102', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('prior_sale', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
3 Connell Sears Roebuck & Co. 1548 section 102 103 Ranbaxy a Section 102
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('response', 'NN', '', 'O') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_process_claims', 'CD', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ423', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('product_claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina_decision', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('addressed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Interchem', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('produced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('persuaded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O')
TorPharm ÁÂ423 North_Carolina_decision Interchem Ranbaxy
__NEW_SENT__
('Declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('distinction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('made..', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('between..', 'VB', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('hand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('false', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('distinction', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
one Ranbaxy
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reasoned', 'VBD', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('allowed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('now', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argue', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonobviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_claims', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anything', 'NN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
ÁÂ671_claims 1
__NEW_SENT__
('Given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('North_Carolina_decision', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('ranitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lack', 'VB', '', 'O') ('novelty', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('102', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('collateral_estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('disputing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_claims', 'NNPS', '', 'O')
North_Carolina_decision 1 section 102 TorPharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('initial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Ranbaxy', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ÁÂ671_process_claims', 'CD', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Ranbaxy 35 103
__NEW_SENT__
('TorPharm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('exercise', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TorPharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.Á±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
TorPharm 28 1
__NEW_SENT__
