('812_F.3d_1295', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TRANSWEB', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INNOVATIVE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PROPERTIES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._2014-1646', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Feb._10,_2016', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('filtration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('membranes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('industrial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('respirators', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Walker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Process', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O')
Walker Process
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Faith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hochberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('16_F.Supp.3d_385', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('holder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
The United States District Court the District of New_Jersey S. Hochberg J. 16_F.Supp.3d_385
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Hughes', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Hughes Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('samples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plasma-fluorinated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filtration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('membrane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('given', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trade', 'NN', '', 'O') ('show', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public_disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('invalidated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obtaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('supported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('incurred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('defending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('antitrust_injury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treble', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Clayton', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I')
the Clayton Act
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1299', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ernest', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Williams', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Quinn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Emanuel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Urquhart', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Michael Ernest Williams Quinn Emanuel Urquhart & Sullivan LLP Los Angeles
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valerie', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Roddy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Harold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barza', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Sanford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Weisburst', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Philip', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sternhell', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Valerie Roddy Harold Barza Sanford Ian Weisburst New York Philip Charles Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Seth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Waxman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cutler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pickering', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hale', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Dorr', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Seth P. Waxman Wilmer Cutler Pickering Hale Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Saunders', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hugh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Merber', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fleming', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sarah', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('B', 'NN', '', 'O')
Thomas Saunders Kenneth Hugh Merber Mark Christopher
__NEW_SENT__
('Petty', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Boston', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Petty Boston
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('WALLACH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('HUGHES', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
BRYSON HUGHES
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('HUGHES', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
3M TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('non-infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('prior_public_use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O')
TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('advisory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Walker_Process_antitrust_violation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('remedy', 'NN', '', 'O')
Walker_Process_antitrust_violation
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approximately', 'RB', 'MONEY', 'B') ('$', '$', 'MONEY', 'I') ('26', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('trebled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
approximately $ 26 million TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('corroborating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior_public_use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('context', 'NN', '', 'O')
TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('affirmative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('latter', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('find', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appropriately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('flow', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unlawful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('violation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antitrust_injury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('properly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('serve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TransWeb 3M
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respirators', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('worn', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('workers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dirty', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('otherwise', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contaminated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('worksite', 'NN', '', 'O')
I. TransWeb 3M
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_media', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('consist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('nonwoven_fibrous_webs', 'JJ', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('rely', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fibers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('traditional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('woven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O')
nonwoven_fibrous_webs
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('use', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('melting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pellets', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('polypropylene', 'NN', '', 'O') ('blowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('melted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('thin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('film', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('cool', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('solidify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonwoven_fibrous_web', 'CD', '', 'O')
TransWeb 3M
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_medium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('imparting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_charge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_medium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('repel', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('capture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('particulates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('mechanical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electromagnetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('means', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_medium', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('semipermanent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('electrical_charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('imparted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('electret', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('independently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('imparting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electret', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('characteristic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('plasma_fluorination', 'NN', '', 'O')
TransWeb 3M
__NEW_SENT__
('Fluorination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('introducing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fluorine_atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical_structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_web', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('techniques', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('involved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('mixing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('fluorine_compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('*1300', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('melted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('filter_material', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disadvantageous', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discovered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('advantageous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fibrous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('introduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluorine_atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical_structure', 'NN', '', 'O')
TransWeb 3M first
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('exposing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('gaseous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fluorine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_web', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plasma', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('intense', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('electromagnetic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('energy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plasma', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('bonds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_web', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('break', 'VB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fluorine_atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('fill', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bonds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('fluorine_compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_web', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Plasma-fluorinated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filter_media', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('environments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('types', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filter_media', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('might', 'MD', '', 'O') ('perform', 'VB', '', 'O') ('poorly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('quickly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('degrade', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('National', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Institute', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Occupational_Safety', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Health', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('NIOSH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('service', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oily', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('environment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respirators', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('categorizing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('resistant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('resistant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('oil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O')
The National Institute for Occupational_Safety Health ( NIOSH
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Occupational_Safety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Health', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('OSHA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('regulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('governing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('NIOSH', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('rating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respirators', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('types', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('worksites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Health Administration OSHA NIOSH the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('focuses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('largely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('events', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('surrounding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filtration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('industry', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exposition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('late', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('April', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('early', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('May', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
late April early May of 1997
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('uncontested', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('founder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Kumar', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ogale', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('attended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('handed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('samples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filter_material', 'JJ', '', 'O')
TransWeb Kumar Ogale
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_material', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('included', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('samples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('T-Melt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('products', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('identifier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('melt-blown', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('nonwoven_fibrous_web', 'CD', '', 'O') ('media', 'NNS', '', 'O')
TransWeb T-Melt
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('primary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Ogale', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('handed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('samples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('T-Melt', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('P', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plasma-fluorinated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('T-Melt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mr._Ogale
__NEW_SENT__
('Mr._Ogale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('testified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('hand', 'VB', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('T-Melt_P_samples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('documents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contest', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr._Ogale', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('handed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('out', 'RP', '', 'O') ('T-Melt_P_samples', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('they', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('serve', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plasma_fluorination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('methods', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Mr._Ogale
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('occurred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'DATE', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('year', 'NN', 'DATE', 'I') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public_disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plasma_fluorination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expo', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statutory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bar', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patentability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('least', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O')
more than one year
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('1998', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Application', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('09/109,497', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
July of 1998 U.S. Patent Application U.S
__NEW_SENT__
('Patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('6,397', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('458_and_6808,551', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('earliest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O')
6,397 458_and_6808,551
__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('asserted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬551_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
3M ¡¬458 ¡¬551_patent TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plasma_fluorination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonwoven_fibrous_webs', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('family', 'NN', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('hydro-charging', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('technique', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('impart', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electrical_charge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filter_medium', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Minnesota', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Minnesota TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('voluntarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('apparent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('personal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O')
TransWeb New_Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('31_and_57', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('31_and_57', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('unenforceability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬551_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('due', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable_conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Walker_Process_antitrust_violation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fraudulent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('procurement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('assertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('551', 'CD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('sham', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('violation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assertion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬458', 'NN', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('¡¬551_patent', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('s', 'POS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('entitlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_violations', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entitlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_violations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
New_Jersey 31_and_57 31_and_57 ¡¬458 ¡¬551_patent ¡¬458 ¡¬458 ¡¬551_patent
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('delivered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('31_and_57', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('31_and_57', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('*1301', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('3M', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Walker', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Process', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('violation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sham', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('violation', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('TransWeb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lost', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antitrust_damages', 'NNS', '', 'O')
31_and_57 31_and_57 Walker Process TransWeb
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('verdicts', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O')
3M
__NEW_SENT__
('3M', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')
3M
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
