('846_F.3d_1190', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('TINNUS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ENTERPRISES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Zuru', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('TELEBRANDS', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bed_Bath', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Beyond', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('2016-1410', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('24', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2017', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
January 24 2017
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('toy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('filled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('multiple_water_balloons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('channeling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balloons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hollow_tubes', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('housing', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Schroeder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('2015_WL_11089480', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('adopted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('report', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recommendation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Love', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('United', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('States', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Magistrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('2015_WL_11089479', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('barring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas Robert Schroeder III J. 2015_WL_11089480 John D. Love 2015_WL_11089479
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Stoll', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Stoll Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('attached', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('analyzing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('likelihood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('merits', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('review', 'VB', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('raise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('failed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('raise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial_question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('term', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('irreparable_harm', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1194', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('No._6', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') (':15-cv-00551-RWS-JDL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Schroeder', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('III', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court Texas No._6 Robert Schroeder III
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mansfield', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dunlap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Dunlap', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bennett', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ludwig', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('PLLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Leesburg', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('VA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Thomas Mansfield Dunlap Dunlap Bennett & Ludwig PLLC Leesburg
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Ludwig', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lorenz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Olavson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Spendlove', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Cortland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Putbrese', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richmond', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('VA.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Underhill', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Boies', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schiller', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Flexner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Telebrands_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O')
David Ludwig Eric Lorenz Robert D. Spendlove Cortland Christopher Putbrese Richmond David Michael Underhill Boies Schiller & Flexner LLP Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stacey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grigsby', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Amy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Neuhardt', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Boies', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Armonk', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Elana_Araj', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cooper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dunham', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Stacey K. Grigsby Amy Lynn Neuhardt David Boies Cooper & Dunham LLP New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Maldonado', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Elana_Araj', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cooper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Dunham', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('appeared', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Bed_Bath', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Beyond', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wallach', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stoll', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert Thomas Maldonado Elana_Araj Cooper & Dunham LLP New_York NY Bed_Bath &
__NEW_SENT__
('Stoll', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Eastern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Tinnus_Enterprises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Telebrands_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('selling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('accused', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Balloon_Bonanza', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('colorable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('imitation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'IN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Texas LLC
__NEW_SENT__
('Telebrands', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('abused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concluding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('likely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('vulnerable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Tinnus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('showing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('irreparable_harm', 'NN', '', 'O')
1 2 3 Tinnus
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('disagree', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Telebrands', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('grant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Telebrands
__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Tinnus_Enterprises', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('produces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('toy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('balloons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1195', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._9051,066', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('calls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Bunch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('O', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Balloons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
LLC U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('Telebrands_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('competing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Balloon_Bonanza', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
Balloon_Bonanza
__NEW_SENT__
('Both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('attach', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hose', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('fill', 'VB', '', 'O') ('multiple_water_balloons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('once', 'RB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('channeling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('balloons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('set', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hollow_tubes', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side-by-side', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('comparison', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rival', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Br', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Appellee Br
__NEW_SENT__
('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
11
__NEW_SENT__
('Tinnus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ZURU', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.1', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Tinnus', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Telebrands', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Bed_Bath', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Beyond', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Telebrands', 'NNPS', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'066_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary_injunction', 'NN', '', 'O')
Tinnus ZURU Ltd.1 Tinnus Telebrands and Bed_Bath & Beyond Inc. Telebrands
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Magistrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Report', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Recommendation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('R', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('recommended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('granting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Tinnus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Report and Recommendation R & R '' Tinnus
__NEW_SENT__
('Tinnus', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Enters.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Telebrands_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._15-00551', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('2015_WL_11089479', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
LLC No._15-00551 E.D
__NEW_SENT__
('Tex', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Sept.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Magistrate', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Op', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Sept. 11 2015 Magistrate Op
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('overruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Telebrands', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('objections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('adopted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('R', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Tinnus', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Telebrands the R & R the R & R 's Tinnus
__NEW_SENT__
('Tinnus', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Enters.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Telebrands_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._15-00551', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('2015_WL_11089480', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('E.D', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
LLC No._15-00551 E.D
__NEW_SENT__
('Tex', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dec.', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('2015', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Dec. 2 2015
__NEW_SENT__
('Shortly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('thereafter', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Trial', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('instituted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Post-Grant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'066_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('likely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arguments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Patent Trial Appeal Board
__NEW_SENT__
