('890_F.3d_1313', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('UCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('UCB_BioPharma_SPRL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technologies', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Harris', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('FRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
UCB INC. UCB_BioPharma_SPRL Research Corporation Technologies Inc. Harris FRC Corporation
__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ACCORD', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('HEALTHCARE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Intas_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Zydus_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('USA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cadila_Healthcare_Limited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Amneal_Pharmaceuticals_LLC', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('Amneal_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Aurobindo_Pharma_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Aurobindo_Pharma_USA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Breckenridge_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sun_Pharma_Global_FZE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Watson_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.-Florida', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('nka', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Actavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Laboratories', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('FL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Watson_Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('nka', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Actavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('MSN_Laboratories_Pvt', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ACCORD HEALTHCARE INC. New_York LLC Actavis Laboratories FL Inc. Watson_Pharma Inc. Actavis Pharma Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Alembic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Ltd. Alembic Pharmaceuticals Ltd.
__NEW_SENT__
('Alembic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Limited', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Actavis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('nka', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Allergan', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Finance', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I')
Alembic Pharma Limited Actavis Inc. Allergan Finance LLC Defendants
__NEW_SENT__
('2016-2610', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2016-2683', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2016-2685', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2016-2698', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2016-2710', 'CD', '', 'O') ('2017-1001', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('May_23,_2018', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_drug_manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('generic_lacosamide_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (':13-cv-01206-LPS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01207-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01208-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01209-LPS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01210-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01211-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01212-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01213-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01214-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01215-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01216-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01218-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01219-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01220-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:14-cv-00834-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('201_F.Supp.3d_491', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
the District of Delaware Nos._1 Leonard P. Stark
__NEW_SENT__
('Generic', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Generic
__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Stoll', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Stoll Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipated', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Prost', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Procedural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Posture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Judgment', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1316', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Nos._1', 'NNP', '', 'O') (':13-cv-01206-LPS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01207-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01208-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01209-LPS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01210-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01211-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01212-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01213-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01214-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01215-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01216-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01218-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01219-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:13-cv-01220-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1:14-cv-00834-LPS', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Leonard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware Leonard P. Stark
__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dimitrios', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Drivas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Case', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Dimitrios T. Drivas
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Gahtan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Christopher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Glancy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Majchrzak', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Laura', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Moran', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Trainor', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Jack', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Blumenfeld', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Megan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dellinger', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Maryellen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Noreika', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Morris', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Nichols', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Arsht', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Tunnell', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Priscilla', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Grace', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Dodson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jeffrey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Elikan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('George', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Frank', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pappas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Covington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Burling', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Alexa', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Hansen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('San', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Francisco', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Adam Gahtan Christopher J. Glancy Eric M. Majchrzak Laura Moran James Trainor Jack B. Blumenfeld Megan Nichols Arsht & Tunnell LLP Wilmington DE Priscilla Grace Dodson Jeffrey B. Elikan Alexa Hansen San Francisco
__NEW_SENT__
('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('G.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Greco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Albany', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Accord', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Healthcare', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Intas_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd.', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shaw', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shaw', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Keller', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilmington', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DE', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Gurpreet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Singh', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Walia', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Gresser', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NN', '', 'O') ('NY', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Richard G. Greco Albany Accord Healthcare Inc. Intas_Pharmaceuticals_Ltd. John W. Shaw Shaw Keller LLP Wilmington DE Gurpreet Singh Walia Cohen & Gresser
__NEW_SENT__
('Maureen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Rurka', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Winston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Strawn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Alembic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Amneal_Pharmaceuticals_LLC', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('Amneal_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Aurobindo_Pharma_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Aurobindo_Pharma_USA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Breckenridge_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cadila_Healthcare_Limited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('MSN_Laboratories_Pvt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mylan_Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Sun_Pharma_Global_FZE', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Watson_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.-Florida', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Watson_Pharma', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Zydus_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('USA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-appellants', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Amneal_Pharmaceuticals_LLC', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('Amneal_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Aurobindo_Pharma_Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Aurobindo_Pharma_USA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Breckenridge_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MSN_Laboratories_Pvt', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sun_Pharma_Global_FZE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Watson_Laboratories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('Florida', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Watson_Pharma', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lombardi', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Reynolds', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mcnair', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Samuel', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Park', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Klein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Eimeric', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Reig-Plessis', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Maureen L. Rurka Winston & Strawn Chicago Alembic Pharmaceuticals Ltd. MSN_Laboratories_Pvt Ltd. Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc. Sun_Pharma_Global_FZE Sun_Pharmaceutical_Industries Ltd. Inc.-Florida Watson_Pharma Inc. USA ) Inc. New_York LLC LLC George C. Lombardi John Reynolds Samuel S. Park Charles B. Klein Eimeric Washington
__NEW_SENT__
('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Jeffer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ali', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Carlson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Caspers', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Vandenburgh', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lindquist', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schuman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.A.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Alembic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceuticals', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Sarah', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Stensland', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Patterson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Thuente', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Pedersen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Minneapolis', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('MN', 'NNP', '', 'O')
M. Jeffer Ali Carlson Vandenburgh Lindquist & Schuman Minneapolis Alembic Pharmaceuticals Ltd. Sarah Stensland Minneapolis
__NEW_SENT__
('Ian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Scott', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Taft', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Stettinius', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hollister', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Corp.', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Apotex_Inc.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Auten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('T.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ruzich', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Ian Scott Chicago Stephen Auten Richard T. Ruzich
__NEW_SENT__
('Nicole', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('W.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stafford', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wilson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Sonsini', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Goodrich', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rosati', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Austin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('TX', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Mylan_Inc.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Aden', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Allen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Adam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Burrowbridge', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Joshua', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kushner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Steuer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Palo', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Alto', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('CA', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Nicole W. Stafford Wilson Mylan_Pharmaceuticals_Inc. Mylan_Inc. Aden M. Allen Adam William Burrowbridge Washington DC Joshua B. Kushner Los Angeles CA David S. Steuer Palo Alto
__NEW_SENT__
('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gaertner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Locke', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lord', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Zydus_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('USA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cadila_Healthcare_Limited', 'VBD', '', 'O')
Michael John Gaertner Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Abramowitz', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Hugh', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Balsam', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Timothy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Flynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Peterson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Andrea', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lynn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wayda', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('NY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
David Brian Hugh S. Balsam Timothy Flynn Peterson Andrea Lynn Wayda New_York NY
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Prost', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Bryson', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stoll', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chief_Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Prost', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Stoll', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1314*1317', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arises', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I')
the Hatch-Waxman Act
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellees', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('UCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('UCB_BioPharma_SPRL', 'ADD', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Technologies', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Harris', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('FRC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('UCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('own', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellees UCB Inc. UCB_BioPharma_SPRL Research Corp. Technologies Inc. Harris FRC Corp. UCB U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('RE38,551', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('covers', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-epileptic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('treats', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('epilepsy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('central', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nervous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('UCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Applications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('NDAs', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('cover', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anti-epileptic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('marketed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('tradename', 'NN', '', 'O') ('VimpatTHE_R', 'NN', '', 'O')
UCB New Drug Applications the Food and Drug Administration FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('Approved', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Products', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('With', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Therapeutic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Equivalence', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Evaluations', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Orange', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Book', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('covering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('VimpatTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')
FDA Approved Drug Products With Therapeutic Equivalence Evaluations
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('generic_drug_manufacturers', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Applications', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VimpatTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Abbreviated New Drug Applications
__NEW_SENT__
('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('governing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('provisions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('unenforceable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('generic_lacosamide_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Consequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('UCB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Appellants', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Delaware', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
UCB Appellants United_States_District_Court the District of Delaware
__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('stipulated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('9', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('13', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('maintained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellants 9 10 and 13
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('exhaustive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('misapplied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('anticipates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and/or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('renders', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('explained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('fully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('correct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('standards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('analyses', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('And', 'CC', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('discern', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ultimate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1318BACKGROUND', 'UH', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('VimpatTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Lacosamide', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('belongs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('functionalized', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amino', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acids', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3_positions', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('variables', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('representing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vast', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
FAA
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('aromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heteroaromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Aromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-dimensional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('typically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('organized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('benzene', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Heteroaromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oxygen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('nitrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('aromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('contain', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('heteroatom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('atom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('carbon', 'NN', '', 'O')
at least one
__NEW_SENT__
('Nonaromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('three-dimensional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('organized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rings', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R-enantiomer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('N-benzyl-2-acetamido-3-methoxypropion-amide', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
("SeeBIG_TOKEN__'551_patent__BIG_TOKEN", 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('col.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('3_ll._65', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-67', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('38_ll._9', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-40', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Enantiomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stereoisomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure-i.e.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('way-but', 'NN', '', 'O') ('differ', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('orientation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('three-dimensional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('orientations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('designated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('S.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('50-50', 'CD', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('enantiomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('racemate', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('racemic_mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('R1', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3_positions', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'B') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted_benzyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted_methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methoxymethyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', '', 'O')
R R1 R3_positions R1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stereoisomer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unexpectedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('potent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('corresponding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('S', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('stereoisomer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('racemic_mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('23_ll._31', 'CD', '', 'O') ('-33', 'NFP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('March', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-epileptic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('nor', 'CC', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('advanced', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clinical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trials', 'NNS', '', 'O')
March 1996 FAA FAA
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prior', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('public', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('disclosure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmacological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('efficacy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('safety', 'NN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('support', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-epileptic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')
FAA
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'IN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('VimpatTHE_R', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('remains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('epilepsy', 'NN', '', 'O')
FAA
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('development', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1980s', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Kohn', '.', '', 'O')
the 1980s
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1985', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Dr._Kohn', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant_activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('identified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('AAB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('provided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concept', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti-epileptic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1985 AAB
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Dr._Kohn', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Kohn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant_activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('analogs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('AAB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O')
1987 AAB
__NEW_SENT__
('Kohn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1987', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('reported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('results', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('positions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O')
Kohn 1987 FAA
__NEW_SENT__
('Kohn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1987', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('placement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R3_position', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant_activity', 'NN', '', 'O')
Kohn 1987 R3_position
__NEW_SENT__
('Relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('studied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Kohn', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted_benzyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted_methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Kohn 1987
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('replaces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1319', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('atoms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('molecule', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('another', 'DT', '', 'O') ('atom', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Dr._Kohn', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('racemate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('enantiomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AAB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('APB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AAB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('phenyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1988 AAB APB AAB R3
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('enantiomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AAB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('APB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('10', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('times', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('potent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('S_enantiomers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
AAB APB 10
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('confirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Kohn', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Kohn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant_activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('AAB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('APB', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('resided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('primarily', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stereoisomers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
1990 AAB APB
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('3240', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
3240
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Kohn', ':', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('kept', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R1_positions', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'B') ('constant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('benzyl', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('respectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('testing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('substituents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R3_position', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dr._Kohn R1_positions
__NEW_SENT__
('Finally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Dr._Kohn', 'SYM', '', 'O') ('evaluated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('compound_3l', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('racemate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Kohn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1991', 'CD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1991
__NEW_SENT__
('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3l', 'CD', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxyamino', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exhibited', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('superior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
R3
__NEW_SENT__
('Notably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound_3l', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Compound', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('3l', 'CD', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('instability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('concern', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formulations', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Kohn', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('publications', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('thesis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('completed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('graduate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('student', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Philippe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('LeGall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('LeGall', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Dr._Kohn 1987 Philippe LeGall LeGall
__NEW_SENT__
('LeGall', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('focused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('potential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('activities', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LeGall 15
__NEW_SENT__
('Relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('LeGall', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('disclosed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O')
LeGall
__NEW_SENT__
('Compound', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('107e', 'NNPS', 'PERSON', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('racemate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('meaning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('isolated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('R-enantiomer', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mixture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('S_enantiomers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Compound 107e
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belonged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('polar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('analogues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('68a', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'B')
68a
__NEW_SENT__
('Similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'VB', '', 'O') ('LeGall', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('replaced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R3_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('methoxymethyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O')
LeGall
__NEW_SENT__
('LeGall', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('provides', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('efficacy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('data', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('15', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O')
LeGall 15
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('belonged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic_groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('little', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ED50_values', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('ranging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('100', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg/kg', 'CD', 'GPE', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('300', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg/kg.1', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('comparison', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LeGall', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('reported', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proven', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ED50_values', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('14.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('18.7', 'CD', '', 'O') ('20.1', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('61.0', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg/kg', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ED50_values', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('51.BIG_TOKEN__0_and_62__BIG_TOKEN0', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mg/kg', 'NNP', '', 'O')
ED50_values 100 mg/kg 300 LeGall ED50_values 14.0 61.0 ED50_values
__NEW_SENT__
('Despite', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmacological_data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('LeGall', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('speculated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('structural', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('similarities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('compound', 'VB', '', 'O') ('86b', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('study', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('EDBIG_TOKEN__50_of_62__BIG_TOKEN', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('good', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anticonvulsant_activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
LeGall 86b
__NEW_SENT__
('J.A', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('5001', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('5050', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
5001 5050
__NEW_SENT__
('LeGall', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('active', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('studied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('heteroaromatic_groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R3_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('whereas', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic_group', 'NN', '', 'O')
LeGall
__NEW_SENT__
('Dr._Kohn', ':', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('led', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._5378', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('729_in_1991', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
U.S._Patent_No._5378
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Dr._Kohn', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1995', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
1995
__NEW_SENT__
('Its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('explains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('exhibit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('central', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('nervous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CNS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('treatment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('epilepsy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('CNS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')
CNS CNS
__NEW_SENT__
("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('col.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('1_ll._30', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-33', '.', '', 'O')
1_ll._30
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('share', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('*1320', 'ADD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1_ll._37', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-43', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('lists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('many', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('form', 'VB', '', 'O') ('millions', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
millions
__NEW_SENT__
('Important', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('here', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('teaches', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('values', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('aryl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'IN', '', 'O') ('especially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('benzyl', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('t', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('5_ll._17', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('-19', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R3_position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('lists', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heterocyclics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower', 'VB', '', 'O') ('alkoxy', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('list', 'VB', '', 'O') ('methoxymethyl', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at_col.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('6_ll._13', 'RB', '', 'O') ('-31', 'NFP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Table', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('pharmacological_data', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('54', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('FAAs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Table 1 54
__NEW_SENT__
('None', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Table', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound_107e', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('LeGall', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FAA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxymethyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', '', 'O')
Table 1 LeGall FAA
__NEW_SENT__
('All', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('listed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Table', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'I') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RBIG_TOKEN__1_and_49__BIG_TOKEN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted_benzyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('varying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ranging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('3.3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg/kg', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('300', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('mg/kg', 'CD', '', 'O')
Table 1 of the 3.3 mg/kg 300
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ten', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('lowest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('ED50', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('eight', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('heteroaromatic_groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('nitrogen-based', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O')
ten eight R3 two
__NEW_SENT__
('Unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('none', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('potent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Table', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', '', 'O')
Table 1
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('nonaromatic_groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('moderate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('weak', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('potency', 'NN', '', 'O')
four R3
__NEW_SENT__
('U.S._Patent_No._5654,301', 'WP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuation-in-part', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1993
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('rely', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness-type_double_patenting', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellants
__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('parent', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'729_patent", '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('placed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R1_positions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('relevant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('purposes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('double', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patenting', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('39-47', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('reproduced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
39-47 39
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formula', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acceptable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('salts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('aryl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('aryl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'IN', '', 'O') ('heterocyclic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heterocyclic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cycloalkyl', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cycloalkyl', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'IN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('withdrawing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('*1321', 'NN', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('withdrawing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('at', 'RB', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('least', 'RBS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('A', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Q', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('O', 'UH', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('withdrawing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('n', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
at least one at least one at least one one R3 1-4
__NEW_SENT__
('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
40
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('hydrogen', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O')
39 one R3
__NEW_SENT__
('41', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
41
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('40', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ethyl', 'RB', '', 'O') ('propyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('isopropyl', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('butyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('isobutyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('t-butyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('amyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hexyl', 'NN', '', 'O')
40 one R3
__NEW_SENT__
('42', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
42
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('41', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R2', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O')
41 one R3
__NEW_SENT__
('43', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
43
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('42', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('electron', 'NN', '', 'O') ('donating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkoxy', 'JJ', '', 'O')
42
__NEW_SENT__
('44', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
44
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VB', '', 'O') ('43', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('alkoxy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('methoxy', 'JJ', '', 'O')
43
__NEW_SENT__
('45', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
45
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('according', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('39-44', 'CD', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('wherein', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('n', 'RB', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
one 39-44 1
__NEW_SENT__
('46', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
46
__NEW_SENT__
('An', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-convulsant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('composition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-convulsant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('37-42', 'CD', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('carrier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('therefor', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('47', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
47
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('CNS', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('disorders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('animal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comprising', 'NN', '', 'O') ('administering', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('animal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anti-convulsant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('amount', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('39-44', 'CD', '', 'O')
CNS one
__NEW_SENT__
("'301_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('93_l._3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('-', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('col.', 'NN', '', 'O') ('94_l._21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
93_l._3 94_l._21
__NEW_SENT__
('Independent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('permits', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('R1', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('comprise', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large_number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substituents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('unsubstituted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O')
39 R R1 R3
__NEW_SENT__
('Hence', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('39', 'PRP', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thousands', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('if', 'IN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('millions', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('combinations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
39 thousands millions
__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('list', 'VB', '', 'O') ('some', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('most', 'RBS', '', 'O') ('preferred', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('list', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('contains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('categories', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('substituents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('creating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scope', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('undisputed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('falls', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broad', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'301_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
39
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('45', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('44', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('recites', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('methoxymethyl_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substituent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R3', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('lacosamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'551_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Claim 45 44 R3 R3
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('45', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('recite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('molecules', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O')
Claim 45
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('45', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('depends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('39', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('recites', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('located', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('R', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('R1', 'NNP', '', 'O')
45 39
__NEW_SENT__
