('105_F.3d_1409', 'LS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('VALMET', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('PAPER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('MACHINERY', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plaintiffs-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BELOIT', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') ('CORPORATION', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')
Valmet Inc. BELOIT
__NEW_SENT__
('No._95-1301', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._28,_1997', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Amended', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Grant', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('May_1,_1997', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Barbara', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Crabb', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('895_F.Supp._1158', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('jury_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Wisconsin Barbara B. Crabb J. 895_F.Supp._1158 two
__NEW_SENT__
('Assignee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Rich Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1409', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Myron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pontani', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lieberman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('York', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('City', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiffs-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Cohen Cohen Lieberman & Pavane New York City
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alper', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stuart', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
William A. Alper Michael C. Stuart
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Butler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Stafford', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rosenbaum', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rieser', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hansen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Madison', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('WI', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jaffe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fox', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kintner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Plotkin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kahn', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Jill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Fox', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kintner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Plotkin', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Kahn', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pontani', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Lieberman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Brian E. Butler Hansen Madison WI Michael E. Jaffe Arent Kintner Plotkin & Washington D.C. Jill R. Newman Kintner Plotkin & Kahn Martin B. Pavane Cohen Lieberman & Pavane
__NEW_SENT__
('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('P.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('McAndrews', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Held', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Malloy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
George P. McAndrews McAndrews Held & Chicago IL
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Steven', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hampton', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gregory', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Schodde', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Steven J. Hampton Gregory C. Schodde
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('D.', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Hill', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wimbiscus', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
D. David Hill Thomas J. Wimbiscus
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('RICH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LOURIE', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('BRYSON', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
LOURIE BRYSON
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RICH', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Appellants', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Paper', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Machinery', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corporation', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O')
Appellants Valmet Paper Machinery Inc. Valmet Inc. Valmet Beloit Corporation Valmet
__NEW_SENT__
('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('holds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying-machine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Beloit two
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Valmet Beloit two
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('valid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('further', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Beloit Beloit
__NEW_SENT__
('Valmet', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relate', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drying', 'NN', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('paper-making', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machinery', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('*1410', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper-making', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('sprays', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suspension', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('fiber', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('maneuver', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wet', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('series', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('steps', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('remove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('beginning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('formation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drains', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('operation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gravity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('generally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('involves', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('pressing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('water', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rollers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
second
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('area', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('heated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('designed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('evaporate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('moisture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heated-cylinder', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('segment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('presents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('challenges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_web', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('moves', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('speed', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('avoid', 'VB', '', 'O') ('stretching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('dry', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('evenly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surfaces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Conventionally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('stage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('employed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('heated_cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('tier', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('setup', 'NN', '', 'O')
two
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-tier', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('arrangement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('lies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('lies', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Looking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('length', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-tier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sequence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('alternates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('planes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next_cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opposite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('plane', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_web', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('runs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('beneath', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower-plane_cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper-plane_cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower-plane_cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('lower', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('top', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('surface', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('depicts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two-tier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dryer.1', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arise', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('draws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('cross', 'VB', '', 'O') ('unsupported', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('open', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next_cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('speeds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bottom', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('up', 'RP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('upper', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('portion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tends', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('flutter', 'RB', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('increases', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stretching', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('breakage', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Two-tier', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machines', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('employed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('guide_belts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('accompany', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('circle', 'VB', '', 'O') ('back', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('beginning', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('continuous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('loop', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('guide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rollers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('reduce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('risk', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('damage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('guide_belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('traveling', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('prevents', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heated_cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('directly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('touching', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Soininen_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._3868,780', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('March_4,_1975', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('assignee', 'NN', '', 'O')
first Valmet
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Soininen_patent', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('s', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('substantially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('parallel', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('rows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('guide_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('direct', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('start', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second_row', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('alternating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('around', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('separate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1411', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rows', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('planes', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Soininen_patent two two
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first_group', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('guide_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('cause', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('run', 'VB', '', 'O') ('along', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('opposite', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('next', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinder', 'NN', '', 'O') ('groups', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('direct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('heat', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('first_group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O')
one second
__NEW_SENT__
('Soininen', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discusses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('inclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('foraminous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('i.e.', 'FW', '', 'O') ('perforated', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('guide_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('walls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('enclose', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sides', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loops', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Forming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('closed', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facilitates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('introduction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('pull', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('outside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('tightly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('onto', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('belt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Soininen_patent.2', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('German', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('citing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Soininen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('elaborated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Soininen', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
1981 German Soininen Soininen
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hauser_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('taught', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('efficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('place', 'VB', '', 'O') ('individual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('suction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Soininen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('perforated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('guide_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('using', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('large', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('walls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('close', 'VB', '', 'O') ('off', 'RP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('space', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inside', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('guide_belt', 'NN', '', 'O')
Soininen
__NEW_SENT__
('Hauser', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('emphasized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('benefits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('moving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('suction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('guide_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('closer', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('heated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('keep', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('contact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('much', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('possible', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Although', 'IN', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hauser_application', 'NN', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('published', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('February', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('17', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1983', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
Hauser_application February 17 1983
__NEW_SENT__
('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('submitted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('German-language', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Hauser', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('publication', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_examiner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('during', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('discussed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('below', 'RB', '', 'O')
Beloit Hauser two Beloit
__NEW_SENT__
('More', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('recently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('obtained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('features', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Bel-Champ', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('No._5144,758', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'758_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('September', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('November', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('14', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('No._5249,372', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ("'372_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('5', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('April_9,_1992', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Beloit Bel-Champ No._5144,758 September 8 1992 November 14 1991 No._5249,372 October 5 1993
__NEW_SENT__
('Basically', 'RB', 'ORG', 'B') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tier', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('comprising', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('plurality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('own', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('dryer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('felt', 'VBD', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('vacuum_rolls..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('close_proximity', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('their', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('adjacent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paper_web', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('second', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('mirror-image', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other_side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('web', 'NN', '', 'O')
Basically Beloit 's first one second
__NEW_SENT__
('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single-tier', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('design', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vacuum_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('close_proximity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('vacuum_rolls', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('cylinders', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('distinguish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dryer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('designs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Soininen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Hauser', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Beloit 1 2 3 Soininen Hauser
__NEW_SENT__
('Below', 'RB', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('figure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('patents.3', 'NN', '', 'O')
Beloit
__NEW_SENT__
('*1412.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('-', ':', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Western_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wisconsin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Soininen_patent', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('invalidate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ("'372_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('s', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('due', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('anticipation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Valmet Beloit Wisconsin Soininen_patent Beloit
__NEW_SENT__
('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('counterclaimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O')
Beloit
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Soininen_patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Soininen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('anticipate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Beloit Soininen Beloit
__NEW_SENT__
('A', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four-part', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('followed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Dealing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'372_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1-3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('3', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'372_patent", 'JJ', '', 'O') ('indefinite', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('therefore', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
1_and_2 1-3 3 1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('1_and_2', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('remained', 'VBD', '', 'O')
1_and_2
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('unnecessarily', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Valmet two
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('guilty', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inequitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('failing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('submit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('English', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('translation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Hauser', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_examiner', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Beloit English Hauser
__NEW_SENT__
('Last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('lost', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('profits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('drying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('machine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Mexico', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Valmet Beloit Valmet New Mexico
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('verdict', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('invalidate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O')
Valmet first two
__NEW_SENT__
('Instead', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('overruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('jury', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('indefiniteness', 'NN', '', 'O')
Beloit JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('damages', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Beloit', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('injunction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('barring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('future', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Valmet', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'758", 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'372_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Beloit Valmet
__NEW_SENT__
