('202_F.3d_1340', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('WINNER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('INTERNATIONAL', 'VBZ', 'ORG', 'I') ('ROYALTY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Ching-Rong', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('WANG', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
WINNER INTERNATIONAL ROYALTY Plaintiff-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-1553', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Jan._27,_2000', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('March_6,_2000', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patent_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claiming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anti-theft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('challenging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent_Appeals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Interferences', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('interference_proceeding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('declaring', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
the Board of Patent_Appeals and Interferences
__NEW_SENT__
('Competitor', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('1998_WL_268279', 'CD', '', 'O')
Competitor California
__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Stanley', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Sporkin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('11_F.Supp.2d_18', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('overturned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court the District of Columbia Stanley Sporkin J. 11_F.Supp.2d_18 Board
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Michel', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('submission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('live', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matters', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('required', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('conduct', 'VB', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('de', 'FW', '', 'O') ('novo', 'FW', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('allowing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('late-disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('witnesses', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('testify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('nexus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('patentably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('distinct', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('feature', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('admissible', 'JJ', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('5', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entitled', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Michel Circuit_Judge 1 Board 2 3 4 5
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1342', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Kenneth', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lapatine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Camhy', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Karlinsky', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Stein', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Kenneth A. Lapatine New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gholz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Oblon', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Spivak', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('McClelland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Maier', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Neustadt', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('P.C', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Charles L. Gholz Maier & Neustadt
__NEW_SENT__
('Joseph', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Yanny', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Yanny', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Grieco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Osher', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Los', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Angeles', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Joseph A. Yanny Los Angeles California
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Grieco', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Michael', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('DiNardo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mary L. Grieco Michael A. DiNardo
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Charles', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Wolfe', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitcher', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Bacon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Alexandria', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Virginia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Charles R. Wolfe Jr. Richard E. Fitcher Bacon & Thomas Virginia
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('MICHEL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('RADER', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('MICHEL', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Ching-Rong', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('overturning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Trademark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Office', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent_Appeals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Interferences', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('``', '``', 'ORG', 'I') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('holding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4935,047', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('9-11', 'CD', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('App', 'NN', '', 'O')
Ching-Rong Wang Wang the District of Columbia the United States Patent and Trademark Office Board of Patent_Appeals and Interferences the `` Board '' 2_and_4 9-11 of U.S.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._07', 'NN', '', 'O') ('/478,411', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'411", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Winner_Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l_Royalty_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('11_F.Supp.2d_18', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('48_USPQ2d_1139_(D.D.C._June_12,_1998)', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Jinn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'411", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Winner_International_Royalty_Corp.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jinn Wu Wu Winner_International_Royalty_Corp. Winner
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('146', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('there', 'RB', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adverse', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('himself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
35 146 1994 Wu Board Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Winner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('superseded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wu Wu
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Board Wu
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 103 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('Other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('asserts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('several', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('outcome', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang Winner California
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Wang California
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Winner_Int', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'", "''", '', 'O') ('l_Royalty_Corp.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('45_USPQ2d_1864', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1998_WL_268279', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D.D.C', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Jan.20', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('1998', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Jan.20 1998
__NEW_SENT__
('Then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conducted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('7', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('day_bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O')
7
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('challenges', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('denial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('rulings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('admission', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('despite', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('similarity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('holding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('revived', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang 1 2 Board 3
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('our', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('2', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1999', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I')
August 2 1999
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('factual_findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('err', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ultimate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('non-obviousness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('admitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('documentary_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('refusing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('affirm', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('addition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('owns', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4738,127', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('embodiment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('anti-theft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('The', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Club', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Johnson `` The Club ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('principal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Taiwanese', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('manufacturer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Club', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('commercial_embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'ORG', 'B') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'I') ('Super', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Club', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("''", "''", 'ORG', 'I') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Ultra', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Club', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('The', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Club', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('GL', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Wu Taiwanese Club `` The Super Club '' `` The Club GL ''
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('automobile', 'NN', '', 'O') ('*1343', 'FW', '', 'O') ('anti-theft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('mounted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('across', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('locked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('self-locking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Club', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('locked', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial_embodiments', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('prevent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('theft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('blocking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('turning', 'VBG', '', 'O')
Club
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('different', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dead-bolt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('so', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('may', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('thought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B')
Johnson Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('While', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('dead-bolt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('system', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('more', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('secure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('convenient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('required', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lock', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('locks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('itself', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key.1', 'NN', '', 'O')
Johnson Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('manufactures', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('anti-theft', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Taiwan', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('exports', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('sells', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('them', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('distributor', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang Taiwan U.S. United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('commercially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('The', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Gorilla', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Grip', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ("''", "''", 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Wang `` The Gorilla Grip ''
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent_application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('directed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Gorilla', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Grip', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('U.S._Patent_No._4887,443', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'443_patent", "''", '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Wang Gorilla Grip
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('discovered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'443_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('very', 'RB', '', 'O') ('similar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('then-pending', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('later', 'RB', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('decided', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('provoke', 'VB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('divisional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('submitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('identical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('broadest', 'JJS', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'443_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
1990 Wu Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('8', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('declared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proceeding', 'NN', '', 'O') ('began', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('determine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
August 8 1991 Wu Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('additional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'411", 'NNS', '', 'O') ('application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('eventually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wu
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference_proceeding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('preliminary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('interference', 'NN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('hence', 'RB', '', 'O') ('both', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("'", 'POS', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('unpatentable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Wang 35 103 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('apparently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acknowledging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('priority', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('questionable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ("'443_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('prove', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Wang Wu Wu
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('final', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('split', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('affected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('except', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('1_and_3', 'CD', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Board
__NEW_SENT__
('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('both', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('141', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', 'DATE', 'I') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('146', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('while', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('146', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Wu 35 141 ( 1994 the District of Columbia 35 146 Wang section 146 California
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('141', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('146', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('proceed', 'VB', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('Columbia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Wu 141 Board 146 Wu the District of Columbia
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('129_F.3d_1237', 'CD', '', 'O') ('44_USPQ2d_1641_(Fed.Cir.1997)', 'CD', '', 'O')
Wu Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('first', 'RB', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('responded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('timely', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('fashion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('notice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('election', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('filing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('146', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Columbia', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wu', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('choice', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('forum', 'NN', '', 'O') ('governed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Wu first Wang section 146
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1242-43', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('44', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('USPQ2d', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1645-46', 'CD', '', 'O')
44
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('141', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('superseded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', '', 'O') ('146', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')
141 146
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1238', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('44', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('USPQ2d', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1642', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1238 44 USPQ2d 1642
__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
first Wang California
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('45_USPQ2d_1864', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seven-day_bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('prior_art', 'NN', '', 'O')
2_and_4
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('11_F.Supp.2d_18', 'CD', '', 'O') ('48_USPQ2d_11392', 'CD', '', 'O') ('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('principal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1344', 'NFP', '', 'O') ('determination', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('well', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('affidavits', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Winner four
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('expert', 'NN', '', 'O') ('witness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('testify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('opinion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('regarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('underlying', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('determinations', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Wang one
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('admitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O')
Board
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('focus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior_art_references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('he', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('rendered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O')
four Wang Board
__NEW_SENT__
('These', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('mentioned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('above', 'RB', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._3462,982', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Taiwan', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('App', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
Johnson U.S. No._3462,982 Moore Taiwan Patent App
__NEW_SENT__
('No._74210,699', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('WuROC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('French', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('App', 'NN', '', 'O')
French
__NEW_SENT__
('No._2566,398', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Grimaldi', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Grimaldi
__NEW_SENT__
('Winner', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('introduced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('Super', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Club', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('line', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('products', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Winner Super Club
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Like', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('disclosed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('immobilizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('inserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('telescoping', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('arms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('outward', 'RB', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('hooks', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('end', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('engage', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('arms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O')
Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('self-locking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('uses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dead-bolt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('lock', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('user', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('turn', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('putting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wheel', 'NN', '', 'O')
Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('Moore', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('steering_wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('lock', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('unfolds', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Y', 'NNP', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('shape', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('utilizes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('self-locking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('require', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('WuROC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('wheel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('brake_pedal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('versatile', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('locking', 'NN', '', 'O') ('core', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('can', 'MD', '', 'O') ('accommodate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dead-bolt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('self-locking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('but', 'CC', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('disclose', 'VB', '', 'O') ('either', 'DT', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanisms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Grimaldi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('discloses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two-piece', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('clutch', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('brake_pedal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('floorboard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('firewall', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('car', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('figures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('appear', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('show', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('rod', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('pawl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('locks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('place', 'NN', '', 'O')
Grimaldi
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('presence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sufficient', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('prior_art_references', 'NNS', '', 'O')
four
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('skilled', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('considered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('dead-bolt-type', 'NN', '', 'O') ('locking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('disadvantageous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compared', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Moore', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('WuROC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('devices', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('extent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('key', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('setting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('in', 'RP', '', 'O') ('position', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('adjusting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('device', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('motivated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('make', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('easier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('albeit', 'IN', '', 'O') ('less', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('secure', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('replacing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('dead-bolt', 'NN', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Johnson', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('self-locking', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ratcheting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('mechanism', 'NN', '', 'O')
Board 1 Johnson Moore Johnson 2 Johnson Johnson
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual_findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('clearly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('erroneous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('adequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('references', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('23-24', 'CD', 'TIME', 'B') ('48', 'CD', 'TIME', 'I') ('USPQ2d', 'NNS', 'TIME', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1143-44', 'CD', '', 'O')
Winner 11 23-24 48 USPQ2d
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Winner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('established', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('commercial_success', 'NN', '', 'O') ('resulting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('improvement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('even', 'RB', '', 'O') ('though', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('such', 'PDT', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('immaterial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('light', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('failure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('establish', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prima', 'NN', '', 'O') ('facie', 'NN', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Accordingly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('inventions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('2_and_4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'047_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('overturned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O')
2_and_4 Board
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('25', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('48', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('USPQ2d', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1145', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
25 48 1145
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('contending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('should', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('substantial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('standard', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('rather', 'RB', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('said', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('doing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('review', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('error', 'NN', '', 'O')
Wang
__NEW_SENT__
('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('asserts', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('incorrectly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('abused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('admitting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('challenged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('documentary_evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('testimony', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('duplicative', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Board', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('record', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('denying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Wang', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Central_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('California', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Wang Board Wang California
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('have', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1295', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 3 1994
__NEW_SENT__
