('231_F.3d_1339', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('YAMANOUCHI', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACEUTICAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('CO.', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('LTD.', ':', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')
YAMANOUCHI PHARMACEUTICAL CO. LTD. Plaintiff-Appellee
__NEW_SENT__
('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellee', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('DANBURY', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('PHARMACAL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('INC.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schein_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marsam_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Defendants-Appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Merck & DANBURY PHARMACAL INC. Schein_Pharmaceutical Inc. Marsam_Pharmaceuticals Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('No._99-1521', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Decided', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Nov._3,_2000', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('En', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Dec._14,_2000', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('anti-ulcer', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('competitor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('who', 'WP', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Richard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Owen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('21_F.Supp.2d_366', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
United_States_District_Court Richard Owen 21_F.Supp.2d_366
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rader', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'RB', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('baseless', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('warranted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('award', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Court of Appeals Rader Circuit_Judge 1 2 ANDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Affirmed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1340', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Robert', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Baechtold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fitzpatrick', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cella', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Harper', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('&', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Scinto', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellees', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Robert L. Baechtold New_York New_York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Hugh', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Barrett', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('V.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Slater', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('E.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Solander', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Amr', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('O.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Aly', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Hugh C. Barrett Brian V. Slater William E. Solander Amr O. Aly
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Paul', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Matukaitis', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Krovatin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rahway', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Jersey', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Merck & Co. Inc. Paul D. Matukaitis William Krovatin Merck & Co. Inc. Rahway New Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lynch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Nicolas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('G.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Barzoukas', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gerard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Devlin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jr.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('White', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Durkee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Houston', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Texas', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B')
Merck & Co. Inc. John F. Lynch Gerard M. Devlin Jr. Arnold White & Durkee Houston Texas
__NEW_SENT__
('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Alper', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pontani', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Lieberman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('New', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('*1341', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('York', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants-appellants', 'NNS', '', 'O')
William A. Alper Cohen Pontani Lieberman & Pavane New_York New *1341 York
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Thomas', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pontani', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Michael', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('C.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Stuart', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Myron', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Cohen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Julia', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('S.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Kim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pavane', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Thomas C. Pontani Cohen Julia S. Kim Martin B. Pavane
__NEW_SENT__
('James', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('F.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hurst', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Winston', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Strawn', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Illinois', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amicus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('curiae', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('National', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Alliance', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
James F. Hurst Winston & Strawn Chicago Illinois National Pharmaceutical Alliance
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Christine', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Siwik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Christine J. Siwik
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('RADER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('GAJARSA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('RADER', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_District_Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Southern_District', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('New_York', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('upheld', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No._4283,408', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('favor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Ltd.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Merck', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
JMOL United_States_District_Court 4 U.S. Yamanouchi Pharmaceutical Co. Ltd. Merck & Yamanouchi
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharm', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Co.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmacal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('21_F.Supp.2d_366', 'CD', '', 'O') ('370', 'CD', '', 'O') ('48_USPQ2d_1741', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1744', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('S.D.N.Y.1998', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi Pharm Co. Danbury Pharmacal Inc.
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendants', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Pharmacal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', 'ORG', 'I') ('Schein_Pharmaceutical', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Inc.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Schein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marsam_Pharmaceuticals', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Marsam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Danbury Pharmacal Inc. Danbury ) Schein Marsam_Pharmaceuticals Inc. Marsam Yamanouchi
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('378', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
378
__NEW_SENT__
('Because', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('correctly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('upheld', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('abuse', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('awarding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('affirms', 'VBZ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('11', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1981', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('relates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inhibitors', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('gastric', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secretion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi August 11 1981
__NEW_SENT__
('Claim', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('4', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('only', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('treating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('heartburn', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('ulcers', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Claim 4
__NEW_SENT__
('Famotidine', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('belongs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('class', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('histamine2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antagonists', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('H2_antagonists', 'NNPS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('inhibit', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('illustrates', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('structure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('H2_antagonists', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('includes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('substituted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('heterocycle', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('group', 'NN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('alkyl', 'NN', '', 'O') ('containing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('chain', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('called', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bridge', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('polar', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('tail', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('connected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('order', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('?', '.', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Figure', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1*', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('Famotidine', 'NNP', '', 'O')
1*
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'DATE', 'B') ('1960s', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('70s', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufacturers', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('searched', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('H2_antagonists', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('improved', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('pharmacological', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('including', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('low', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('toxicity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('high', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('activity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lack', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effects', 'NNS', '', 'O')
the 1960s 70s
__NEW_SENT__
('Research', 'NN', '', 'O') ('revealed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('hundreds', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('thousands', 'NNS', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('potential', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
hundreds of thousands
__NEW_SENT__
('Indeed', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pharmaceutical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('companies', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('synthesized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('more', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('11,000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('H2', 'NN', '', 'O') ('antagonist', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O')
more than 11,000
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'FAC', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('371', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Yamanouchi 21 F.Supp.2d 371
__NEW_SENT__
('Very', 'RB', '', 'O') ('rarely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('however', 'RB', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('pharmacologically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('H2_antagonists', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Notable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('failures', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('include', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('tiotidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('cancer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rats', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('burimamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('ineffective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dosing', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('metiamide', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('white', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('blood', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cell', 'NN', '', 'O') ('loss', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('lupitidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('pre-cancerous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('lesions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('rats', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('oxmetidine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('caused', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('hepatitis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('11,000', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('candidates', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('fewer', 'JJR', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('than', 'IN', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('fifty', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('showed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('enough', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('promise', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('warrant', 'VB', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('clinical', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trials', 'NNS', '', 'O')
11,000 fewer than fifty
__NEW_SENT__
('Ultimately', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('*1342', 'ADD', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('consumer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('cimetidine,1', 'NN', '', 'O') ('ranitidine,2', 'CD', '', 'O') ('famotidine,3', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('nizatidine.4', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Famotidine', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('extremely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('successful', 'JJ', '', 'O')
FDA four Famotidine
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1996', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('example', 'NN', '', 'O') ('prescription', 'NN', '', 'O') ('sales', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('alone', 'RB', '', 'O') ('reached', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', 'MONEY', 'B') ('690', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('million', 'CD', 'MONEY', 'I') ('dollars', 'NNS', 'MONEY', 'I')
1996 the United States over 690 million dollars
__NEW_SENT__
('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subsidiary', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Schein', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('produces', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('markets', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('generic_drugs', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Danbury Schein
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1997', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Abbreviated_New_Drug_Application', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('generic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O')
January 1997 Danbury the Food and Drug Administration FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('procedure', 'NN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('applicant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('FDA_approval', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_drug', 'NN', '', 'O')
FDA_approval
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'LAW', 'B') ('Hatch-Waxman', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Price', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Competition', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Term', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Restoration', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('Pub.L', 'NNP', '', 'O')
The Hatch-Waxman Act The Drug Price Competition and Patent Term Restoration Act
__NEW_SENT__
('No._98-417', 'IN', '', 'O') ('98_Stat._1585_(1984)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('codified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355_and_35', 'CD', '', 'O') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Cosmetic', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Act', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FDCA', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('Pub.L', 'NN', '', 'O')
21 1994 the Federal Food Drug and Cosmetic Act
__NEW_SENT__
('No._52-675', 'NN', '', 'O') ('52_Stat._1040_(1938)', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('codified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('amended', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±¡±', 'NN', '', 'O') ('301-397', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('permit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('expedite', 'VB', '', 'O') ('FDA_approval', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_version', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
21 301-397 1994 FDA_approval FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('e.g.', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Bayer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('AG', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Elan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Pharm', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Bayer AG Elan Pharm
__NEW_SENT__
('Research', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Corp.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('212_F.3d_1241', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1244', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('54_USPQ2d_1711', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1712', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2000', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Research Corp. 1244
__NEW_SENT__
('Under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDCA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('must', 'MD', '', 'O') ('certify', 'VB', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('statements', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('certification', 'VBP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('II', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('soon', 'RB', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('expire', 'VB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specified', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('III', 'CD', 'PERSON', 'B') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('will', 'MD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'NN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
FDCA ANDA one four II III
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('I', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NN', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 2 IV
__NEW_SENT__
('To', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDCA', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('only', 'RB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('generic_drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('bioequivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('iv', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 2
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('ANDA', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('made', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('paragraph_IV_certification', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O')
Danbury Danbury 4
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('21', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('355', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('j', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('vii', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
21 2 IV
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_26,_1997', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('sent', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('a', 'DT', 'LAW', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Certification', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Notice', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I') ('Letter', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'I')
Danbury Yamanouchi a Patent Certification Notice Letter
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification_letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('informed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ANDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('filing', 'NN', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi Danbury IV ANDA
__NEW_SENT__
('Accompanying', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification_letter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('affidavits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Drs', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Bernard', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Loev', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('K.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Siepler', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('supporting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('certification', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bernard Loev John K. Siepler Danbury
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Notice', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Letter', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('requires', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('analysis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Notice Letter
__NEW_SENT__
('Within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('forty-five', 'JJ', 'DATE', 'B') ('days', 'NNS', 'DATE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('receiving', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certification_letter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('alleging', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('willful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('285', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1994', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
forty-five days Yamanouchi Danbury 35 2 35 285 1994
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
35 4
__NEW_SENT__
('During', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('period', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Marsam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('number', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('paragraph', 'NN', '', 'O') ('IV', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('ANDAs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('seeking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('FDA_approval', 'NN', 'DATE', 'B') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('market', 'VB', '', 'O') ('injectable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('versions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O')
Marsam IV FDA_approval
__NEW_SENT__
('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Marsam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('suits', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('consolidated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Schein', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Marsam', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('hereinafter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('collectively', 'RB', '', 'O') ('referred', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi Marsam two Danbury Schein Marsam Danbury
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('agreed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('After', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('last', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('witness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Fed.R.Civ.P', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Danbury Yamanouchi JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('52', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('52', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('c', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
52 Rule 52
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('clear', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('convincing', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('have', 'VB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('obvious', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('time', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi Danbury 4
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('JMOL', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O')
Yamanouchi JMOL
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'FAC', 'B') ('21', 'CD', 'FAC', 'I') ('F.Supp.2d', 'NN', 'FAC', 'I') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('370', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
Yamanouchi 21 F.Supp.2d 370
__NEW_SENT__
('Specifically', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('shown', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motivation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('combine', 'VB', '', 'O') ('selected', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('portions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('art', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('create', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('specific', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('famotidine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('extraordinary', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('*1343', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Danbury
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('373', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
373
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('characterized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('largely', 'RB', '', 'O') ('hindsight', 'NN', '', 'O') ('speculation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('argument', 'NN', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('adequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('foundation', 'NN', '', 'O')
Danbury
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('370', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('373', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('376', 'CD', '', 'O')
370 373
__NEW_SENT__
('Based', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('those', 'DT', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('determined', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Danbury', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('willfully', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'408_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Danbury
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('district_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('exceptional', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('awarded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('attorney_fees', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('costs', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Yamanouchi', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'B')
Yamanouchi
__NEW_SENT__
('See', 'VB', '', 'O') ('id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('378', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
378
__NEW_SENT__
