('19_F.3d_1418', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
19_F.3d_1418
__NEW_SENT__
('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
United States Court of Appeals Federal Circuit
__NEW_SENT__
('ZENITH', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LABORATORIES', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('INC.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('BRISTOL-MYERS', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('SQUIBB', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('COMPANY', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._92-1527', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('March_24,_1994', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Rehearing', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Denied', 'VBN', 'ORG', 'I') (';', ':', 'ORG', 'I') ('Suggestion', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rehearing', 'VBG', 'ORG', 'I') ('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Banc', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Declined', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('May_26,_1994', 'NNP', '', 'O')
| Rehearing Denied ; Suggestion for Rehearing
__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Seller', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antibiotic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('allegedly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('crystal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('declaratory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('antibiotic', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('assist', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('preingestation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('encapsulation', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('District_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Alfred', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('M.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Wolin', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('seller_induced_infringement', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'JJ', '', 'O')
The United States the District of New_Jersey Alfred M. Wolin J.
__NEW_SENT__
('Appeal', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('taken', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Plager', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('limit', 'VB', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('preingested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ',', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('absence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('evidence', 'NN', '', 'O') ('comparing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('alleged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingestation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('precluded', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('finding', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('seller_induced_infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('3', 'LS', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('matter', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('law', 'NN', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Plager Circuit_Judge 1 2 3
__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1419', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Stephen', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('N.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Shulman', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cadwalader', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wickersham', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Taft', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Washington', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Stephen N. Shulman Wickersham & Taft Washington DC
__NEW_SENT__
('With', 'IN', '', 'O') ('him', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Mark', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('C.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ellenberg', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
Mark C. Ellenberg
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('William', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('L.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mentlik', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Arnold', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Krumholz', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lerner', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Littenberg', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Krumholz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mentlik', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Westfield', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
William L. Mentlik Arnold H. Krumholz David Littenberg Krumholz & Mentlik
__NEW_SENT__
('S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Leslie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Misrock', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Pennie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NN', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
S. Leslie Misrock Pennie & Edmonds
__NEW_SENT__
('Of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counsel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('D.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Coggio', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Jennifer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Gordon', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Kent', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('H.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Cheng', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Pennie', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edmonds', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('New_York_City', 'NN', '', 'O')
Brian D. Coggio Jennifer Gordon Kent H. Cheng Pennie & Edmonds
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('brief', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Frederick', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('B.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Lacey', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('LeBoeuf', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Lamb', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Leiby', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('MacRae', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newark', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('NJ', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Frederick B. Lacey LeBoeuf Lamb Leiby & MacRae
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('PLAGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('SCHALL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('PLAGER', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment_action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('whether', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('becomes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('infringing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('transitory', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('changes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vivo', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('There', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('fact', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issues-what', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('changes', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('actually', 'RB', '', 'O') ('occur', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('ingested', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('how', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('do', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('know', 'VB', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('there', 'EX', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('legal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('issues-does', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('changes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('human', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('body', 'NN', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('way', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('becoming', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('drug', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('original', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('active_ingredient', 'NN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'RBR', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inducement', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Civil', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Action', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('No._91-3423', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff/appellant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Zenith_Laboratories', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ("'s", 'POS', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('commercial_sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'CD', '', 'O') ('induces', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('4,504,657', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (')1', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
the District of New_Jersey Civil Action No._91-3423 Zenith_Laboratories Inc. 's Zenith U.S. 4,504,657
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith_Lab', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol-Myers_Squibb_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('24_USPQ2d_1652', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1992_WL_340761_(D.N.J.1992)', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Zenith_Lab Inc. Zenith II
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('owned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol-Myers_Squibb_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('For', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reasons', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RB', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('reverse', 'VBP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('BACKGROUND', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('antibiotic', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cephalosporin', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('family', 'NN', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bacteria', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('resistant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('penicillin', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('Patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('No._3489,752', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'752_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1970', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
United States 1970 Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'752_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('forms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil-they', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('chemical', 'NN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('per', 'FW', '', 'O') ('se', 'FW', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'752_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('expired', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1987', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1987
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('meantime', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('work', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('find', 'VB', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('useful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('overcome', 'VB', '', 'O') ('problems', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('so', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('usable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('humans', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('task', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('developing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('production', 'NN', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('chemists', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('They', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('developed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('what', 'WP', '', 'O') ('became', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('named', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('discoverers-a', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('new', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('crystalline', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil', 'NN', '', 'O')
one
__NEW_SENT__
('Unlike', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('forms', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('possesses', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('certain', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('pre-ingested', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('powdered', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('related', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('bulk', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('density', 'NN', '', 'O') ('solubility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('stability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('manufacturing-related', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('characteristics', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('make', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('particularly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('suitable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('packaging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('capsules', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1420', 'FW', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('subject', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('single', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('claim', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('1', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B')
1
__NEW_SENT__
('Crystalline', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('7-', 'XX', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('D', 'NN', '', 'O') ('--', ':', '', 'O') ('amino', 'NN', '', 'O') ('--', '.', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('p-hydroxyphenyl-', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('acetamido', 'NN', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('-3-methyl-3-cephem-4-carboxylic', 'HYPH', '', 'O') ('acid', 'NN', '', 'O') ('monohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('exhibiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('essentially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('x-ray', 'NN', '', 'O') ('diffraction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('properties', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('[', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('37-line', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('table', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('relative', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('intensities', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('exhibited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('at', 'IN', '', 'O') ('various', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('scan', 'NN', '', 'O') ('angles', 'NNS', '', 'O') (']', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Bouzard_monohydrate
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('July', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('Zenith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('plaintiff', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment_action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contracted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Spanish', 'JJ', 'NORP', 'B') ('company', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('S.A.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Barcelona', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('become', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('exclusive', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('distributor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('known', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', '.', '', 'O')
July 1988 Spanish Gema S.A. Barcelona Gema United States Gema
__NEW_SENT__
('Cefadroxil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('DC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hemihydrate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('differs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('structurally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate.2', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('undertook', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Food', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Drug', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Administration', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('marketing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('United', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('States', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Cefadroxil DC Bouzard_monohydrate.2 Zenith Gema the Food and Drug Administration FDA the United States
__NEW_SENT__
('Pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('regulations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('abbreviated', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'CD', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('bioequivalent', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil', 'NN', '', 'O') ('monohydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('which', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('already', 'RB', '', 'O') ('been', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('approved', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial_sale', 'NN', '', 'O')
FDA Zenith Gema FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('October', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1990', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('approval.3', 'RB', '', 'O')
October 1990 FDA
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('after', 'IN', '', 'O') ('learning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('efforts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('obtain', 'VB', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('affiliates', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Maryland', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Civil', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('No', 'UH', '', 'O')
June 1991 Zenith Gema FDA Bristol Gema Gema
__NEW_SENT__
('HAR', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('91-1765', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Maryland_action', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('Gema', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('announced', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('abandoning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('plans', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('stipulation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Gema
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('present', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('declaratory_judgment_action', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('District_Court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'GPE', 'B') ('District', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'GPE', 'I') ('New_Jersey', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'I')
Zenith August 1991 Bristol the District of New_Jersey
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('contained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('counts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Zenith four
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('does', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('declaration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('equitably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('estopped', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('asserting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'CD', '', 'O') ('infringes', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Zenith two Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('alleged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('initiating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Maryland_action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('violated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('consent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decree', 'NN', '', 'O') ('previously', 'RB', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('settlement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('between', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('parties', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('engaged', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('unfair', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('competition', 'NN', '', 'O')
three Zenith Bristol four Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('added', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('fifth', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('still', 'RB', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('committed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('antitrust', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('violations', 'NNS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Zenith fifth Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('moved', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('counts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('four', 'CD', '', 'O')
Bristol one two three
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('filed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('cross-motions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('counts', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Zenith
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('December', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('12', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1991', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('dismiss', 'VB', '', 'O') ('count', 'VB', '', 'O') ('three', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('consent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('decree', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ground', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('moot', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('view', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('previous', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dismissal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Maryland_action', 'NN', '', 'O')
December 12 1991 Bristol three
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith_Lab', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Inc.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol-Myers_Squibb_Co.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('24_USPQ2d_1641', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1651', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1991_WL_267892_(D.N.J.1991)', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Zenith_Lab Inc. 1651
__NEW_SENT__
('As', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement_count', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('stayed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pending', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('oral', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O')
Zenith
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1648', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
1648
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('all', 'DT', '', 'O') ('other', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('motions', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1648', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('1650-51', 'CD', '', 'O')
1648
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hearing', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement_count', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('conceded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('being', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('hemihydrate', 'NN', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('literally', 'RB', '', 'O') ('infringe', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('pre-ingested', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('form', 'NN', '', 'O')
Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('nevertheless', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('liable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('product', 'NN', '', 'O') ('converted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('into', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('compound', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('induce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NNP', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
Bristol Zenith two Zenith Zenith 35 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial_court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('raised', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_4,_1992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O')
Bristol Zenith
__NEW_SENT__
('*1421', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('April_16,_1992', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('upon', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('vacated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('March_4,_1992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('decision', 'NN', '', 'O')
April_16,_1992 Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('summary_judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('basis', 'NN', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('two', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('declarations', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('submitted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('reconsideration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('demonstrated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('genuine', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('dispute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('vivo', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('conversion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O')
Zenith Bristol two
__NEW_SENT__
('Consequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('severed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('remaining', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('counts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('tried', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('separately', 'RB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('From', 'IN', '', 'O') ('May_26,_1992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('June_5,_1992', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('conducted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('bench_trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('one', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('rejected', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('theory', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('doctrine', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('equivalents', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('through', 'IN', '', 'O') ('prosecution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O') ('estoppel', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('relinquished', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('coverage', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', '.', '', 'O')
Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('found', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'CD', '', 'O') ('converts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('Bouzard_monohydrate', 'VB', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Since', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('act', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('literal', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thus', 'RB', '', 'O') ('occurs', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patient', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('stomach', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('result', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('ingestion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'CD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concluded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('would', 'MD', '', 'O') ('induce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
Zenith
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('August', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('6', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1992', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('accordance', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('findings', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('entered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Bristol', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
August 6 1992 Bristol
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith', 'IN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('24_USPQ2d_1652', 'NN', '', 'O')
Zenith II
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('271', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('e', 'LS', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('4', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('A', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('ordered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('effective', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('approval', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('FDA', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('cefadroxil_DC', 'CD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('commercial', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('distribution', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('sale', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zenith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('could', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('no', 'RB', '', 'O') ('earlier', 'JJR', '', 'O') ('than', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_12,_2002', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expiration', 'NN', '', 'O') ('date', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ("'657_patent", 'NN', '', 'O')
35 4 1988 FDA Zenith
__NEW_SENT__
('Id.at', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1676', 'CD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('It', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('subsequently', 'RB', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('finality', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('pursuant', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Rule', 'NNP', 'LAW', 'B') ('54', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('b', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Federal', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Rules', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Civil', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Procedure', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
Rule 54 the Federal Rules of Civil Procedure
__NEW_SENT__
('Zenith', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Zenith
__NEW_SENT__
