('815_F.3d_1302', 'XX', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('United_States_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Appeals', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('ZOLTEK', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('CORPORATION', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plaintiff-Appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('UNITED', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('STATES', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('Defendant-Appellee', 'VB', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('No._2014-5082', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('|', 'UH', '', 'O') ('Feb._19,_2016', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Synopsis', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Background', 'NN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('brought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('carbon_fiber_sheet_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('military', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('aircraft', 'NN', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('carbon_fiber_sheet_products', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Following', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('three-day', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('bench', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('issue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Claims', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Edward', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('J.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Damich', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Senior', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Judge', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('ruled', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inadequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O')
the Court of Federal_Claims Edward J. Damich Senior
__NEW_SENT__
('Patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBD', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Holdings', 'NNS', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O') ('The', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Appeals', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Newman', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', 'ORG', 'I') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') (':', ':', '', 'O')
The Court of Appeals Newman Circuit_Judge
__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('having', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('inadequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Reversed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Attorneys', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Law', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Firms', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1303', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Dean', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('A.', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Monco', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Wood', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Phillips', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Katz', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Clark', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('&', 'CC', 'ORG', 'I') ('Mortimer', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('plaintiff-appellant', 'NN', '', 'O')
Dean A. Wood Phillips Katz Clark & Mortimer Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('S', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Mortimer', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('Meredith', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Addy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Katten', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Muchin', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Rosenman', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('LLP', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Chicago', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('IL', 'NNP', '', 'O')
John S Mortimer Meredith Martin Addy Katten Chicago
__NEW_SENT__
('Gary', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Lee', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Hausken', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Commercial', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Litigation', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Branch', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Civil', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Division', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('United_States', 'VBZ', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Department', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Justice', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Washington', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('D.C.', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('argued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant-appellee', 'NN', '', 'O')
Gary Lee Hausken Commercial Litigation Branch Civil Division United_States Department D.C.
__NEW_SENT__
('Also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('represented', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('David', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('M.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Ruddy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Joyce', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('R.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Branda', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('John', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('Fargo', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I')
David M. Ruddy Joyce R. Branda John Fargo
__NEW_SENT__
('Before', 'IN', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('CLEVENGER', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('MOORE', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judges', 'NNS', '', 'O')
NEWMAN CLEVENGER
__NEW_SENT__
('Opinion', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('*1304', 'FW', '', 'O') ('NEWMAN', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Circuit_Judge', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('seeks', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('compensation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('authorization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Departments', 'NNPS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Air', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Force', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Navy', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented_method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('producing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('carbon_fiber_sheet_products', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('claimed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'JJ', 'ORG', 'B') ('Reissue', 'NNP', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'B') ('Patent', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I') ('No', 'NN', 'WORK_OF_ART', 'I')
the Air Force Navy United_States Reissue Patent No
__NEW_SENT__
('Re', 'IN', '', 'O') ('34,162', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('issued', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('January', 'NNP', 'DATE', 'B') ('19', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('1993', 'CD', 'DATE', 'I') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬162_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
34,162 January 19 1993
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬162_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('reissue', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('U.S.', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('No._4728,395', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('issued', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('March_1,_1988', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('inventor', 'VB', '', 'O') ('George', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Boyd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('assigned', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Mr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Boyd', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('employer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Stackpole', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('Fibers', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('Company', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I')
U.S. Patent No._4728,395 George Boyd Boyd Stackpole Fibers Company
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('acquired', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('acquisition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Stackpole', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1988', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B')
Stackpole 1988
__NEW_SENT__
('Litigation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('history', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('March_25,_1996', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('filed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Federal_Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('alleging', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('process', 'NN', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('produce', 'VB', '', 'O') ('carbon_fiber_sheet_materials', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('B-2_Bomber', 'NNP', 'PRODUCT', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('F-22_Fighter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Plane', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('infringed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬162_patent', 'NNP', '', 'O')
March_25,_1996 Zoltek B-2_Bomber
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('third', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O')
third
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('factual', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('background', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('set', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('forth', 'RP', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('prior', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('opinions', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('first', 'JJ', 'ORDINAL', 'B') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('answered', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('question', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('hold', 'VB', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patentee', 'NN', '', 'O') ('has', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('no', 'DT', '', 'O') ('cause', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('when', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('any', 'DT', '', 'O') ('step', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patented_method', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('practiced', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('outside', 'RB', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('F-22_Fighter', 'NNS', '', 'O')
first
__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('442_F.3d_1345', 'IN', '', 'O') ('1353', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2006', 'ADD', 'ORG', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Plager', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('J.', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('dissenting', 'VBG', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1353 Fed.Cir.2006 Plager J. Zoltek I
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('request', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('leave', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('amend', 'VB', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('complaint', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('substitute', 'VB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('defendant', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Lockheed', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Martin', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('general', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('contractor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('F-22_Fighter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('granted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('count', 'NN', '', 'O') ('relating', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('F-22_Fighter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('United_States', 'NNPS', 'ORG', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'LOC', 'B') ('Northern', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('District', 'NNP', 'LOC', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Georgia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('where', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('it', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('reasonably', 'RB', '', 'O') ('plausible', 'JJ', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('had', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('jurisdiction', 'NN', '', 'O') ('over', 'IN', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('suit', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lockheed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B')
Zoltek Lockheed Martin Zoltek the United_States District Court the Northern District Georgia Lockheed
__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('85_Fed.Cl._409', 'CD', '', 'O') ('422', 'CD', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('2009', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
2009
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Lockheed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('motion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('aspect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('certified', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('appeal', 'NN', '', 'O')
Lockheed
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('Federal_Circuit', 'NN', 'PERSON', 'B') ('then', 'RB', '', 'O') ('acted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('part', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('reversed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'NORP', 'B') ('I', 'PRP', '', 'O')
Federal_Circuit Zoltek
__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('recognized', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('liability', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('acts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('that', 'WDT', '', 'O') ('are', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('performed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('authorization', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('consent', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('28', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('U.S.C.¡±', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('1498', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('a', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('Whenever', 'WRB', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('invention', 'NN', '', 'O') ('described', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('covered', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'B') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('used', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufactured', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('without', 'IN', '', 'O') ('license', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ('thereof', 'RB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('lawful', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('right', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('use', 'VB', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('same', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('owner', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('remedy', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shall', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('action', 'NN', '', 'O') ('against', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States_Court', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Federal_Claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('recovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('his', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('reasonable', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('entire', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('compensation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('such', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
28 1498 United_States
__NEW_SENT__
('By', 'IN', '', 'O') ('statute', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contractor', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('immunized', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('liability', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Id', 'NNP', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacture..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('by', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('contractor..', 'NN', '', 'O') ('shall', 'MD', '', 'O') ('be', 'VB', '', 'O') ('construed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('use', 'NN', '', 'O') ('or', 'CC', '', 'O') ('manufacture', 'VB', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ("''", "''", '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('This', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('dismissed', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('Lockheed', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('a', 'DT', '', 'O') ('party', 'NN', '', 'O') ('negated', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('proposed', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('transfer', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Georgia', 'NNP', 'GPE', 'B') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('remanded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', 'ORG', 'B') ('Court', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'I') ('of', 'IN', 'ORG', 'I') ('Federal_Claims', 'NNS', 'ORG', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('inclusion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('counts', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('both', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('F-22_Fighter', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('B-2_Bomber', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Lockheed Georgia the Court of Federal_Claims
__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'IN', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('672_F.3d_1309', 'CD', '', 'O') ('1311', 'CD', 'DATE', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2012', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('en', 'IN', '', 'O') ('banc', 'NN', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('II', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
1311 Zoltek II
__NEW_SENT__
('On', 'IN', '', 'O') ('remand', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('separated', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('discovery', 'NN', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('to', 'TO', '', 'O') ('infringement', 'NN', '', 'O') ('with', 'IN', '', 'O') ('respect', 'NN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('F-22_Fighter', 'NNS', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('sought', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('mandamus', 'NN', '', 'O') ('from', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('concerning', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('these', 'DT', '', 'O') ('actions', 'NNS', '', 'O') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('petition', 'NN', '', 'O') ('was', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('denied', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Zoltek
__NEW_SENT__
('In', 'IN', '', 'O') ('re', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('526_Fed.Appx._956', 'CD', '', 'O') ('957', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('Fed.Cir.2013', 'NNP', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('non-precedential', 'JJ', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')
957
__NEW_SENT__
('Trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('proceeded', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('limited', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('government', 'NN', '', 'O') ('challenged', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('¡¬162_patent', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('sections', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('101', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('103', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('and', 'CC', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('112', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Title', 'NN', 'CARDINAL', 'B') ('35', 'CD', 'CARDINAL', 'I')
¡¬162_patent 101 103 and 112 Title 35
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('sustained', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('eligibility', 'NN', '', 'O') ('under', 'IN', '', 'O') ('section', 'NN', 'LAW', 'B') ('101', 'CD', 'LAW', 'I') (';', ':', '', 'O') ('that', 'DT', '', 'O') ('ruling', 'NN', '', 'O') ('is', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('appealed', 'VBN', '', 'O')
section 101
__NEW_SENT__
('At', 'IN', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('each', 'DT', '', 'O') ('side', 'NN', '', 'O') ('presented', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('an', 'DT', '', 'O') ('expert', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('witness', 'NN', '', 'O') ('Dr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Brian', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Sullivan', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('government', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('Mr.', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Zsolt', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('Rumy', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'I') ('for', 'IN', '', 'O') ('Zoltek', 'NNP', '', 'O')
Brian Sullivan Zsolt Rumy
__NEW_SENT__
('The', 'DT', '', 'O') ('*1305', 'FW', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('held', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('asserted', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('claims', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('invalid', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('on', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('grounds', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('inadequate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek_Corporation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('v.', 'CC', '', 'O') ('United_States', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('No._96-166', 'NN', '', 'O') ('C', 'NN', '', 'O') ('2014_WL_1279152_(Fed.Cl._Mar._31,_2014)', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('(', '-LRB-', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('Op', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('``', '``', '', 'O') (')', '-RRB-', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek', 'JJ', 'PERSON', 'B') ('appeals', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('arguing', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('applied', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('incorrect', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('laws', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('written', 'VBN', '', 'O') ('description', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('obviousness', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('did', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('not', 'RB', '', 'O') ('apply', 'VB', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('appropriate', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('burdens', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('standards', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('proof', 'NN', '', 'O') ('and', 'CC', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('conclusions', 'NNS', '', 'O')
Zoltek
__NEW_SENT__
('Zoltek', 'NNP', 'PERSON', 'B') ('also', 'RB', '', 'O') ('argues', 'VBZ', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('were', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('improperly', 'RB', '', 'O') ('bifurcated', 'VBN', '', 'O')
Zoltek
__NEW_SENT__
('We', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('circumstances', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('this', 'DT', '', 'O') ('case', 'NN', '', 'O') ('taking', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('note', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('government', 'NN', '', 'O') ("'s", 'POS', '', 'O') ('official', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('invocation', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('state', 'NN', '', 'O') ('secret', 'JJ', '', 'O') ('privilege', 'NN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('CFC', 'NNP', 'ORG', 'B') ('acted', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('within', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('discretion', 'NN', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('limiting', 'VBG', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('initially', 'RB', '', 'O') ('to', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('issues', 'NNS', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('validity', 'NN', '', 'O')
CFC
__NEW_SENT__
('However', 'RB', '', 'O') ('as', 'IN', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('next', 'RB', '', 'O') ('discuss', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('we', 'PRP', '', 'O') ('conclude', 'VBP', '', 'O') ('that', 'IN', '', 'O') ('the', 'DT', '', 'O') ('trial', 'NN', '', 'O') ('court', 'NN', '', 'O') ('erred', 'VBD', '', 'O') ('in', 'IN', '', 'O') ('its', 'PRP$', '', 'O') ('judgment', 'NN', '', 'O') ('of', 'IN', '', 'O') ('patent', 'NN', '', 'O') ('invalidity', 'NN', '', 'O')

__NEW_SENT__
